import { Question } from "../Models/Question.model";

export function getTopicBasedQuestions(quiz_id: string) {
  return questions.filter((question) => {
    return question.quiz_id == Number(quiz_id);
  })
}

export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question_id: 1,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "What is the formula for Newton's second law of motion?",
    alpha: "F = ma",
    beta: "F = m/g",
    charlie: "F = mv",
    delta: "F = a/m",
    correct_answer: "F = ma",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 2,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "Who formulated the laws of motion?",
    alpha: "Isaac Newton",
    beta: "Galileo Galilei",
    charlie: "Albert Einstein",
    delta: "Nikola Tesla",
    correct_answer: "Isaac Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 3,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "What is the SI unit of force?",
    alpha: "Newton",
    beta: "Joule",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Pascal",
    correct_answer: "Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 4,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "According to Newton's first law of motion, an object at rest will stay at rest unless...",
    alpha: "acted upon by an unbalanced force",
    beta: "subjected to air resistance",
    charlie: "accelerated by gravity",
    delta: "rotated by an external force",
    correct_answer: "acted upon by an unbalanced force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 5,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "What is the formula for gravitational force between two objects?",
    alpha: "F = G(m1 * m2) / r^2",
    beta: "F = m1 * a",
    charlie: "F = P / A",
    delta: "F = Q / V",
    correct_answer: "F = G(m1 * m2) / r^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 6,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "Which law of motion is also known as the law of inertia?",
    alpha: "Newton's First Law",
    beta: "Newton's Second Law",
    charlie: "Newton's Third Law",
    delta: "Hooke's Law",
    correct_answer: "Newton's First Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 7,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "What is the rate of change of velocity called?",
    alpha: "Acceleration",
    beta: "Speed",
    charlie: "Velocity",
    delta: "Displacement",
    correct_answer: "Acceleration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 8,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "In which unit is force typically measured?",
    alpha: "Newton",
    beta: "Joule",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Meter",
    correct_answer: "Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 9,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "What is the weight of an object?",
    alpha: "Force of gravity on the object",
    beta: "Mass of the object",
    charlie: "Acceleration of the object",
    delta: "Volume of the object",
    correct_answer: "Force of gravity on the object",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 10,
    quiz_id: 1,
    question: "Which of Newton's laws explains why a rocket moves forward when gases are expelled backward?",
    alpha: "Newton's First Law",
    beta: "Newton's Second Law",
    charlie: "Newton's Third Law",
    delta: "Hooke's Law",
    correct_answer: "Newton's Third Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 11,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What is the branch of physics that deals with the motion of objects without considering the forces that cause the motion?",
    alpha: "Dynamics",
    beta: "Statics",
    charlie: "Kinematics",
    delta: "Thermodynamics",
    correct_answer: "Kinematics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 12,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What is the equation for average speed?",
    alpha: "Speed = Distance / Time",
    beta: "Speed = Time / Distance",
    charlie: "Distance = Speed * Time",
    delta: "Time = Speed / Distance",
    correct_answer: "Speed = Distance / Time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 13,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "If an object's velocity is constant, what can be said about its acceleration?",
    alpha: "Acceleration is zero",
    beta: "Acceleration is constant",
    charlie: "Acceleration is increasing",
    delta: "Acceleration is decreasing",
    correct_answer: "Acceleration is zero",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 14,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What is the SI unit of acceleration?",
    alpha: "Meter",
    beta: "Newton",
    charlie: "Meter per second squared",
    delta: "Joule",
    correct_answer: "Meter per second squared",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 15,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "A car accelerates from 10 m/s to 30 m/s in 5 seconds. What is its acceleration?",
    alpha: "4 m/s²",
    beta: "6 m/s²",
    charlie: "8 m/s²",
    delta: "10 m/s²",
    correct_answer: "4 m/s²",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 16,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What does the slope of a velocity-time graph represent?",
    alpha: "Distance",
    beta: "Acceleration",
    charlie: "Speed",
    delta: "Displacement",
    correct_answer: "Acceleration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 17,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "If an object is in free fall, what is the value of acceleration due to gravity near the surface of the Earth?",
    alpha: "9.8 m/s²",
    beta: "5.0 m/s²",
    charlie: "10.0 m/s²",
    delta: "8.0 m/s²",
    correct_answer: "9.8 m/s²",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 18,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What is the area under the velocity-time graph equal to?",
    alpha: "Displacement",
    beta: "Speed",
    charlie: "Acceleration",
    delta: "Time",
    correct_answer: "Displacement",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 19,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "If an object is moving with constant speed, what can be said about its acceleration?",
    alpha: "Acceleration is zero",
    beta: "Acceleration is constant",
    charlie: "Acceleration is increasing",
    delta: "Acceleration is decreasing",
    correct_answer: "Acceleration is zero",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 20,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: "What is the equation for calculating displacement in terms of initial velocity, time, and acceleration?",
    alpha: "d = ut + (1/2)at²",
    beta: "d = vt - (1/2)at²",
    charlie: "d = ut + vat",
    delta: "d = 2ut + at²",
    correct_answer: "d = ut + (1/2)at²",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 21,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the branch of physics that deals with the forces that cause motion?",
    alpha: "Kinematics",
    beta: "Statics",
    charlie: "Dynamics",
    delta: "Thermodynamics",
    correct_answer: "Dynamics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 22,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "According to Newton's second law of motion, what is the relationship between force, mass, and acceleration?",
    alpha: "F = m / a",
    beta: "F = a / m",
    charlie: "F = m * a",
    delta: "F = m + a",
    correct_answer: "F = m * a",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 23,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the SI unit of force?",
    alpha: "Newton",
    beta: "Joule",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Pascal",
    correct_answer: "Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 24,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "If a force is applied to an object in the direction of its motion, what effect does it have on the object's speed?",
    alpha: "Increases speed",
    beta: "Decreases speed",
    charlie: "No effect on speed",
    delta: "Reverses direction",
    correct_answer: "Increases speed",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 25,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the net force acting on an object in equilibrium?",
    alpha: "Zero",
    beta: "Equal to mass",
    charlie: "Infinity",
    delta: "Depends on velocity",
    correct_answer: "Zero",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 26,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the force exerted by a surface to support the weight of an object resting on it?",
    alpha: "Frictional force",
    beta: "Tension force",
    charlie: "Normal force",
    delta: "Applied force",
    correct_answer: "Normal force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 27,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "If the net force acting on an object is zero, what can be said about its motion?",
    alpha: "It is at rest",
    beta: "It is moving with constant speed",
    charlie: "It is accelerating",
    delta: "It is in free fall",
    correct_answer: "It is moving with constant speed",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 28,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the force that opposes the motion of objects sliding past each other?",
    alpha: "Tension force",
    beta: "Frictional force",
    charlie: "Normal force",
    delta: "Applied force",
    correct_answer: "Frictional force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 29,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "According to Newton's third law of motion, if object A exerts a force on object B, what is the reaction?",
    alpha: "Force exerted by B on A is greater",
    beta: "Force exerted by B on A is equal",
    charlie: "Force exerted by A on B is greater",
    delta: "No reaction force",
    correct_answer: "Force exerted by B on A is equal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 30,
    quiz_id: 3,
    question: "What is the force exerted by a stretched or compressed spring?",
    alpha: "Tension force",
    beta: "Frictional force",
    charlie: "Normal force",
    delta: "Spring force",
    correct_answer: "Spring force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 31,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "What is the formula for Newton's second law of motion?",
    alpha: "F = ma",
    beta: "F = m/g",
    charlie: "F = mv",
    delta: "F = a/m",
    correct_answer: "F = ma",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 32,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "Who formulated the laws of motion?",
    alpha: "Isaac Newton",
    beta: "Galileo Galilei",
    charlie: "Albert Einstein",
    delta: "Nikola Tesla",
    correct_answer: "Isaac Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 33,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "What is the SI unit of force?",
    alpha: "Newton",
    beta: "Joule",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Pascal",
    correct_answer: "Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 34,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "According to Newton's first law of motion, an object at rest will stay at rest unless...",
    alpha: "acted upon by an unbalanced force",
    beta: "subjected to air resistance",
    charlie: "accelerated by gravity",
    delta: "rotated by an external force",
    correct_answer: "acted upon by an unbalanced force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 35,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "What is the formula for gravitational force between two objects?",
    alpha: "F = G(m1 * m2) / r^2",
    beta: "F = m1 * a",
    charlie: "F = P / A",
    delta: "F = Q / V",
    correct_answer: "F = G(m1 * m2) / r^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 36,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "Which law of motion is also known as the law of inertia?",
    alpha: "Newton's First Law",
    beta: "Newton's Second Law",
    charlie: "Newton's Third Law",
    delta: "Hooke's Law",
    correct_answer: "Newton's First Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 37,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "What is the rate of change of velocity called?",
    alpha: "Acceleration",
    beta: "Speed",
    charlie: "Velocity",
    delta: "Displacement",
    correct_answer: "Acceleration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 38,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "In which unit is force typically measured?",
    alpha: "Newton",
    beta: "Joule",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Meter",
    correct_answer: "Newton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 39,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "What is the weight of an object?",
    alpha: "Force of gravity on the object",
    beta: "Mass of the object",
    charlie: "Acceleration of the object",
    delta: "Volume of the object",
    correct_answer: "Force of gravity on the object",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 40,
    quiz_id: 4,
    question: "Which of Newton's laws explains why a rocket moves forward when gases are expelled backward?",
    alpha: "Newton's First Law",
    beta: "Newton's Second Law",
    charlie: "Newton's Third Law",
    delta: "Hooke's Law",
    correct_answer: "Newton's Third Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 41,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the branch of physics that studies the behavior of fluids, both liquids and gases?",
    alpha: "Thermodynamics",
    beta: "Fluid Dynamics",
    charlie: "Fluid Mechanics",
    delta: "Hydrodynamics",
    correct_answer: "Fluid Mechanics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 42,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the equation that relates pressure, density, and height in a fluid at rest?",
    alpha: "P = ρgh",
    beta: "P = h/ρg",
    charlie: "P = gh/ρ",
    delta: "P = g/ρh",
    correct_answer: "P = ρgh",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 43,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the SI unit of pressure?",
    alpha: "Pascal",
    beta: "Newton",
    charlie: "Joule",
    delta: "Watt",
    correct_answer: "Pascal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 44,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a fluid flows faster in a narrow section of a pipe compared to a wider section?",
    alpha: "Turbulence",
    beta: "Laminar flow",
    charlie: "Viscosity",
    delta: "Bernoulli's principle",
    correct_answer: "Bernoulli's principle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 45,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "Which law states that the volume flow rate of an incompressible fluid remains constant along a tube of varying cross-sectional area?",
    alpha: "Archimedes' principle",
    beta: "Pascal's law",
    charlie: "Boyle's law",
    delta: "Continuity equation",
    correct_answer: "Continuity equation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 46,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the term for the force per unit area exerted on a surface by the weight of the air above that surface in the atmosphere?",
    alpha: "Pressure",
    beta: "Buoyancy",
    charlie: "Viscosity",
    delta: "Surface tension",
    correct_answer: "Pressure",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 47,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "In a fluid at rest, how is pressure distributed with depth?",
    alpha: "Linearly",
    beta: "Exponentially",
    charlie: "Uniformly",
    delta: "Inversely",
    correct_answer: "Linearly",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 48,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the term for the force exerted by a fluid against a surface as it flows over it?",
    alpha: "Pressure",
    beta: "Buoyancy",
    charlie: "Viscosity",
    delta: "Drag force",
    correct_answer: "Drag force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 49,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What is the term for the resistance of a fluid to flow?",
    alpha: "Pressure",
    beta: "Buoyancy",
    charlie: "Viscosity",
    delta: "Surface tension",
    correct_answer: "Viscosity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 50,
    quiz_id: 5,
    question: "What law describes the upward buoyant force exerted on a body immersed in a fluid?",
    alpha: "Archimedes' principle",
    beta: "Pascal's law",
    charlie: "Boyle's law",
    delta: "Bernoulli's principle",
    correct_answer: "Archimedes' principle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 51,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the Zeroth Law of Thermodynamics?",
    alpha: "Energy is conserved",
    beta: "Heat flows from hot to cold",
    charlie: "Temperature is a measure of average kinetic energy",
    delta: "If two systems are each in thermal equilibrium with a third system, they are in thermal equilibrium with each other",
    correct_answer: "If two systems are each in thermal equilibrium with a third system, they are in thermal equilibrium with each other",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 52,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the First Law of Thermodynamics also known as?",
    alpha: "Law of Conservation of Energy",
    beta: "Law of Conservation of Matter",
    charlie: "Law of Entropy",
    delta: "Law of Motion",
    correct_answer: "Law of Conservation of Energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 53,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "According to the Second Law of Thermodynamics, what is the direction of natural heat flow?",
    alpha: "From cold to hot",
    beta: "From high temperature to low temperature",
    charlie: "From low temperature to high temperature",
    delta: "From the source to the sink",
    correct_answer: "From high temperature to low temperature",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 54,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the formula for the efficiency of a heat engine?",
    alpha: "Efficiency = (Work output / Heat input) * 100%",
    beta: "Efficiency = (Heat input / Work output) * 100%",
    charlie: "Efficiency = (Work input / Heat output) * 100%",
    delta: "Efficiency = (Heat output / Work input) * 100%",
    correct_answer: "Efficiency = (Work output / Heat input) * 100%",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 55,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the Third Law of Thermodynamics primarily concerned with?",
    alpha: "Entropy",
    beta: "Enthalpy",
    charlie: "Temperature",
    delta: "Heat",
    correct_answer: "Entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 56,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What does the Carnot cycle describe?",
    alpha: "A heat engine",
    beta: "A refrigerator",
    charlie: "A heat pump",
    delta: "A thermodynamic process",
    correct_answer: "A heat engine",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 57,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "In which thermodynamic process does the system neither absorb nor release heat?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Adiabatic process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 58,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the concept of absolute zero in thermodynamics?",
    alpha: "The lowest possible temperature",
    beta: "The highest possible temperature",
    charlie: "The temperature at which water boils",
    delta: "The temperature at which water freezes",
    correct_answer: "The lowest possible temperature",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 59,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "What is the law that states the entropy of an isolated system always increases?",
    alpha: "Zeroth Law of Thermodynamics",
    beta: "First Law of Thermodynamics",
    charlie: "Second Law of Thermodynamics",
    delta: "Third Law of Thermodynamics",
    correct_answer: "Second Law of Thermodynamics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 60,
    quiz_id: 6,
    question: "In which thermodynamic process does the system exchange heat with the surroundings, but the internal energy remains constant?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isobaric process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 61,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the process of heat transfer through direct contact of particles in a substance?",
    alpha: "Conduction",
    beta: "Convection",
    charlie: "Radiation",
    delta: "Insulation",
    correct_answer: "Conduction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 62,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "How is heat transferred in fluids (liquids and gases) by the movement of the fluid itself?",
    alpha: "Conduction",
    beta: "Convection",
    charlie: "Radiation",
    delta: "Insulation",
    correct_answer: "Convection",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 63,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "In which process does heat transfer through electromagnetic waves?",
    alpha: "Conduction",
    beta: "Convection",
    charlie: "Radiation",
    delta: "Insulation",
    correct_answer: "Radiation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 64,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "Which material is a good conductor of heat?",
    alpha: "Rubber",
    beta: "Plastic",
    charlie: "Copper",
    delta: "Wood",
    correct_answer: "Copper",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 65,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the unit of heat energy in the International System of Units (SI)?",
    alpha: "Joule",
    beta: "Calorie",
    charlie: "Watt",
    delta: "Newton",
    correct_answer: "Joule",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 66,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the principle behind a thermos bottle that helps keep liquids hot or cold?",
    alpha: "Conduction",
    beta: "Convection",
    charlie: "Radiation",
    delta: "Insulation",
    correct_answer: "Radiation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 67,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the process of heat transfer in a vacuum where no medium is present?",
    alpha: "Conduction",
    beta: "Convection",
    charlie: "Radiation",
    delta: "Insulation",
    correct_answer: "Radiation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 68,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "Which color is the best emitter and absorber of radiation in the visible spectrum?",
    alpha: "Red",
    beta: "Green",
    charlie: "Blue",
    delta: "White",
    correct_answer: "Black",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 69,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the name of the law that states the rate of heat transfer is directly proportional to the temperature difference?",
    alpha: "Newton's First Law",
    beta: "Newton's Second Law",
    charlie: "Newton's Third Law",
    delta: "Newton's Law of Cooling",
    correct_answer: "Newton's Law of Cooling",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 70,
    quiz_id: 7,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a material allows heat to pass through it easily?",
    alpha: "Conductor",
    beta: "Insulator",
    charlie: "Reflector",
    delta: "Refractor",
    correct_answer: "Conductor",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 71,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "In which thermodynamic process does the system exchange heat with the surroundings, and the internal energy remains constant?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isothermal process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 72,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What is the term for a thermodynamic process in which no heat is exchanged with the surroundings?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Adiabatic process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 73,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "Which thermodynamic process occurs at constant pressure?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isobaric process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 74,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What is the term for a thermodynamic process in which volume remains constant?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isometric process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 75,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "In which thermodynamic process does the system exchange neither heat nor matter with the surroundings?",
    alpha: "Closed system",
    beta: "Open system",
    charlie: "Isolated system",
    delta: "Adiabatic system",
    correct_answer: "Isolated system",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 76,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What is the equation for the work done in an isobaric process?",
    alpha: "W = PΔV",
    beta: "W = nRT",
    charlie: "W = Q",
    delta: "W = ΔU",
    correct_answer: "W = PΔV",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 77,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What is the term for the point on a temperature-pressure phase diagram where all three phases (solid, liquid, and gas) coexist?",
    alpha: "Critical point",
    beta: "Triple point",
    charlie: "Transition point",
    delta: "Equilibrium point",
    correct_answer: "Triple point",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 78,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "In which thermodynamic process does the temperature remain constant?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isothermal process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 79,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What is the term for a process that occurs at constant volume?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Isometric process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 80,
    quiz_id: 8,
    question: "What law states that the pressure of a given mass of gas is directly proportional to its absolute temperature, provided the volume remains constant?",
    alpha: "Boyle's law",
    beta: "Charles's law",
    charlie: "Gay-Lussac's law",
    delta: "Avogadro's law",
    correct_answer: "Gay-Lussac's law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 81,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the thermodynamic property that describes the measure of disorder or randomness in a system?",
    alpha: "Enthalpy",
    beta: "Entropy",
    charlie: "Internal energy",
    delta: "Gibbs free energy",
    correct_answer: "Entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 82,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "In which process does the entropy of an isolated system always increase?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Adiabatic process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 83,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the term for a process that occurs without the exchange of heat with the surroundings?",
    alpha: "Isobaric process",
    beta: "Isothermal process",
    charlie: "Adiabatic process",
    delta: "Isometric process",
    correct_answer: "Adiabatic process",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 84,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the thermodynamic property that represents the total heat content of a system?",
    alpha: "Enthalpy",
    beta: "Entropy",
    charlie: "Internal energy",
    delta: "Gibbs free energy",
    correct_answer: "Enthalpy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 85,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "In an exothermic reaction, is the change in enthalpy positive or negative?",
    alpha: "Positive",
    beta: "Negative",
    charlie: "Zero",
    delta: "Depends on the reaction",
    correct_answer: "Negative",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 86,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the mathematical expression for the change in enthalpy (ΔH) in a chemical reaction?",
    alpha: "ΔH = q + PΔV",
    beta: "ΔH = q - PΔV",
    charlie: "ΔH = q",
    delta: "ΔH = PΔV",
    correct_answer: "ΔH = q + PΔV",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 87,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "Which law states that the total entropy of an isolated system will always increase over time?",
    alpha: "Zeroth Law of Thermodynamics",
    beta: "First Law of Thermodynamics",
    charlie: "Second Law of Thermodynamics",
    delta: "Third Law of Thermodynamics",
    correct_answer: "Second Law of Thermodynamics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 88,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the term for the change in entropy in a reversible process at absolute zero?",
    alpha: "Zeroth entropy",
    beta: "Infinite entropy",
    charlie: "Zero entropy",
    delta: "Negative entropy",
    correct_answer: "Zero entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 89,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "What is the standard unit of entropy in the International System of Units (SI)?",
    alpha: "Joule",
    beta: "Calorie",
    charlie: "Kelvin",
    delta: "Joule per Kelvin",
    correct_answer: "Joule per Kelvin",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 90,
    quiz_id: 9,
    question: "Which property is a measure of the thermal disorder in a system?",
    alpha: "Enthalpy",
    beta: "Entropy",
    charlie: "Internal energy",
    delta: "Gibbs free energy",
    correct_answer: "Entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 91,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "In which thermodynamic application does the conversion of heat into mechanical work occur?",
    alpha: "Refrigeration",
    beta: "Heat exchangers",
    charlie: "Heat engines",
    delta: "Thermal insulation",
    correct_answer: "Heat engines",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 92,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a refrigerator?",
    alpha: "To generate electricity",
    beta: "To heat a space",
    charlie: "To cool a space",
    delta: "To pump water",
    correct_answer: "To cool a space",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 93,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "Which thermodynamic application involves the transfer of heat from a lower-temperature reservoir to a higher-temperature reservoir?",
    alpha: "Refrigeration",
    beta: "Heat exchangers",
    charlie: "Heat engines",
    delta: "Thermal insulation",
    correct_answer: "Heat engines",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 94,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a heat exchanger?",
    alpha: "To generate electricity",
    beta: "To heat a space",
    charlie: "To cool a space",
    delta: "To transfer heat between fluids",
    correct_answer: "To transfer heat between fluids",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 95,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "In which thermodynamic application does the conversion of mechanical work into heat occur?",
    alpha: "Refrigeration",
    beta: "Heat exchangers",
    charlie: "Heat engines",
    delta: "Thermal insulation",
    correct_answer: "Thermal insulation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 96,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of thermal insulation?",
    alpha: "To generate electricity",
    beta: "To heat a space",
    charlie: "To cool a space",
    delta: "To minimize heat transfer",
    correct_answer: "To minimize heat transfer",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 97,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "Which thermodynamic application involves the transfer of heat from a higher-temperature reservoir to a lower-temperature reservoir?",
    alpha: "Refrigeration",
    beta: "Heat exchangers",
    charlie: "Heat engines",
    delta: "Thermal insulation",
    correct_answer: "Refrigeration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 98,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a heat pump?",
    alpha: "To generate electricity",
    beta: "To heat a space",
    charlie: "To cool a space",
    delta: "To transfer heat between reservoirs",
    correct_answer: "To transfer heat between reservoirs",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 99,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "In which thermodynamic application is the focus on maintaining a constant temperature?",
    alpha: "Refrigeration",
    beta: "Heat exchangers",
    charlie: "Heat engines",
    delta: "Thermal insulation",
    correct_answer: "Heat exchangers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 100,
    quiz_id: 10,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of a thermostat?",
    alpha: "To generate electricity",
    beta: "To heat a space",
    charlie: "To cool a space",
    delta: "To regulate temperature",
    correct_answer: "To regulate temperature",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 101,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the fundamental quantity that creates an electric field?",
    alpha: "Charge",
    beta: "Voltage",
    charlie: "Current",
    delta: "Resistance",
    correct_answer: "Charge",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 102,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the SI unit of electric charge?",
    alpha: "Volt",
    beta: "Ampere",
    charlie: "Coulomb",
    delta: "Ohm",
    correct_answer: "Coulomb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 103,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "According to Coulomb's Law, what happens to the force between two charges if the distance between them is doubled?",
    alpha: "The force is halved",
    beta: "The force is quadrupled",
    charlie: "The force is doubled",
    delta: "The force remains the same",
    correct_answer: "The force is halved",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 104,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the direction of the electric field lines produced by a positive charge?",
    alpha: "Away from the charge",
    beta: "Towards the charge",
    charlie: "Circular around the charge",
    delta: "No electric field lines",
    correct_answer: "Away from the charge",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 105,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "In which medium does an electric field experience the least resistance?",
    alpha: "Air",
    beta: "Water",
    charlie: "Vacuum",
    delta: "Rubber",
    correct_answer: "Vacuum",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 106,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the formula for electric force between two charges q1 and q2 separated by a distance r?",
    alpha: "F = (k * q1 * q2) / r^2",
    beta: "F = k * q1 * q2 * r",
    charlie: "F = q1 / q2 * r",
    delta: "F = k * q1 / q2 * r^2",
    correct_answer: "F = (k * q1 * q2) / r^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 107,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the electric field strength at a point in space due to a point charge Q?",
    alpha: "E = (k * Q) / r",
    beta: "E = k * Q * r",
    charlie: "E = Q / (k * r)",
    delta: "E = (Q * r) / k",
    correct_answer: "E = (k * Q) / r",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 108,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the direction of the electric field at a point in space?",
    alpha: "Parallel to the field lines",
    beta: "Perpendicular to the field lines",
    charlie: "Circular around the charge",
    delta: "No direction",
    correct_answer: "Parallel to the field lines",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 109,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the relationship between electric field strength (E) and electric force (F) on a charge (q)?",
    alpha: "F = E * q",
    beta: "E = F / q",
    charlie: "F = q / E",
    delta: "E = F * q",
    correct_answer: "F = E * q",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 110,
    quiz_id: 11,
    question: "What is the term for the property of an object that resists changes in its electric state?",
    alpha: "Conductor",
    beta: "Insulator",
    charlie: "Capacitor",
    delta: "Resistor",
    correct_answer: "Capacitor",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 111,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the fundamental quantity that creates a magnetic field?",
    alpha: "Voltage",
    beta: "Current",
    charlie: "Charge",
    delta: "Resistance",
    correct_answer: "Current",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 112,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the SI unit of magnetic field strength?",
    alpha: "Volt",
    beta: "Ampere",
    charlie: "Tesla",
    delta: "Ohm",
    correct_answer: "Tesla",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 113,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "According to the right-hand rule, what is the direction of the magnetic field around a current-carrying wire?",
    alpha: "Clockwise",
    beta: "Counterclockwise",
    charlie: "Towards the wire",
    delta: "Away from the wire",
    correct_answer: "Counterclockwise",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 114,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "In which medium does a magnetic field experience the least resistance?",
    alpha: "Air",
    beta: "Water",
    charlie: "Vacuum",
    delta: "Iron",
    correct_answer: "Vacuum",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 115,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the force experienced by a charged particle moving in a magnetic field called?",
    alpha: "Electric force",
    beta: "Gravitational force",
    charlie: "Centripetal force",
    delta: "Lorentz force",
    correct_answer: "Lorentz force",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 116,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the formula for the magnetic force (Lorentz force) on a charged particle moving with velocity v in a magnetic field B?",
    alpha: "F = qvB",
    beta: "F = q/Bv",
    charlie: "F = B/qv",
    delta: "F = v/qB",
    correct_answer: "F = qvB",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 117,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the direction of the magnetic field lines around a current-carrying loop?",
    alpha: "Clockwise",
    beta: "Counterclockwise",
    charlie: "Towards the loop",
    delta: "Away from the loop",
    correct_answer: "Counterclockwise",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 118,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the relationship between the strength of a magnetic field (B), the current (I), and the distance from the wire (r) in Ampere's Law?",
    alpha: "B = I * r",
    beta: "B = I / r",
    charlie: "B = I * r^2",
    delta: "B = I / r^2",
    correct_answer: "B = I * r",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 119,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "What is the term for a device that produces a strong magnetic field when an electric current is passed through it?",
    alpha: "Insulator",
    beta: "Magnet",
    charlie: "Resistor",
    delta: "Electromagnet",
    correct_answer: "Electromagnet",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 120,
    quiz_id: 12,
    question: "In which direction does the force act on a current-carrying conductor in a magnetic field, according to Fleming's Left-Hand Rule?",
    alpha: "Along the conductor",
    beta: "Opposite to the magnetic field",
    charlie: "Perpendicular to both the conductor and the magnetic field",
    delta: "Parallel to the magnetic field",
    correct_answer: "Perpendicular to both the conductor and the magnetic field",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 121,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "Who discovered the phenomenon of electromagnetic induction?",
    alpha: "Michael Faraday",
    beta: "Thomas Edison",
    charlie: "Nikola Tesla",
    delta: "James Clerk Maxwell",
    correct_answer: "Michael Faraday",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 122,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a changing magnetic field induces an electromotive force (EMF) in a conductor?",
    alpha: "Ohm's Law",
    beta: "Lenz's Law",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Faraday's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 123,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "According to Faraday's Law of Electromagnetic Induction, what is the relationship between the induced EMF and the rate of change of magnetic flux?",
    alpha: "EMF = ΔΦ/Δt",
    beta: "EMF = Δt/ΔΦ",
    charlie: "EMF = Φ/Δt",
    delta: "EMF = Φ * Δt",
    correct_answer: "EMF = ΔΦ/Δt",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 124,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What is the SI unit of magnetic flux?",
    alpha: "Weber",
    beta: "Tesla",
    charlie: "Ampere",
    delta: "Ohm",
    correct_answer: "Weber",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 125,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "How can the induced EMF in a coil be increased, according to Faraday's Law?",
    alpha: "Increasing the number of turns in the coil",
    beta: "Decreasing the area of the coil",
    charlie: "Reducing the strength of the magnetic field",
    delta: "Slowing down the rate of change of magnetic flux",
    correct_answer: "Increasing the number of turns in the coil",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 126,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What is the direction of the induced current in a conductor according to Lenz's Law?",
    alpha: "In the direction of the magnetic field",
    beta: "Opposite to the direction of the magnetic field",
    charlie: "Perpendicular to the magnetic field",
    delta: "Parallel to the magnetic field",
    correct_answer: "Opposite to the direction of the magnetic field",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 127,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What type of current is induced when the magnetic field within a coil changes with time?",
    alpha: "Direct current (DC)",
    beta: "Alternating current (AC)",
    charlie: "Pulsating current",
    delta: "Steady current",
    correct_answer: "Alternating current (AC)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 128,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What device is commonly used to convert mechanical energy into electrical energy through electromagnetic induction?",
    alpha: "Resistor",
    beta: "Capacitor",
    charlie: "Inductor",
    delta: "Generator",
    correct_answer: "Generator",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 129,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What is the term for the process where a changing current in one coil induces a current in a nearby coil without direct electrical connection?",
    alpha: "Electromagnetic interference",
    beta: "Electromagnetic induction",
    charlie: "Mutual inductance",
    delta: "Self-inductance",
    correct_answer: "Mutual inductance",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 130,
    quiz_id: 13,
    question: "What law states that the induced EMF in a closed loop is equal to the negative rate of change of magnetic flux through the loop?",
    alpha: "Ohm's Law",
    beta: "Lenz's Law",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Lenz's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 131,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "Who formulated the set of equations describing the behavior of electric and magnetic fields, known as Maxwell's Equations?",
    alpha: "Isaac Newton",
    beta: "Albert Einstein",
    charlie: "James Clerk Maxwell",
    delta: "Niels Bohr",
    correct_answer: "James Clerk Maxwell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 132,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "What is the integral form of Maxwell's Equation that relates the electric flux through a closed surface to the total charge enclosed by that surface?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 133,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "Which of Maxwell's Equations states that the net magnetic flux through a closed surface is zero?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 134,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "What is the differential form of Maxwell's Equation that describes how a changing magnetic field produces an electric field?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 135,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "Which of Maxwell's Equations describes the relationship between a changing electric field and a magnetic field?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Ampere's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 136,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "What is the differential form of Maxwell's Equation that relates the electric field to the charge density?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 137,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "Which Maxwell's Equation relates the curl of the magnetic field to the electric current density and the rate of change of electric field?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Ampere's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 138,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "What is the differential form of Maxwell's Equation that relates the magnetic field to the current density and the rate of change of electric field?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Ampere's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 139,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "In Maxwell's Equations, what is the term added by Maxwell to correct Ampere's Law and include the contribution of changing electric fields?",
    alpha: "Displacement current",
    beta: "Conduction current",
    charlie: "Magnetic current",
    delta: "Electric current",
    correct_answer: "Displacement current",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 140,
    quiz_id: 14,
    question: "What is the integral form of Maxwell's Equation that relates the circulation of the magnetic field around a closed loop to the total current passing through that loop?",
    alpha: "Gauss's Law for Electricity",
    beta: "Gauss's Law for Magnetism",
    charlie: "Faraday's Law of Induction",
    delta: "Ampere's Law",
    correct_answer: "Ampere's Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 141,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "Which phenomenon explains the bending of light as it passes through different media?",
    alpha: "Reflection",
    beta: "Refraction",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Interference",
    correct_answer: "Refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 142,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a wave encounters an obstacle and bends around it?",
    alpha: "Reflection",
    beta: "Refraction",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Interference",
    correct_answer: "Diffraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 143,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "Which application uses the principle of electromagnetic induction to generate electrical energy?",
    alpha: "Television",
    beta: "Refrigeration",
    charlie: "Generator",
    delta: "X-ray machine",
    correct_answer: "Generator",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 144,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "In which application does the Doppler effect play a crucial role?",
    alpha: "GPS navigation",
    beta: "Ultrasound imaging",
    charlie: "Sound recording",
    delta: "Spectroscopy",
    correct_answer: "Ultrasound imaging",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 145,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where two waves overlap and create regions of reinforcement and cancellation?",
    alpha: "Reflection",
    beta: "Refraction",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Interference",
    correct_answer: "Interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 146,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "Which application utilizes the principles of both optics and electronics to create images of internal body structures?",
    alpha: "X-ray machine",
    beta: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    charlie: "Electron microscope",
    delta: "Endoscope",
    correct_answer: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 147,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a wave is split into two waves with different polarizations?",
    alpha: "Polarization",
    beta: "Diffraction",
    charlie: "Refraction",
    delta: "Interference",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 148,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "In which application is the principle of conservation of energy crucial to its operation?",
    alpha: "Telescope",
    beta: "Incandescent light bulb",
    charlie: "Microwave oven",
    delta: "Hydroelectric power plant",
    correct_answer: "Hydroelectric power plant",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 149,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "Which phenomenon explains the change in the frequency of a wave due to the motion of the source or the observer?",
    alpha: "Reflection",
    beta: "Refraction",
    charlie: "Doppler effect",
    delta: "Diffraction",
    correct_answer: "Doppler effect",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 150,
    quiz_id: 15,
    question: "In which application is the principle of superposition used to transmit information using binary code?",
    alpha: "Fiber optics communication",
    beta: "Laser surgery",
    charlie: "Nuclear power plant",
    delta: "Satellite communication",
    correct_answer: "Fiber optics communication",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 151,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the law that describes the relationship between the angles of incidence and reflection for light rays striking a mirror?",
    alpha: "Snell's Law",
    beta: "Fermat's Principle",
    charlie: "Law of Reflection",
    delta: "Law of Refraction",
    correct_answer: "Law of Reflection",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 152,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the point on a lens or mirror where parallel light rays either converge or appear to diverge?",
    alpha: "Focal point",
    beta: "Vertex",
    charlie: "Aperture",
    delta: "Principal axis",
    correct_answer: "Focal point",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 153,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What type of lens is thicker at the center than at the edges and converges parallel light rays to a focal point?",
    alpha: "Concave lens",
    beta: "Convex lens",
    charlie: "Diverging lens",
    delta: "Plano-convex lens",
    correct_answer: "Convex lens",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 154,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where a lens fails to focus all colors to the same convergence point, resulting in colored fringes?",
    alpha: "Dispersion",
    beta: "Diffraction",
    charlie: "Interference",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Dispersion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 155,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the term for the distance between the center of a lens or mirror to its focal point?",
    alpha: "Radius of curvature",
    beta: "Focal length",
    charlie: "Aperture size",
    delta: "Lens thickness",
    correct_answer: "Focal length",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 156,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "In a concave mirror, where does the reflected light rays converge or appear to diverge from?",
    alpha: "Focal point",
    beta: "Vertex",
    charlie: "Center of curvature",
    delta: "Principal axis",
    correct_answer: "Focal point",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 157,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What type of lens is thinner at the center than at the edges and causes parallel light rays to diverge?",
    alpha: "Concave lens",
    beta: "Convex lens",
    charlie: "Diverging lens",
    delta: "Plano-concave lens",
    correct_answer: "Concave lens",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 158,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where light waves spread out as they pass through a narrow opening or around an obstacle?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Diffraction",
    charlie: "Reflection",
    delta: "Interference",
    correct_answer: "Diffraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 159,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the term for the maximum angle at which total internal reflection can occur in a medium with a lower index of refraction?",
    alpha: "Critical angle",
    beta: "Optical angle",
    charlie: "Refraction angle",
    delta: "Reflective angle",
    correct_answer: "Critical angle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 160,
    quiz_id: 16,
    question: "What is the term for a lens that is thicker in the center than at the edges and converges parallel light rays?",
    alpha: "Concave lens",
    beta: "Convex lens",
    charlie: "Diverging lens",
    delta: "Plano-convex lens",
    correct_answer: "Convex lens",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 161,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where two or more waves combine to form a new wave with greater or lower amplitude?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 162,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the term for the bending of waves around obstacles or the spreading of waves as they pass through openings?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Diffraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 163,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "In the context of wave optics, what does Huygen's principle state?",
    alpha: "Each point on a wavefront becomes a source of secondary waves",
    beta: "Waves always travel in straight lines",
    charlie: "The speed of light is constant in a vacuum",
    delta: "The angle of reflection equals the angle of incidence",
    correct_answer: "Each point on a wavefront becomes a source of secondary waves",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 164,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where light waves vibrate in a preferred direction after passing through certain materials?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 165,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where a wave encounters a change in medium and changes its speed and direction?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 166,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the interference pattern produced by the overlapping of two coherent light sources?",
    alpha: "Diffraction pattern",
    beta: "Polarization pattern",
    charlie: "Newton's rings",
    delta: "Young's fringes",
    correct_answer: "Young's fringes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 167,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the term for the bending of light waves as they pass through a medium with different refractive indices?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 168,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where the speed of light changes as it passes from one medium to another?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 169,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the term for the spreading of light into its component colors due to the different refractive indices of each color?",
    alpha: "Dispersion",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Dispersion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 170,
    quiz_id: 17,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where light waves reinforce or cancel each other out, producing alternating bright and dark bands?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 171,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where two or more waves combine to form a new wave with greater or lower amplitude?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 172,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the term for the bending of waves around obstacles or the spreading of waves as they pass through openings?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Diffraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 173,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What type of interference occurs when two waves are perfectly in phase and reinforce each other?",
    alpha: "Constructive interference",
    beta: "Destructive interference",
    charlie: "Coherent interference",
    delta: "Incoherent interference",
    correct_answer: "Constructive interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 174,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the term for the maximum and minimum intensities observed in an interference pattern?",
    alpha: "Antinodes and nodes",
    beta: "Crests and troughs",
    charlie: "Maxima and minima",
    delta: "Peaks and valleys",
    correct_answer: "Maxima and minima",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 175,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "In the context of wave optics, what does Huygen's principle state?",
    alpha: "Each point on a wavefront becomes a source of secondary waves",
    beta: "Waves always travel in straight lines",
    charlie: "The speed of light is constant in a vacuum",
    delta: "The angle of reflection equals the angle of incidence",
    correct_answer: "Each point on a wavefront becomes a source of secondary waves",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 176,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What type of interference occurs when two waves are perfectly out of phase and cancel each other?",
    alpha: "Constructive interference",
    beta: "Destructive interference",
    charlie: "Coherent interference",
    delta: "Incoherent interference",
    correct_answer: "Destructive interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 177,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the interference pattern produced by the overlapping of two coherent light sources?",
    alpha: "Diffraction pattern",
    beta: "Polarization pattern",
    charlie: "Newton's rings",
    delta: "Young's fringes",
    correct_answer: "Young's fringes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 178,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where light waves vibrate in a preferred direction after passing through certain materials?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 179,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the term for the bending of light waves as they pass through a medium with different refractive indices?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 180,
    quiz_id: 18,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where light waves reinforce or cancel each other out, producing alternating bright and dark bands?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 181,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where light waves vibrate in a preferred direction after passing through certain materials?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 182,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What type of waves can be polarized?",
    alpha: "Longitudinal waves",
    beta: "Transverse waves",
    charlie: "Electromagnetic waves",
    delta: "Sound waves",
    correct_answer: "Transverse waves",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 183,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What is the device that can be used to selectively absorb light waves vibrating in one direction and transmit light waves vibrating in other directions?",
    alpha: "Polaroid filter",
    beta: "Diffraction grating",
    charlie: "Fresnel lens",
    delta: "Concave mirror",
    correct_answer: "Polaroid filter",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 184,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "In which direction are the electric and magnetic fields oscillating in an unpolarized light wave?",
    alpha: "Parallel to each other",
    beta: "Perpendicular to each other",
    charlie: "In the direction of propagation",
    delta: "Circular motion",
    correct_answer: "Perpendicular to each other",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 185,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where light waves are restricted to vibrate in a single plane?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 186,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "Which of the following materials is commonly used to produce polarized light?",
    alpha: "Wood",
    beta: "Paper",
    charlie: "Glass",
    delta: "Polaroid",
    correct_answer: "Polaroid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 187,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where the orientation of polarized light is rotated as it passes through certain materials?",
    alpha: "Diffraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Dispersion",
    delta: "Optical rotation",
    correct_answer: "Optical rotation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 188,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What type of polarized light is produced when unpolarized light reflects off a non-metallic surface at a specific angle?",
    alpha: "Plane-polarized light",
    beta: "Circularly polarized light",
    charlie: "Diffuse-polarized light",
    delta: "Birefringent light",
    correct_answer: "Plane-polarized light",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 189,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "Which property of light waves is responsible for the phenomenon of polarized sunglasses reducing glare?",
    alpha: "Refraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Diffraction",
    delta: "Polarization",
    correct_answer: "Polarization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 190,
    quiz_id: 19,
    question: "What is the term for the separation of unpolarized light into two beams that are vibrating perpendicular to each other?",
    alpha: "Diffraction",
    beta: "Interference",
    charlie: "Refraction",
    delta: "Double refraction",
    correct_answer: "Double refraction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 191,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "What type of lens is typically used in a magnifying glass?",
    alpha: "Convex lens",
    beta: "Concave lens",
    charlie: "Plano-concave lens",
    delta: "Plano-convex lens",
    correct_answer: "Convex lens",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 192,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "In a telescope, what is the purpose of the eyepiece lens?",
    alpha: "To collect and focus light",
    beta: "To magnify the image",
    charlie: "To gather more light",
    delta: "To reduce chromatic aberration",
    correct_answer: "To magnify the image",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 193,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "What is the instrument that uses multiple lenses to produce a highly magnified and detailed image of small objects?",
    alpha: "Telescope",
    beta: "Microscope",
    charlie: "Binoculars",
    delta: "Spectrometer",
    correct_answer: "Microscope",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 194,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "Which optical instrument uses a combination of lenses and mirrors to view objects at a distance?",
    alpha: "Telescope",
    beta: "Microscope",
    charlie: "Binoculars",
    delta: "Spectrometer",
    correct_answer: "Telescope",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 195,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "What is the purpose of the objective lens in a telescope?",
    alpha: "To collect and focus light",
    beta: "To magnify the image",
    charlie: "To gather more light",
    delta: "To reduce chromatic aberration",
    correct_answer: "To collect and focus light",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 196,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "Which optical instrument is designed for viewing distant objects with both eyes?",
    alpha: "Telescope",
    beta: "Microscope",
    charlie: "Binoculars",
    delta: "Spectrometer",
    correct_answer: "Binoculars",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 197,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "What is the function of a spectrometer?",
    alpha: "To magnify the image",
    beta: "To analyze the spectrum of light",
    charlie: "To view microscopic objects",
    delta: "To observe distant objects",
    correct_answer: "To analyze the spectrum of light",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 198,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "In a camera, what is the purpose of the diaphragm or aperture?",
    alpha: "To collect and focus light",
    beta: "To magnify the image",
    charlie: "To control the amount of light entering",
    delta: "To reduce chromatic aberration",
    correct_answer: "To control the amount of light entering",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 199,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "What optical instrument is used to disperse light into its component colors?",
    alpha: "Telescope",
    beta: "Microscope",
    charlie: "Binoculars",
    delta: "Spectrometer",
    correct_answer: "Spectrometer",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 200,
    quiz_id: 20,
    question: "In a microscope, what is the purpose of the condenser lens?",
    alpha: "To collect and focus light",
    beta: "To magnify the image",
    charlie: "To gather more light",
    delta: "To reduce chromatic aberration",
    correct_answer: "To collect and focus light",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 201,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What is the concept that describes the dual nature of particles, exhibiting both wave-like and particle-like properties?",
    alpha: "Quantum theory",
    beta: "Wave-particle duality",
    charlie: "Relativity",
    delta: "Electromagnetism",
    correct_answer: "Wave-particle duality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 202,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "Who proposed the wave-particle duality theory for electrons?",
    alpha: "Isaac Newton",
    beta: "Albert Einstein",
    charlie: "Louis de Broglie",
    delta: "Max Planck",
    correct_answer: "Louis de Broglie",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 203,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "In the double-slit experiment, what pattern is observed when particles exhibit wave-like behavior?",
    alpha: "Single slit pattern",
    beta: "Interference pattern",
    charlie: "Diffraction pattern",
    delta: "Particle pattern",
    correct_answer: "Interference pattern",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 204,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "Which equation is used to express the wave-particle duality of a particle with momentum?",
    alpha: "Newton's Second Law",
    beta: "Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle",
    charlie: "Schrödinger Equation",
    delta: "de Broglie wavelength equation",
    correct_answer: "de Broglie wavelength equation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 205,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What is the phenomenon where electrons exhibit wave-like interference patterns when passing through a double slit?",
    alpha: "Photoelectric effect",
    beta: "Compton scattering",
    charlie: "Davisson-Germer effect",
    delta: "Quantum tunneling",
    correct_answer: "Davisson-Germer effect",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 206,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What is the term for the smallest discrete amount of any physical property?",
    alpha: "Quanta",
    beta: "Photons",
    charlie: "Quantum",
    delta: "Particles",
    correct_answer: "Quanta",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 207,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "Which experiment demonstrated that light can exhibit both particle and wave characteristics?",
    alpha: "Double-slit experiment",
    beta: "Photoelectric effect",
    charlie: "Davisson-Germer experiment",
    delta: "Compton scattering",
    correct_answer: "Double-slit experiment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 208,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What is the principle that states it is impossible to simultaneously know the exact position and momentum of a particle?",
    alpha: "Principle of Superposition",
    beta: "Pauli Exclusion Principle",
    charlie: "Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle",
    delta: "Bohr's Correspondence Principle",
    correct_answer: "Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 209,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What concept suggests that particles exist in all possible states until observed or measured?",
    alpha: "Principle of Superposition",
    beta: "Wave-Particle Duality",
    charlie: "Quantum Entanglement",
    delta: "Wavefunction collapse",
    correct_answer: "Principle of Superposition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 210,
    quiz_id: 21,
    question: "What is the mathematical representation of the quantum state of a physical system in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Wavefunction",
    beta: "Quantum number",
    charlie: "Spinor",
    delta: "Entanglement",
    correct_answer: "Wavefunction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 211,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "Who formulated the Schrödinger Equation in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Max Planck",
    beta: "Louis de Broglie",
    charlie: "Werner Heisenberg",
    delta: "Erwin Schrödinger",
    correct_answer: "Erwin Schrödinger",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 212,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What is the Schrödinger Equation used to describe?",
    alpha: "Wave-particle duality",
    beta: "Quantum entanglement",
    charlie: "Particle motion in a potential field",
    delta: "Relativity",
    correct_answer: "Particle motion in a potential field",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 213,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "In the Schrödinger Equation, what does the wavefunction represent?",
    alpha: "Particle's position",
    beta: "Particle's momentum",
    charlie: "Probability amplitude",
    delta: "Energy of the particle",
    correct_answer: "Probability amplitude",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 214,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What type of system is described by the time-independent Schrödinger Equation?",
    alpha: "Stable systems",
    beta: "Systems in motion",
    charlie: "Systems with changing energy",
    delta: "Dynamic systems",
    correct_answer: "Stable systems",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 215,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What is the fundamental quantity that the Schrödinger Equation provides information about in a quantum system?",
    alpha: "Wavefunction",
    beta: "Energy",
    charlie: "Momentum",
    delta: "Spin",
    correct_answer: "Energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 216,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "In the time-dependent Schrödinger Equation, what role does the Hamiltonian operator play?",
    alpha: "Determining position",
    beta: "Determining momentum",
    charlie: "Determining energy",
    delta: "Determining spin",
    correct_answer: "Determining energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 217,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What is the general form of the one-dimensional time-dependent Schrödinger Equation?",
    alpha: "iħ ∂Ψ/∂t = HΨ",
    beta: "iħ ∂Ψ/∂x = HΨ",
    charlie: "iħ ∂Ψ/∂p = HΨ",
    delta: "iħ ∂Ψ/∂E = HΨ",
    correct_answer: "iħ ∂Ψ/∂t = HΨ",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 218,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What does the term 'iħ' represent in the Schrödinger Equation?",
    alpha: "Plank's constant",
    beta: "Imaginary unit",
    charlie: "Reduced Planck's constant",
    delta: "Planck's constant divided by 2π",
    correct_answer: "Reduced Planck's constant",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 219,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "Which of the following statements about the Schrödinger Equation is true?",
    alpha: "It describes the motion of classical particles",
    beta: "It provides exact values for particle properties",
    charlie: "It is only applicable to macroscopic objects",
    delta: "It involves probabilistic predictions for particle behavior",
    correct_answer: "It involves probabilistic predictions for particle behavior",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 220,
    quiz_id: 22,
    question: "What is the primary limitation of the Schrödinger Equation in solving for exact particle properties?",
    alpha: "It only applies to one-dimensional systems",
    beta: "It neglects the role of probability",
    charlie: "It cannot be solved analytically for many-body systems",
    delta: "It doesn't account for wave-particle duality",
    correct_answer: "It cannot be solved analytically for many-body systems",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 221,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the fundamental quantity that describes the state of a quantum system in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Position",
    beta: "Momentum",
    charlie: "Wavefunction",
    delta: "Energy",
    correct_answer: "Wavefunction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 222,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what is the probability density function associated with a particle's position called?",
    alpha: "Probability wave",
    beta: "Wavefunction",
    charlie: "Quantum state",
    delta: "Probability amplitude",
    correct_answer: "Probability density function",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 223,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the term for a complete set of commuting observables in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Quantum state",
    beta: "Eigenstate",
    charlie: "Basis set",
    delta: "Observable set",
    correct_answer: "Basis set",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 224,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what does the eigenstate of an operator represent?",
    alpha: "A probability distribution",
    beta: "A definite value of the observable",
    charlie: "A superposition of states",
    delta: "A changing state",
    correct_answer: "A definite value of the observable",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 225,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the term for the set of possible outcomes of a measurement in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Probability distribution",
    beta: "Quantum state",
    charlie: "Spectrum",
    delta: "Eigenvalues",
    correct_answer: "Eigenvalues",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 226,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the mathematical operator that corresponds to the observable associated with energy in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Position operator",
    beta: "Momentum operator",
    charlie: "Hamiltonian operator",
    delta: "Angular momentum operator",
    correct_answer: "Hamiltonian operator",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 227,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what does the expectation value of an observable represent?",
    alpha: "The most probable value",
    beta: "The average value",
    charlie: "The maximum value",
    delta: "The minimum value",
    correct_answer: "The average value",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 228,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the term for the process of obtaining eigenvalues and eigenstates of a quantum system?",
    alpha: "Observation",
    beta: "Measurement",
    charlie: "Normalization",
    delta: "Diagonalization",
    correct_answer: "Diagonalization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 229,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle in quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Exact simultaneous measurement of position and momentum is impossible",
    beta: "Particles exist in all possible states until observed",
    charlie: "Particles can only exist in quantized energy states",
    delta: "Probability of finding a particle is proportional to its wavefunction",
    correct_answer: "Exact simultaneous measurement of position and momentum is impossible",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 230,
    quiz_id: 23,
    question: "What is the term for the set of quantum states that spans the entire Hilbert space for a particular system?",
    alpha: "Basis set",
    beta: "Eigenstate",
    charlie: "Quantum state",
    delta: "Superposition",
    correct_answer: "Basis set",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 231,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "What is the fundamental assumption that states a quantum system is fully described by a wavefunction?",
    alpha: "Superposition Principle",
    beta: "Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle",
    charlie: "Wave-Particle Duality",
    delta: "Wavefunction Postulate",
    correct_answer: "Wavefunction Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 232,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "Which postulate of quantum mechanics states that the result of a measurement is an eigenvalue of the corresponding operator?",
    alpha: "Superposition Principle",
    beta: "Probability Postulate",
    charlie: "Eigenstate Postulate",
    delta: "Observation Postulate",
    correct_answer: "Observation Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 233,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "What principle in quantum mechanics suggests that two non-commuting observables cannot both have precise values simultaneously?",
    alpha: "Superposition Principle",
    beta: "Probability Postulate",
    charlie: "Commutation Principle",
    delta: "Uncertainty Principle",
    correct_answer: "Uncertainty Principle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 234,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what postulate asserts that the time evolution of a quantum state is governed by the Schrödinger Equation?",
    alpha: "Time Evolution Postulate",
    beta: "Wavefunction Postulate",
    charlie: "Observation Postulate",
    delta: "Probability Postulate",
    correct_answer: "Time Evolution Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 235,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "Which postulate in quantum mechanics introduces the concept of probability amplitudes associated with different outcomes of a measurement?",
    alpha: "Probability Postulate",
    beta: "Observation Postulate",
    charlie: "Superposition Principle",
    delta: "Uncertainty Principle",
    correct_answer: "Probability Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 236,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "What does the Superposition Principle state in the context of quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Particles exist in all possible states until observed",
    beta: "Two observables cannot have precise values simultaneously",
    charlie: "The wavefunction evolves continuously in time",
    delta: "The state of a system can be a linear combination of other states",
    correct_answer: "The state of a system can be a linear combination of other states",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 237,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "Which postulate of quantum mechanics states that the probability of finding a particle in a certain state is given by the squared magnitude of its probability amplitude?",
    alpha: "Wavefunction Postulate",
    beta: "Probability Postulate",
    charlie: "Observation Postulate",
    delta: "Superposition Principle",
    correct_answer: "Probability Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 238,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "What is the principle that asserts the non-local correlation between entangled particles, as described by quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Superposition Principle",
    beta: "Bell's Theorem",
    charlie: "Wavefunction Postulate",
    delta: "Entanglement Principle",
    correct_answer: "Bell's Theorem",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 239,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what is the principle that states that identical particles with the same spin must be indistinguishable?",
    alpha: "Exclusion Principle",
    beta: "Fermi-Dirac Statistics",
    charlie: "Bose-Einstein Statistics",
    delta: "Pauli Exclusion Principle",
    correct_answer: "Pauli Exclusion Principle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 240,
    quiz_id: 24,
    question: "What postulate of quantum mechanics is associated with the concept that measurements can disturb the system being measured?",
    alpha: "Superposition Principle",
    beta: "Disturbance Postulate",
    charlie: "Commutation Principle",
    delta: "Observer Effect Postulate",
    correct_answer: "Observer Effect Postulate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 241,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "What is the application of modern physics that involves using semiconductor devices to control and process electrical signals?",
    alpha: "Quantum computing",
    beta: "Nuclear power generation",
    charlie: "Solid-state electronics",
    delta: "Laser technology",
    correct_answer: "Solid-state electronics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 242,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "Which medical imaging technique relies on the principles of nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) and is widely used for visualizing internal structures of the body?",
    alpha: "X-ray imaging",
    beta: "Computed tomography (CT)",
    charlie: "Positron emission tomography (PET)",
    delta: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    correct_answer: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 243,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "What technology, based on the photoelectric effect, is commonly used in bar code scanners, document scanners, and digital cameras?",
    alpha: "Laser technology",
    beta: "X-ray imaging",
    charlie: "Semiconductor devices",
    delta: "Photovoltaic cells",
    correct_answer: "Photovoltaic cells",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 244,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "In which application does the phenomenon of superconductivity play a crucial role, allowing the creation of powerful magnets for medical imaging and particle accelerators?",
    alpha: "Electric power transmission",
    beta: "Magnetic levitation trains",
    charlie: "Particle accelerators",
    delta: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    correct_answer: "Particle accelerators",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 245,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "What technology, based on the principles of quantum mechanics, is employed in the development of highly secure communication systems?",
    alpha: "Quantum computing",
    beta: "Fiber optics",
    charlie: "Quantum cryptography",
    delta: "Nuclear power generation",
    correct_answer: "Quantum cryptography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 246,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "Which application of modern physics involves the use of lasers to precisely cut or reshape materials in manufacturing processes?",
    alpha: "Magnetic resonance imaging (MRI)",
    beta: "Laser surgery",
    charlie: "Laser machining",
    delta: "Quantum computing",
    correct_answer: "Laser machining",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 247,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "In which area of modern physics is the concept of wave-particle duality particularly important?",
    alpha: "Quantum computing",
    beta: "Fiber optics",
    charlie: "Solid-state physics",
    delta: "Quantum mechanics",
    correct_answer: "Quantum mechanics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 248,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "What is the application of modern physics that involves the study of subatomic particles and their interactions in particle accelerators?",
    alpha: "Quantum computing",
    beta: "Nuclear power generation",
    charlie: "High-energy physics",
    delta: "Fiber optics",
    correct_answer: "High-energy physics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 249,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "Which technology, based on the principles of quantum mechanics, holds the potential to perform complex calculations much faster than classical computers?",
    alpha: "Fiber optics",
    beta: "Quantum computing",
    charlie: "Laser technology",
    delta: "Solid-state electronics",
    correct_answer: "Quantum computing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 250,
    quiz_id: 25,
    question: "What is the application of modern physics that involves the study of the behavior of matter and energy at extremely small scales, leading to advancements in nanotechnology?",
    alpha: "Quantum mechanics",
    beta: "Solid-state physics",
    charlie: "Nuclear physics",
    delta: "Condensed matter physics",
    correct_answer: "Condensed matter physics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 251,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "How many elements are there in the modern periodic table?",
    alpha: "92",
    beta: "104",
    charlie: "118",
    delta: "140",
    correct_answer: "118",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 252,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "What is the lightest element in the periodic table?",
    alpha: "Hydrogen",
    beta: "Helium",
    charlie: "Lithium",
    delta: "Beryllium",
    correct_answer: "Hydrogen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 253,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "Which element has the chemical symbol 'O'?",
    alpha: "Oxygen",
    beta: "Osmium",
    charlie: "Oganesson",
    delta: "Osmium",
    correct_answer: "Oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 254,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "What is the atomic number of carbon?",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "12",
    charlie: "6",
    delta: "14",
    correct_answer: "6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 255,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "Which group of elements is known as the noble gases?",
    alpha: "Group 1",
    beta: "Group 2",
    charlie: "Group 17",
    delta: "Group 18",
    correct_answer: "Group 18",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 256,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "Which element is essential for life and forms the basis of organic chemistry?",
    alpha: "Carbon",
    beta: "Oxygen",
    charlie: "Nitrogen",
    delta: "Hydrogen",
    correct_answer: "Carbon",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 257,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
    alpha: "Au",
    beta: "Ag",
    charlie: "Fe",
    delta: "Cu",
    correct_answer: "Au",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 258,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "Which element is commonly used in nuclear power plants as a fuel?",
    alpha: "Uranium",
    beta: "Plutonium",
    charlie: "Thorium",
    delta: "Radium",
    correct_answer: "Uranium",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 259,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "What is the lightest alkali metal in Group 1 of the periodic table?",
    alpha: "Lithium",
    beta: "Sodium",
    charlie: "Potassium",
    delta: "Rubidium",
    correct_answer: "Lithium",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 260,
    quiz_id: 26,
    question: "Which element is the most abundant in the Earth's crust?",
    alpha: "Silicon",
    beta: "Aluminum",
    charlie: "Oxygen",
    delta: "Iron",
    correct_answer: "Oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 261,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "What type of chemical bond is formed when electrons are transferred from one atom to another?",
    alpha: "Covalent bond",
    beta: "Ionic bond",
    charlie: "Metallic bond",
    delta: "Hydrogen bond",
    correct_answer: "Ionic bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 262,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "In a covalent bond, how are electrons shared between atoms?",
    alpha: "Unequally",
    beta: "Not shared",
    charlie: "Equally",
    delta: "Randomly",
    correct_answer: "Equally",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 263,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "Which type of bond is characterized by the sharing of electrons between atoms?",
    alpha: "Ionic bond",
    beta: "Covalent bond",
    charlie: "Metallic bond",
    delta: "Van der Waals bond",
    correct_answer: "Covalent bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 264,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "What is the term for a bond formed between two atoms of the same element, where the electrons are equally shared?",
    alpha: "Ionic bond",
    beta: "Polar bond",
    charlie: "Nonpolar bond",
    delta: "Covalent bond",
    correct_answer: "Nonpolar bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 265,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "Which element is commonly involved in hydrogen bonding?",
    alpha: "Oxygen",
    beta: "Nitrogen",
    charlie: "Hydrogen",
    delta: "Fluorine",
    correct_answer: "Oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 266,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "In metallic bonding, what is responsible for holding the metal atoms together in a lattice structure?",
    alpha: "Covalent bonds",
    beta: "Ionic bonds",
    charlie: "Metallic bonds",
    delta: "Van der Waals forces",
    correct_answer: "Metallic bonds",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 267,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "Which type of bond is relatively weaker and occurs between molecules due to temporary shifts in electron density?",
    alpha: "Ionic bond",
    beta: "Covalent bond",
    charlie: "Metallic bond",
    delta: "Van der Waals bond",
    correct_answer: "Van der Waals bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 268,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "What is the term for a bond formed between a metal and a nonmetal, resulting in a transfer of electrons?",
    alpha: "Covalent bond",
    beta: "Ionic bond",
    charlie: "Metallic bond",
    delta: "Hydrogen bond",
    correct_answer: "Ionic bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 269,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "What type of bond is characterized by an unequal sharing of electrons, leading to partial charges on the atoms?",
    alpha: "Ionic bond",
    beta: "Covalent bond",
    charlie: "Metallic bond",
    delta: "Polar bond",
    correct_answer: "Polar bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 270,
    quiz_id: 27,
    question: "What is the term for the attraction between the positively charged end of one polar molecule and the negatively charged end of another polar molecule?",
    alpha: "Ionic attraction",
    beta: "Van der Waals force",
    charlie: "Dipole-dipole interaction",
    delta: "Metallic bonding",
    correct_answer: "Dipole-dipole interaction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 271,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the central metal atom or ion in a coordination compound called?",
    alpha: "Ligand",
    beta: "Complex ion",
    charlie: "Coordination sphere",
    delta: "Coordination center",
    correct_answer: "Coordination center",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 272,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the term for a molecule or ion that donates a pair of electrons to a metal ion in a coordination compound?",
    alpha: "Central atom",
    beta: "Coordination sphere",
    charlie: "Ligand",
    delta: "Complex ion",
    correct_answer: "Ligand",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 273,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "In the formula [Co(NH3)6]Cl3, what is the coordination number of cobalt?",
    alpha: "4",
    beta: "5",
    charlie: "6",
    delta: "8",
    correct_answer: "6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 274,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the term for a complex ion that is formed when a ligand donates a lone pair of electrons to a metal ion?",
    alpha: "Coordination sphere",
    beta: "Octahedral complex",
    charlie: "Chelate complex",
    delta: "Coordination covalent complex",
    correct_answer: "Coordination covalent complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 275,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the geometry of a complex with a coordination number of 4 and no lone pairs on the central metal ion?",
    alpha: "Tetrahedral",
    beta: "Square planar",
    charlie: "Trigonal bipyramidal",
    delta: "Octahedral",
    correct_answer: "Tetrahedral",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 276,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "Which type of isomerism occurs when the ligands in a coordination compound can be arranged in different ways around the central metal ion?",
    alpha: "Ionization isomerism",
    beta: "Coordination isomerism",
    charlie: "Stereoisomerism",
    delta: "Linkage isomerism",
    correct_answer: "Stereoisomerism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 277,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the term for a ligand that can form multiple coordinate bonds with a metal ion in a coordination compound?",
    alpha: "Monodentate ligand",
    beta: "Bidentate ligand",
    charlie: "Polydentate ligand",
    delta: "Heterodentate ligand",
    correct_answer: "Polydentate ligand",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 278,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "In the complex [Pt(NH3)2Cl2], what is the oxidation state of platinum?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "+2",
    charlie: "+4",
    delta: "+6",
    correct_answer: "+2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 279,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "What is the term for a type of isomerism in which the linkage of ligands to the central metal ion is different?",
    alpha: "Ionization isomerism",
    beta: "Coordination isomerism",
    charlie: "Stereoisomerism",
    delta: "Linkage isomerism",
    correct_answer: "Linkage isomerism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 280,
    quiz_id: 28,
    question: "In the complex [Fe(CN)6]4-, what is the charge on the complex ion?",
    alpha: "-1",
    beta: "-2",
    charlie: "-3",
    delta: "-4",
    correct_answer: "-4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 281,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "Which group of elements in the periodic table is known as the transition metals?",
    alpha: "Group 1",
    beta: "Group 2",
    charlie: "Groups 3-12",
    delta: "Group 17",
    correct_answer: "Groups 3-12",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 282,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "What is the common oxidation state of many transition metals in their compounds?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "+1",
    charlie: "+2",
    delta: "+3",
    correct_answer: "+2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 283,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "Which transition metal is known for forming colorful compounds and is used in the production of pigments?",
    alpha: "Iron (Fe)",
    beta: "Copper (Cu)",
    charlie: "Chromium (Cr)",
    delta: "Cobalt (Co)",
    correct_answer: "Chromium (Cr)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 284,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "What is the term for the ability of transition metals to form stable complexes with ligands?",
    alpha: "Complex ion formation",
    beta: "Coordination ability",
    charlie: "Ligand bonding",
    delta: "Chelation",
    correct_answer: "Chelation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 285,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "Which transition metal is commonly used in the production of stainless steel?",
    alpha: "Nickel (Ni)",
    beta: "Copper (Cu)",
    charlie: "Titanium (Ti)",
    delta: "Chromium (Cr)",
    correct_answer: "Chromium (Cr)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 286,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where a transition metal ion in a complex undergoes changes in oxidation state without breaking apart?",
    alpha: "Redox reaction",
    beta: "Oxidation-reduction",
    charlie: "Coordination isomerism",
    delta: "Redox cycling",
    correct_answer: "Redox cycling",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 287,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "Which transition metal is a key component in the hemoglobin molecule, responsible for oxygen transport in blood?",
    alpha: "Copper (Cu)",
    beta: "Iron (Fe)",
    charlie: "Zinc (Zn)",
    delta: "Manganese (Mn)",
    correct_answer: "Iron (Fe)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 288,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "What is the term for a compound containing a metal ion bonded to one or more ligands?",
    alpha: "Coordination compound",
    beta: "Transition compound",
    charlie: "Metallic compound",
    delta: "Ligand compound",
    correct_answer: "Coordination compound",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 289,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "Which transition metal is commonly used as a catalyst in the Haber process for the synthesis of ammonia?",
    alpha: "Ruthenium (Ru)",
    beta: "Platinum (Pt)",
    charlie: "Iron (Fe)",
    delta: "Molybdenum (Mo)",
    correct_answer: "Iron (Fe)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 290,
    quiz_id: 29,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where a transition metal ion forms a complex with a ligand by sharing an electron pair?",
    alpha: "Chelation",
    beta: "Dative bonding",
    charlie: "Ligand exchange",
    delta: "Metallic bonding",
    correct_answer: "Dative bonding",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 291,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "Which group of elements in the periodic table is commonly referred to as the main group elements?",
    alpha: "Group 1",
    beta: "Group 2",
    charlie: "Groups 3-12",
    delta: "Groups 13-18",
    correct_answer: "Groups 13-18",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 292,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "What is the general electron configuration of the main group elements?",
    alpha: "ns²np¹-⁶",
    beta: "ns²np⁶",
    charlie: "ns²np⁴",
    delta: "ns²np⁵",
    correct_answer: "ns²np¹-⁶",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 293,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "Which main group element is a noble gas and has the electron configuration 1s²2s²2p⁶?",
    alpha: "Helium (He)",
    beta: "Neon (Ne)",
    charlie: "Argon (Ar)",
    delta: "Krypton (Kr)",
    correct_answer: "Neon (Ne)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 294,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "In which group of the periodic table do the alkali metals belong?",
    alpha: "Group 1",
    beta: "Group 2",
    charlie: "Group 17",
    delta: "Group 18",
    correct_answer: "Group 1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 295,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "What is the term for the outermost electrons of an atom that are involved in chemical bonding?",
    alpha: "Core electrons",
    beta: "Valence electrons",
    charlie: "Inner electrons",
    delta: "Transition electrons",
    correct_answer: "Valence electrons",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 296,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "Which main group element is commonly found in group 17 and is known for its diatomic molecules?",
    alpha: "Fluorine (F)",
    beta: "Chlorine (Cl)",
    charlie: "Bromine (Br)",
    delta: "Iodine (I)",
    correct_answer: "Chlorine (Cl)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 297,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "Which main group element is essential for life and is a major component of organic compounds?",
    alpha: "Nitrogen (N)",
    beta: "Carbon (C)",
    charlie: "Oxygen (O)",
    delta: "Hydrogen (H)",
    correct_answer: "Carbon (C)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 298,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "In which group of the periodic table do the noble gases belong?",
    alpha: "Group 1",
    beta: "Group 2",
    charlie: "Group 17",
    delta: "Group 18",
    correct_answer: "Group 18",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 299,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "Which main group element is commonly used as a reducing agent and is a component of hydrochloric acid (HCl)?",
    alpha: "Sulfur (S)",
    beta: "Chlorine (Cl)",
    charlie: "Hydrogen (H)",
    delta: "Phosphorus (P)",
    correct_answer: "Hydrogen (H)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 300,
    quiz_id: 30,
    question: "What is the term for elements in the same column of the periodic table with similar chemical properties?",
    alpha: "Period",
    beta: "Family",
    charlie: "Group",
    delta: "Block",
    correct_answer: "Group",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 301,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "What is the general formula for an alkane, a type of hydrocarbon?",
    alpha: "CnH2n",
    beta: "CnH2n+2",
    charlie: "CnHn",
    delta: "CnHn-2",
    correct_answer: "CnH2n+2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 302,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "How many carbon atoms are there in the compound known as ethane?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 303,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "What is the term for a hydrocarbon with at least one carbon-carbon triple bond?",
    alpha: "Alkane",
    beta: "Alkene",
    charlie: "Alkyne",
    delta: "Aromatic",
    correct_answer: "Alkyne",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 304,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "Which type of hydrocarbon is characterized by a ring of carbon atoms with alternating single and double bonds?",
    alpha: "Alkane",
    beta: "Alkene",
    charlie: "Alkyne",
    delta: "Aromatic",
    correct_answer: "Aromatic",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 305,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "What is the simplest alkene with a double bond in its structure?",
    alpha: "Ethene",
    beta: "Propene",
    charlie: "Methene",
    delta: "Butene",
    correct_answer: "Ethene",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 306,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "Which type of isomerism occurs in hydrocarbons with the same molecular formula but different arrangements of atoms?",
    alpha: "Structural isomerism",
    beta: "Cis-trans isomerism",
    charlie: "Stereoisomerism",
    delta: "Geometric isomerism",
    correct_answer: "Structural isomerism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 307,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "What is the term for a hydrocarbon that contains only single bonds between carbon atoms?",
    alpha: "Alkane",
    beta: "Alkene",
    charlie: "Alkyne",
    delta: "Aromatic",
    correct_answer: "Alkane",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 308,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "Which hydrocarbon is known as a saturated hydrocarbon and has the general formula CnH2n+2?",
    alpha: "Alkane",
    beta: "Alkene",
    charlie: "Alkyne",
    delta: "Aromatic",
    correct_answer: "Alkane",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 309,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "In the compound but-2-ene, where is the double bond located?",
    alpha: "Between carbon atoms 1 and 2",
    beta: "Between carbon atoms 2 and 3",
    charlie: "Between carbon atoms 3 and 4",
    delta: "Between carbon atoms 1 and 4",
    correct_answer: "Between carbon atoms 2 and 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 310,
    quiz_id: 31,
    question: "What is the primary component of natural gas?",
    alpha: "Methane",
    beta: "Ethane",
    charlie: "Propane",
    delta: "Butane",
    correct_answer: "Methane",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 311,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "What functional group is present in alcohols?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Ester",
    correct_answer: "Hydroxyl",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 312,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "In which type of compound is the carbonyl group commonly found?",
    alpha: "Alcohol",
    beta: "Aldehyde",
    charlie: "Ester",
    delta: "Amide",
    correct_answer: "Aldehyde",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 313,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "What functional group is present in carboxylic acids?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Carboxyl",
    correct_answer: "Carboxyl",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 314,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "Which functional group is characteristic of amines?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Ester",
    correct_answer: "Amino",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 315,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "What type of compound contains the ester functional group?",
    alpha: "Alcohol",
    beta: "Aldehyde",
    charlie: "Ester",
    delta: "Amide",
    correct_answer: "Ester",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 316,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "In which functional group is a nitrogen atom bonded to two alkyl or aryl groups?",
    alpha: "Amide",
    beta: "Amino",
    charlie: "Carboxyl",
    delta: "Nitrile",
    correct_answer: "Amide",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 317,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "What is the characteristic functional group of aldehydes?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Aldehyde",
    correct_answer: "Aldehyde",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 318,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "Which functional group is present in ethers?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Ether",
    correct_answer: "Ether",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 319,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "What is the characteristic functional group of ketones?",
    alpha: "Carbonyl",
    beta: "Hydroxyl",
    charlie: "Amino",
    delta: "Ketone",
    correct_answer: "Ketone",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 320,
    quiz_id: 32,
    question: "In which type of compound is the nitrile functional group commonly found?",
    alpha: "Alcohol",
    beta: "Aldehyde",
    charlie: "Ester",
    delta: "Nitrile",
    correct_answer: "Nitrile",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 321,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for stereoisomers that are non-superimposable mirror images of each other?",
    alpha: "Enantiomers",
    beta: "Diastereomers",
    charlie: "Constitutional isomers",
    delta: "Cis-trans isomers",
    correct_answer: "Enantiomers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 322,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for the specific arrangement of atoms in a molecule that results from the free rotation of single bonds?",
    alpha: "Chirality",
    beta: "Conformation",
    charlie: "Isomerism",
    delta: "Stereochemistry",
    correct_answer: "Conformation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 323,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "In a Fischer projection, horizontal lines represent bonds that are...",
    alpha: "Wedge",
    beta: "Dashed",
    charlie: "In the plane of the paper",
    delta: "Out of the plane of the paper",
    correct_answer: "Out of the plane of the paper",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 324,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for stereoisomers that are not mirror images of each other?",
    alpha: "Enantiomers",
    beta: "Diastereomers",
    charlie: "Constitutional isomers",
    delta: "Cis-trans isomers",
    correct_answer: "Diastereomers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 325,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for a molecule that has a non-superimposable mirror image but is not chiral itself?",
    alpha: "Chiral",
    beta: "Achiral",
    charlie: "Diastereomeric",
    delta: "Enantiomeric",
    correct_answer: "Achiral",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 326,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of geometric isomerism?",
    alpha: "Enantiomers",
    beta: "Cis-trans isomers",
    charlie: "Conformational isomers",
    delta: "Structural isomers",
    correct_answer: "Cis-trans isomers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 327,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for the arrangement of substituents around a chiral center that cannot be superimposed on its mirror image?",
    alpha: "Chirality",
    beta: "Conformation",
    charlie: "Enantiomerism",
    delta: "Diastereomerism",
    correct_answer: "Chirality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 328,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "In a Newman projection, what type of angle is formed between the two groups being observed?",
    alpha: "Dihedral angle",
    beta: "Steric angle",
    charlie: "Bond angle",
    delta: "Torsional angle",
    correct_answer: "Dihedral angle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 329,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the term for stereoisomers that have the same connectivity of atoms but differ in the arrangement of atoms in space?",
    alpha: "Constitutional isomers",
    beta: "Diastereomers",
    charlie: "Enantiomers",
    delta: "Structural isomers",
    correct_answer: "Stereoisomers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 330,
    quiz_id: 33,
    question: "What is the relationship between cis and trans isomers?",
    alpha: "Enantiomers",
    beta: "Diastereomers",
    charlie: "Constitutional isomers",
    delta: "Geometric isomers",
    correct_answer: "Geometric isomers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 331,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "What type of reaction involves the addition of water across a double bond?",
    alpha: "Hydrogenation",
    beta: "Hydration",
    charlie: "Halogenation",
    delta: "Oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Hydration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 332,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "In which type of reaction does a nucleophile attack an electrophile, resulting in the formation of a bond?",
    alpha: "Substitution",
    beta: "Addition",
    charlie: "Elimination",
    delta: "Reduction",
    correct_answer: "Addition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 333,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "What is the term for a reaction in which a molecule loses electrons?",
    alpha: "Reduction",
    beta: "Oxidation",
    charlie: "Substitution",
    delta: "Elimination",
    correct_answer: "Oxidation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 334,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "In which type of reaction does one functional group replace another?",
    alpha: "Substitution",
    beta: "Addition",
    charlie: "Elimination",
    delta: "Rearrangement",
    correct_answer: "Substitution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 335,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "What type of reaction involves the removal of a leaving group and the formation of a double bond?",
    alpha: "Hydrogenation",
    beta: "Dehydration",
    charlie: "Halogenation",
    delta: "Oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Dehydration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 336,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "Which reaction type involves the exchange of substituents between two reactant molecules?",
    alpha: "Substitution",
    beta: "Addition",
    charlie: "Elimination",
    delta: "Cross-coupling",
    correct_answer: "Cross-coupling",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 337,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "What type of reaction involves the removal of a molecule, often water, from a larger molecule?",
    alpha: "Hydrolysis",
    beta: "Dehydration",
    charlie: "Halogenation",
    delta: "Oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Dehydration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 338,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "In which type of reaction does the breaking of a bond result in the formation of a double bond?",
    alpha: "Hydrogenation",
    beta: "Hydration",
    charlie: "Elimination",
    delta: "Oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Elimination",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 339,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "What is the term for a reaction in which a molecule gains electrons?",
    alpha: "Reduction",
    beta: "Oxidation",
    charlie: "Substitution",
    delta: "Elimination",
    correct_answer: "Reduction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 340,
    quiz_id: 34,
    question: "Which type of reaction involves the addition of hydrogen to a carbon-carbon double bond?",
    alpha: "Hydration",
    beta: "Hydrogenation",
    charlie: "Halogenation",
    delta: "Oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Hydrogenation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 341,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "What is the primary structural component of biological membranes?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Lipids",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 342,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "Which type of biomolecule includes enzymes, antibodies, and hormones?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Proteins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 343,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "What is the monomer unit of proteins?",
    alpha: "Amino acids",
    beta: "Monosaccharides",
    charlie: "Nucleotides",
    delta: "Fatty acids",
    correct_answer: "Amino acids",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 344,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "Which polysaccharide serves as an energy storage molecule in animals?",
    alpha: "Starch",
    beta: "Cellulose",
    charlie: "Glycogen",
    delta: "Chitin",
    correct_answer: "Glycogen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 345,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "What is the main function of DNA in living organisms?",
    alpha: "Energy storage",
    beta: "Catalysis",
    charlie: "Information storage",
    delta: "Structural support",
    correct_answer: "Information storage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 346,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "Which biomolecule is composed of a phosphate group, a sugar, and a nitrogenous base?",
    alpha: "Protein",
    beta: "Lipid",
    charlie: "Carbohydrate",
    delta: "Nucleic acid",
    correct_answer: "Nucleic acid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 347,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "What is the structural unit of a nucleic acid?",
    alpha: "Amino acid",
    beta: "Monosaccharide",
    charlie: "Nucleotide",
    delta: "Fatty acid",
    correct_answer: "Nucleotide",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 348,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "Which type of bond connects the nucleotides in a DNA molecule?",
    alpha: "Ionic bond",
    beta: "Covalent bond",
    charlie: "Hydrogen bond",
    delta: "Van der Waals bond",
    correct_answer: "Covalent bond",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 349,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "What is the term for a large molecule composed of repeating structural units?",
    alpha: "Polymer",
    beta: "Monomer",
    charlie: "Oligomer",
    delta: "Dimer",
    correct_answer: "Polymer",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 350,
    quiz_id: 35,
    question: "Which natural polymer provides structural support to the cell walls of plants?",
    alpha: "Starch",
    beta: "Cellulose",
    charlie: "Glycogen",
    delta: "Chitin",
    correct_answer: "Cellulose",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 351,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the First Law of Thermodynamics also known as?",
    alpha: "Law of Entropy",
    beta: "Law of Conservation of Energy",
    charlie: "Law of Specific Heat",
    delta: "Law of Thermometry",
    correct_answer: "Law of Conservation of Energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 352,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "In thermodynamics, what is the state variable that represents the internal energy of a system?",
    alpha: "Temperature",
    beta: "Pressure",
    charlie: "Volume",
    delta: "Entropy",
    correct_answer: "Internal energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 353,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the process called in which a gas changes directly into a solid without passing through the liquid state?",
    alpha: "Condensation",
    beta: "Sublimation",
    charlie: "Evaporation",
    delta: "Fusion",
    correct_answer: "Sublimation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 354,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the term for the measure of disorder or randomness in a system?",
    alpha: "Temperature",
    beta: "Pressure",
    charlie: "Volume",
    delta: "Entropy",
    correct_answer: "Entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 355,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "According to the Second Law of Thermodynamics, what is the direction of spontaneous processes in an isolated system?",
    alpha: "Toward higher energy",
    beta: "Toward lower energy",
    charlie: "Toward equilibrium",
    delta: "Toward randomness",
    correct_answer: "Toward higher entropy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 356,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the term for the maximum amount of work that can be obtained from a system at constant temperature and pressure?",
    alpha: "Enthalpy",
    beta: "Entropy",
    charlie: "Gibbs free energy",
    delta: "Internal energy",
    correct_answer: "Gibbs free energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 357,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the mathematical expression for the First Law of Thermodynamics?",
    alpha: "ΔU = q + w",
    beta: "ΔU = q - w",
    charlie: "ΔU = q × w",
    delta: "ΔU = q / w",
    correct_answer: "ΔU = q - w",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 358,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the term for a process in which there is no transfer of heat between a system and its surroundings?",
    alpha: "Adiabatic",
    beta: "Isothermal",
    charlie: "Isobaric",
    delta: "Isometric",
    correct_answer: "Adiabatic",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 359,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "What is the condition for a process to be spontaneous according to the Second Law of Thermodynamics?",
    alpha: "ΔH < 0",
    beta: "ΔS > 0",
    charlie: "ΔG < 0",
    delta: "ΔU < 0",
    correct_answer: "ΔG < 0",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 360,
    quiz_id: 36,
    question: "Which thermodynamic function represents the heat content of a system at constant pressure?",
    alpha: "Enthalpy",
    beta: "Entropy",
    charlie: "Internal energy",
    delta: "Gibbs free energy",
    correct_answer: "Enthalpy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 361,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the study of the rates of chemical processes and the factors that affect them called?",
    alpha: "Thermodynamics",
    beta: "Chemical Kinetics",
    charlie: "Quantum Mechanics",
    delta: "Electrochemistry",
    correct_answer: "Chemical Kinetics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 362,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the term for the minimum energy required for a reaction to occur?",
    alpha: "Activation energy",
    beta: "Reaction energy",
    charlie: "Catalytic energy",
    delta: "Thermal energy",
    correct_answer: "Activation energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 363,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "Which factor influences the rate of a chemical reaction by increasing the frequency of collisions between reactant molecules?",
    alpha: "Temperature",
    beta: "Pressure",
    charlie: "Concentration",
    delta: "Catalyst",
    correct_answer: "Concentration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 364,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the order of a reaction with respect to a particular reactant if doubling the concentration of that reactant doubles the rate?",
    alpha: "Zero order",
    beta: "First order",
    charlie: "Second order",
    delta: "Third order",
    correct_answer: "First order",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 365,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "Which type of reaction rate is expressed as the change in concentration per unit time?",
    alpha: "Instantaneous rate",
    beta: "Average rate",
    charlie: "Initial rate",
    delta: "Final rate",
    correct_answer: "Average rate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 366,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the term for a substance that increases the rate of a chemical reaction without being consumed in the process?",
    alpha: "Reactant",
    beta: "Product",
    charlie: "Catalyst",
    delta: "Inhibitor",
    correct_answer: "Catalyst",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 367,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the effect of increasing the temperature on the rate of most chemical reactions?",
    alpha: "Decreases rate",
    beta: "No effect",
    charlie: "Increases rate",
    delta: "Stops reaction",
    correct_answer: "Increases rate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 368,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "Which law states that the rate of a chemical reaction is directly proportional to the product of the concentrations of the reactants?",
    alpha: "Arrhenius Law",
    beta: "Rate Law",
    charlie: "Collision Theory",
    delta: "Le Chatelier's Principle",
    correct_answer: "Rate Law",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 369,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "What is the term for the time required for the concentration of a reactant to decrease to half of its initial value?",
    alpha: "Half-life",
    beta: "Lifetime",
    charlie: "Doubling time",
    delta: "Decay time",
    correct_answer: "Half-life",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 370,
    quiz_id: 37,
    question: "In a zero-order reaction, how does the rate depend on the concentration of the reactants?",
    alpha: "Directly proportional",
    beta: "Inversely proportional",
    charlie: "Exponential dependence",
    delta: "No dependence",
    correct_answer: "No dependence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 371,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "Who developed the mathematical formulation of quantum mechanics known as wave mechanics?",
    alpha: "Werner Heisenberg",
    beta: "Louis de Broglie",
    charlie: "Max Planck",
    delta: "Erwin Schrödinger",
    correct_answer: "Erwin Schrödinger",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 372,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What is the Heisenberg Uncertainty Principle?",
    alpha: "The position and momentum of a particle cannot be simultaneously measured with arbitrary precision.",
    beta: "The energy and time of a particle cannot be simultaneously measured with arbitrary precision.",
    charlie: "The angular momentum and velocity of a particle cannot be simultaneously measured with arbitrary precision.",
    delta: "The spin and charge of a particle cannot be simultaneously measured with arbitrary precision.",
    correct_answer: "The position and momentum of a particle cannot be simultaneously measured with arbitrary precision.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 373,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "Which of the following is a fundamental postulate of quantum mechanics?",
    alpha: "Wave-particle duality",
    beta: "Pauli Exclusion Principle",
    charlie: "Quantum entanglement",
    delta: "Quantum superposition",
    correct_answer: "Wave-particle duality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 374,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What does the wave function in quantum mechanics represent?",
    alpha: "Particle's position",
    beta: "Particle's momentum",
    charlie: "Particle's energy",
    delta: "Probability amplitude",
    correct_answer: "Probability amplitude",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 375,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What is the term for the discrete values of energy that electrons in an atom can possess?",
    alpha: "Energy levels",
    beta: "Quantum states",
    charlie: "Orbitals",
    delta: "Quantum numbers",
    correct_answer: "Energy levels",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 376,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "In quantum mechanics, what does the Schrödinger equation describe?",
    alpha: "Wave-particle duality",
    beta: "Wave function evolution",
    charlie: "Quantum tunneling",
    delta: "Quantum entanglement",
    correct_answer: "Wave function evolution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 377,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What is the Pauli Exclusion Principle?",
    alpha: "Two electrons in the same orbital must have opposite spins.",
    beta: "No two electrons in an atom can have the same set of four quantum numbers.",
    charlie: "Electrons tend to occupy the lowest energy orbitals first.",
    delta: "Electrons move in elliptical orbits around the nucleus.",
    correct_answer: "No two electrons in an atom can have the same set of four quantum numbers.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 378,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where two or more particles become connected and instantaneously affect each other's state, regardless of distance?",
    alpha: "Quantum entanglement",
    beta: "Quantum superposition",
    charlie: "Quantum tunneling",
    delta: "Quantum interference",
    correct_answer: "Quantum entanglement",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 379,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What are the quantum numbers that describe the shape of an orbital?",
    alpha: "Principal and azimuthal quantum numbers",
    beta: "Principal and magnetic quantum numbers",
    charlie: "Azimuthal and magnetic quantum numbers",
    delta: "Principal, azimuthal, and magnetic quantum numbers",
    correct_answer: "Azimuthal and magnetic quantum numbers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 380,
    quiz_id: 38,
    question: "What is the term for the region in space where an electron is most likely to be found?",
    alpha: "Orbit",
    beta: "Shell",
    charlie: "Nucleus",
    delta: "Orbital",
    correct_answer: "Orbital",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 381,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the electrochemical cell notation for a galvanic cell or voltaic cell?",
    alpha: "Anode | Cathode ||",
    beta: "Cathode | Anode ||",
    charlie: "Anode || Cathode |",
    delta: "Cathode || Anode |",
    correct_answer: "Anode | Cathode ||",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 382,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "In electrochemical cells, what is the function of the salt bridge?",
    alpha: "Allows the flow of electrons",
    beta: "Maintains electrical neutrality",
    charlie: "Increases reaction rate",
    delta: "Provides electrical insulation",
    correct_answer: "Maintains electrical neutrality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 383,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the standard electrode potential of the standard hydrogen electrode (SHE) under standard conditions?",
    alpha: "0 V",
    beta: "1 V",
    charlie: "-1 V",
    delta: "2 V",
    correct_answer: "0 V",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 384,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the oxidation half-reaction in the electrochemical cell where zinc is oxidized to zinc ions?",
    alpha: "Zn → Zn²⁺ + 2e⁻",
    beta: "Zn²⁺ + 2e⁻ → Zn",
    charlie: "2H₂O → O₂ + 4H⁺ + 4e⁻",
    delta: "2H⁺ + 2e⁻ → H₂",
    correct_answer: "Zn → Zn²⁺ + 2e⁻",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 385,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the term for the potential of an electrode under nonstandard conditions?",
    alpha: "Cell potential",
    beta: "Standard potential",
    charlie: "Half-cell potential",
    delta: "Electromotive force (EMF)",
    correct_answer: "Half-cell potential",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 386,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the Nernst equation used for in electrochemistry?",
    alpha: "Calculating standard electrode potentials",
    beta: "Determining cell potential",
    charlie: "Calculating reaction quotient",
    delta: "Adjusting for nonstandard conditions",
    correct_answer: "Adjusting for nonstandard conditions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 387,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "In which type of electrochemical cell does spontaneous chemical reactions generate an electric current?",
    alpha: "Galvanic cell",
    beta: "Electrolytic cell",
    charlie: "Concentration cell",
    delta: "Salt bridge cell",
    correct_answer: "Galvanic cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 388,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the term for the maximum electrical potential difference that can be obtained from a galvanic cell?",
    alpha: "Cell potential",
    beta: "Standard potential",
    charlie: "Half-cell potential",
    delta: "Electromotive force (EMF)",
    correct_answer: "Electromotive force (EMF)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 389,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "Which metal is commonly used as the standard for the reduction potential in electrochemical cells?",
    alpha: "Copper",
    beta: "Zinc",
    charlie: "Silver",
    delta: "Gold",
    correct_answer: "Hydrogen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 390,
    quiz_id: 39,
    question: "What is the term for the electrode at which oxidation occurs in an electrochemical cell?",
    alpha: "Cathode",
    beta: "Anode",
    charlie: "Salt bridge",
    delta: "Electrolyte",
    correct_answer: "Anode",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 391,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "What type of spectroscopy is commonly used to study the rotational and vibrational transitions of molecules?",
    alpha: "UV-Visible spectroscopy",
    beta: "Infrared spectroscopy",
    charlie: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    delta: "Raman spectroscopy",
    correct_answer: "Infrared spectroscopy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 392,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "What is the term for the range of electromagnetic radiation that molecular spectroscopy typically deals with?",
    alpha: "Visible range",
    beta: "Infrared range",
    charlie: "Microwave range",
    delta: "Radiofrequency range",
    correct_answer: "Infrared range",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 393,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "Which molecular motion is primarily probed by infrared spectroscopy?",
    alpha: "Rotational motion",
    beta: "Vibrational motion",
    charlie: "Electronic motion",
    delta: "Translational motion",
    correct_answer: "Vibrational motion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 394,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "What is the primary principle behind NMR spectroscopy?",
    alpha: "Absorption of ultraviolet radiation",
    beta: "Absorption of infrared radiation",
    charlie: "Absorption of microwaves by nuclei",
    delta: "Absorption of X-rays by electrons",
    correct_answer: "Absorption of microwaves by nuclei",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 395,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "Which type of spectroscopy is particularly useful for studying the electronic structure of molecules?",
    alpha: "UV-Visible spectroscopy",
    beta: "Infrared spectroscopy",
    charlie: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    delta: "X-ray spectroscopy",
    correct_answer: "UV-Visible spectroscopy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 396,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "In Raman spectroscopy, what is the principle behind the scattering of light?",
    alpha: "Electronic transitions",
    beta: "Vibrational transitions",
    charlie: "Rotational transitions",
    delta: "Nuclear transitions",
    correct_answer: "Vibrational transitions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 397,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where the frequency of absorbed or emitted light is shifted due to the motion of the atoms or molecules?",
    alpha: "Doppler effect",
    beta: "Stokes shift",
    charlie: "Redshift",
    delta: "Raman effect",
    correct_answer: "Raman effect",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 398,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "What is the primary information obtained from NMR spectroscopy?",
    alpha: "Vibrational transitions",
    beta: "Rotational transitions",
    charlie: "Electronic transitions",
    delta: "Chemical environments of nuclei",
    correct_answer: "Chemical environments of nuclei",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 399,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "Which spectroscopic technique is commonly used for determining the three-dimensional structure of molecules, particularly large biological molecules?",
    alpha: "Infrared spectroscopy",
    beta: "UV-Visible spectroscopy",
    charlie: "X-ray crystallography",
    delta: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    correct_answer: "X-ray crystallography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 400,
    quiz_id: 40,
    question: "In molecular spectroscopy, what is the term for the region of a spectrum where there is an increase in absorbance or intensity?",
    alpha: "Absorption peak",
    beta: "Absorption trough",
    charlie: "Absorption band",
    delta: "Absorption line",
    correct_answer: "Absorption band",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 401,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the building block or monomer unit of nucleic acids?",
    alpha: "Amino acids",
    beta: "Monosaccharides",
    charlie: "Nucleotides",
    delta: "Fatty acids",
    correct_answer: "Nucleotides",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 402,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the function of enzymes in biological systems?",
    alpha: "Structural support",
    beta: "Energy storage",
    charlie: "Catalysts for chemical reactions",
    delta: "Transport of molecules",
    correct_answer: "Catalysts for chemical reactions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 403,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "Which biomolecule serves as the primary source of energy in living cells?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Carbohydrates",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 404,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the structural unit of proteins?",
    alpha: "Amino acid",
    beta: "Monosaccharide",
    charlie: "Nucleotide",
    delta: "Fatty acid",
    correct_answer: "Amino acid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 405,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "Which biomolecule is involved in the storage and transmission of genetic information?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Nucleic acids",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 406,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the function of hemoglobin in the human body?",
    alpha: "Transport of oxygen",
    beta: "Digestion of food",
    charlie: "Synthesis of hormones",
    delta: "Storage of glucose",
    correct_answer: "Transport of oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 407,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "Which biomolecule is composed of a glycerol molecule and three fatty acid molecules?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Lipids",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 408,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the primary function of RNA (ribonucleic acid) in cells?",
    alpha: "Energy storage",
    beta: "Structural support",
    charlie: "Transport of molecules",
    delta: "Genetic information transfer",
    correct_answer: "Genetic information transfer",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 409,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "Which biomolecule is composed of long chains of amino acids linked by peptide bonds?",
    alpha: "Proteins",
    beta: "Lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Proteins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 410,
    quiz_id: 41,
    question: "What is the term for the process by which complex molecules are broken down into simpler ones, releasing energy?",
    alpha: "Anabolism",
    beta: "Catabolism",
    charlie: "Metabolism",
    delta: "Metabolism",
    correct_answer: "Catabolism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 411,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the primary function of enzymes in biological systems?",
    alpha: "Structural support",
    beta: "Energy storage",
    charlie: "Catalysts for chemical reactions",
    delta: "Transport of molecules",
    correct_answer: "Catalysts for chemical reactions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 412,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What are enzymes made of?",
    alpha: "Lipids",
    beta: "Carbohydrates",
    charlie: "Proteins",
    delta: "Nucleic acids",
    correct_answer: "Proteins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 413,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the term for the specific region of an enzyme where the substrate binds?",
    alpha: "Active site",
    beta: "Inhibitory site",
    charlie: "Allosteric site",
    delta: "Binding site",
    correct_answer: "Active site",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 414,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "How do enzymes speed up chemical reactions?",
    alpha: "Increasing temperature",
    beta: "Increasing pressure",
    charlie: "Lowering activation energy",
    delta: "Increasing substrate concentration",
    correct_answer: "Lowering activation energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 415,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the term for substances that can inhibit or reduce the activity of enzymes?",
    alpha: "Activators",
    beta: "Catalysts",
    charlie: "Inhibitors",
    delta: "Substrates",
    correct_answer: "Inhibitors",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 416,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the primary role of coenzymes in enzyme-catalyzed reactions?",
    alpha: "Provide structural support",
    beta: "Act as substrates",
    charlie: "Transport electrons or functional groups",
    delta: "Increase reaction temperature",
    correct_answer: "Transport electrons or functional groups",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 417,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the term for a group of enzymes that facilitate the breakdown of complex molecules into simpler ones?",
    alpha: "Synthases",
    beta: "Isomerases",
    charlie: "Lyases",
    delta: "Hydrolases",
    correct_answer: "Hydrolases",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 418,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "In cellular respiration, what is the enzyme responsible for catalyzing the conversion of glucose to pyruvate?",
    alpha: "Amylase",
    beta: "Hexokinase",
    charlie: "Pyruvate kinase",
    delta: "Phosphofructokinase",
    correct_answer: "Hexokinase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 419,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "What is the term for the process by which glucose is converted into lactic acid or ethanol in the absence of oxygen?",
    alpha: "Glycolysis",
    beta: "Citric acid cycle",
    charlie: "Fermentation",
    delta: "Oxidative phosphorylation",
    correct_answer: "Fermentation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 420,
    quiz_id: 42,
    question: "In photosynthesis, what enzyme is responsible for the fixation of carbon dioxide into organic molecules?",
    alpha: "Rubisco",
    beta: "ATP synthase",
    charlie: "Cytochrome c oxidase",
    delta: "RNA polymerase",
    correct_answer: "Rubisco",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 421,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What are the two main types of nucleic acids found in living organisms?",
    alpha: "DNA and RNA",
    beta: "Proteins and lipids",
    charlie: "Carbohydrates and sugars",
    delta: "Enzymes and coenzymes",
    correct_answer: "DNA and RNA",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 422,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the full name of DNA?",
    alpha: "Deoxyribonucleic acid",
    beta: "Ribonucleic acid",
    charlie: "Nucleotide acid",
    delta: "Polyribonucleotide acid",
    correct_answer: "Deoxyribonucleic acid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 423,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the primary function of DNA in cells?",
    alpha: "Energy storage",
    beta: "Structural support",
    charlie: "Genetic information storage",
    delta: "Enzyme synthesis",
    correct_answer: "Genetic information storage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 424,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "Which nitrogenous base is NOT present in RNA?",
    alpha: "Adenine",
    beta: "Thymine",
    charlie: "Cytosine",
    delta: "Uracil",
    correct_answer: "Thymine",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 425,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the complementary base pair for adenine in DNA?",
    alpha: "Thymine",
    beta: "Cytosine",
    charlie: "Guanine",
    delta: "Uracil",
    correct_answer: "Thymine",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 426,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "Which enzyme is responsible for synthesizing RNA from a DNA template during transcription?",
    alpha: "DNA polymerase",
    beta: "RNA polymerase",
    charlie: "Helicase",
    delta: "Ligase",
    correct_answer: "RNA polymerase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 427,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the term for the three-nucleotide sequence on mRNA that codes for a specific amino acid?",
    alpha: "Intron",
    beta: "Codon",
    charlie: "Exon",
    delta: "Anticodon",
    correct_answer: "Codon",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 428,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to the ribosome during protein synthesis?",
    alpha: "mRNA",
    beta: "tRNA",
    charlie: "rRNA",
    delta: "snRNA",
    correct_answer: "tRNA",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 429,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the term for the process by which the information in DNA is used to synthesize RNA?",
    alpha: "Replication",
    beta: "Translation",
    charlie: "Transcription",
    delta: "Mutation",
    correct_answer: "Transcription",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 430,
    quiz_id: 43,
    question: "What is the role of the ribosome in protein synthesis?",
    alpha: "Synthesize RNA",
    beta: "Synthesize DNA",
    charlie: "Synthesize proteins",
    delta: "Synthesize lipids",
    correct_answer: "Synthesize proteins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 431,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "What is the basic structural and functional unit of all living organisms?",
    alpha: "Cell",
    beta: "Tissue",
    charlie: "Organ",
    delta: "Organism",
    correct_answer: "Cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 432,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "Which organelle is responsible for the synthesis of proteins in a cell?",
    alpha: "Mitochondrion",
    beta: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    charlie: "Golgi apparatus",
    delta: "Ribosome",
    correct_answer: "Ribosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 433,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "What is the function of the mitochondria in a cell?",
    alpha: "Photosynthesis",
    beta: "Cellular respiration",
    charlie: "Protein synthesis",
    delta: "Lipid synthesis",
    correct_answer: "Cellular respiration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 434,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "Which cellular structure contains the genetic material (DNA) of a eukaryotic cell?",
    alpha: "Nucleus",
    beta: "Mitochondrion",
    charlie: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    delta: "Ribosome",
    correct_answer: "Nucleus",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 435,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "What is the function of the endoplasmic reticulum (ER) in a cell?",
    alpha: "Lipid synthesis",
    beta: "Protein synthesis",
    charlie: "Detoxification",
    delta: "Storage of genetic material",
    correct_answer: "Protein synthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 436,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "Which cellular organelle is responsible for sorting, modifying, and packaging proteins for secretion?",
    alpha: "Lysosome",
    beta: "Golgi apparatus",
    charlie: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    delta: "Vacuole",
    correct_answer: "Golgi apparatus",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 437,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "What is the primary function of the lysosomes in a cell?",
    alpha: "Energy production",
    beta: "Digestion of cellular debris",
    charlie: "Photosynthesis",
    delta: "Protein synthesis",
    correct_answer: "Digestion of cellular debris",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 438,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "Which cellular structure is responsible for providing structural support and shape to plant cells?",
    alpha: "Cytoskeleton",
    beta: "Cell membrane",
    charlie: "Cell wall",
    delta: "Nuclear envelope",
    correct_answer: "Cell wall",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 439,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "What is the term for the semi-fluid matrix that fills the interior of a cell and surrounds the organelles?",
    alpha: "Cytoplasm",
    beta: "Nucleoplasm",
    charlie: "Endoplasm",
    delta: "Interstitium",
    correct_answer: "Cytoplasm",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 440,
    quiz_id: 44,
    question: "Which cellular structure is responsible for the movement of chromosomes during cell division?",
    alpha: "Centrosome",
    beta: "Nucleolus",
    charlie: "Lysosome",
    delta: "Golgi apparatus",
    correct_answer: "Centrosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 441,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "What is the primary function of hormones in the human body?",
    alpha: "Digestion of food",
    beta: "Transport of oxygen",
    charlie: "Regulation of physiological processes",
    delta: "Synthesis of proteins",
    correct_answer: "Regulation of physiological processes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 442,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "Which gland is often referred to as the 'master gland' because it controls other endocrine glands?",
    alpha: "Thyroid gland",
    beta: "Pancreas",
    charlie: "Adrenal gland",
    delta: "Pituitary gland",
    correct_answer: "Pituitary gland",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 443,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "What hormone is produced by the pancreas and regulates blood sugar levels?",
    alpha: "Insulin",
    beta: "Thyroxine",
    charlie: "Adrenaline",
    delta: "Estrogen",
    correct_answer: "Insulin",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 444,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "Which hormone is responsible for regulating the sleep-wake cycle?",
    alpha: "Melatonin",
    beta: "Serotonin",
    charlie: "Dopamine",
    delta: "Epinephrine",
    correct_answer: "Melatonin",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 445,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "What is the primary function of adrenaline (epinephrine) in the body?",
    alpha: "Regulation of blood pressure",
    beta: "Fight or flight response",
    charlie: "Digestion of food",
    delta: "Regulation of sleep",
    correct_answer: "Fight or flight response",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 446,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "Which hormone is responsible for the development of male secondary sexual characteristics?",
    alpha: "Estrogen",
    beta: "Progesterone",
    charlie: "Testosterone",
    delta: "Insulin",
    correct_answer: "Testosterone",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 447,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "What is the primary function of thyroid hormones?",
    alpha: "Regulate metabolism",
    beta: "Control blood sugar levels",
    charlie: "Stimulate muscle contraction",
    delta: "Promote bone growth",
    correct_answer: "Regulate metabolism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 448,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "Which hormone is produced by the ovaries and is important for the menstrual cycle and pregnancy?",
    alpha: "Estrogen",
    beta: "Progesterone",
    charlie: "Testosterone",
    delta: "Insulin",
    correct_answer: "Progesterone",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 449,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "What is the hormone responsible for promoting water retention in the kidneys?",
    alpha: "Aldosterone",
    beta: "Adrenaline",
    charlie: "Insulin",
    delta: "Thyroxine",
    correct_answer: "Aldosterone",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 450,
    quiz_id: 45,
    question: "Which hormone is responsible for promoting the development of female secondary sexual characteristics?",
    alpha: "Estrogen",
    beta: "Progesterone",
    charlie: "Testosterone",
    delta: "Insulin",
    correct_answer: "Estrogen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 461,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What is the primary goal of analytical chemistry?",
    alpha: "Study of atoms and molecules",
    beta: "Analysis of chemical compounds",
    charlie: "Investigation of chemical reactions",
    delta: "Synthesis of new materials",
    correct_answer: "Analysis of chemical compounds",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 462,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "Which technique is commonly used for the separation of components in a mixture based on their different migration rates in a mobile phase?",
    alpha: "Mass spectrometry",
    beta: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    charlie: "Chromatography",
    delta: "Spectroscopy",
    correct_answer: "Chromatography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 463,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What is the term for a technique that separates molecules based on their size and charge using an electric field?",
    alpha: "Chromatography",
    beta: "Mass spectrometry",
    charlie: "Capillary electrophoresis",
    delta: "Infrared spectroscopy",
    correct_answer: "Capillary electrophoresis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 464,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "Which analytical technique is commonly used for the quantitative determination of the concentration of a substance in a sample?",
    alpha: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    beta: "Spectroscopy",
    charlie: "Titration",
    delta: "Mass spectrometry",
    correct_answer: "Titration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 465,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What is the purpose of a calibration curve in analytical chemistry?",
    alpha: "Separation of components",
    beta: "Identification of unknown substances",
    charlie: "Determination of concentration",
    delta: "Measurement of molecular weight",
    correct_answer: "Determination of concentration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 466,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "Which spectroscopic technique is particularly useful for identifying functional groups in organic compounds?",
    alpha: "Ultraviolet (UV) spectroscopy",
    beta: "Infrared (IR) spectroscopy",
    charlie: "Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR)",
    delta: "X-ray crystallography",
    correct_answer: "Infrared (IR) spectroscopy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 467,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What does the acronym HPLC stand for in the context of analytical chemistry?",
    alpha: "High-Performance Liquid Chromatography",
    beta: "High-Pressure Leaching Chemistry",
    charlie: "Hydrogen Peroxide Limiting Concentration",
    delta: "Homogeneous Polymerization of Liquid Compounds",
    correct_answer: "High-Performance Liquid Chromatography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 468,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "In atomic absorption spectroscopy, what is being measured to determine the concentration of an element in a sample?",
    alpha: "Absorption of X-rays",
    beta: "Absorption of ultraviolet light",
    charlie: "Absorption of infrared light",
    delta: "Absorption of atomic transitions",
    correct_answer: "Absorption of atomic transitions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 469,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What is the main principle behind mass spectrometry?",
    alpha: "Measurement of magnetic fields",
    beta: "Measurement of mass-to-charge ratio",
    charlie: "Measurement of light absorption",
    delta: "Measurement of electric potential",
    correct_answer: "Measurement of mass-to-charge ratio",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 470,
    quiz_id: 47,
    question: "What is the function of a detector in analytical instruments such as chromatographs or spectrometers?",
    alpha: "Separation of components",
    beta: "Identification of unknown substances",
    charlie: "Conversion of signals to electrical output",
    delta: "Measurement of sample temperature",
    correct_answer: "Conversion of signals to electrical output",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 471,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "What is the primary principle behind chromatography methods?",
    alpha: "Absorption of ultraviolet light",
    beta: "Scattering of X-rays",
    charlie: "Separation based on molecular size and affinity",
    delta: "Absorption of microwaves",
    correct_answer: "Separation based on molecular size and affinity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 472,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "Which type of chromatography relies on the differential partitioning of analytes between a stationary phase and a mobile phase?",
    alpha: "Column chromatography",
    beta: "Thin-layer chromatography",
    charlie: "Gas chromatography",
    delta: "Liquid chromatography",
    correct_answer: "Liquid chromatography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 473,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "In gas chromatography, what is the mobile phase?",
    alpha: "Liquid",
    beta: "Gas",
    charlie: "Solid",
    delta: "Semisolid",
    correct_answer: "Gas",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 474,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "What is the purpose of the stationary phase in chromatography?",
    alpha: "To move with the mobile phase",
    beta: "To dissolve the sample",
    charlie: "To separate and interact with analytes",
    delta: "To increase the flow rate",
    correct_answer: "To separate and interact with analytes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 475,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "Which type of chromatography is often used for the separation of amino acids and peptides?",
    alpha: "Ion-exchange chromatography",
    beta: "Affinity chromatography",
    charlie: "Size-exclusion chromatography",
    delta: "High-performance liquid chromatography (HPLC)",
    correct_answer: "Ion-exchange chromatography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 476,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "What is the role of a detector in chromatography?",
    alpha: "To dissolve the sample",
    beta: "To separate analytes",
    charlie: "To detect and quantify separated analytes",
    delta: "To increase the flow rate",
    correct_answer: "To detect and quantify separated analytes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 477,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "In thin-layer chromatography, what is the stationary phase?",
    alpha: "Liquid",
    beta: "Gas",
    charlie: "Solid",
    delta: "Semisolid",
    correct_answer: "Solid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 478,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "Which type of chromatography is based on the interaction between biomolecules and a specific ligand?",
    alpha: "Column chromatography",
    beta: "Ion-exchange chromatography",
    charlie: "Affinity chromatography",
    delta: "Size-exclusion chromatography",
    correct_answer: "Affinity chromatography",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 479,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "What is the primary factor that determines the separation of analytes in size-exclusion chromatography?",
    alpha: "Charge",
    beta: "Molecular size",
    charlie: "Affinity",
    delta: "Hydrophobicity",
    correct_answer: "Molecular size",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 480,
    quiz_id: 48,
    question: "In high-performance liquid chromatography (HPLC), what is the typical composition of the mobile phase?",
    alpha: "Liquid",
    beta: "Gas",
    charlie: "Solid",
    delta: "Semisolid",
    correct_answer: "Liquid",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 481,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "What is the fundamental principle behind voltammetry techniques in electroanalysis?",
    alpha: "Measurement of voltage",
    beta: "Measurement of current",
    charlie: "Measurement of resistance",
    delta: "Measurement of capacitance",
    correct_answer: "Measurement of current",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 482,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "In potentiometry, what type of electrode is used to measure the potential of the solution being analyzed?",
    alpha: "Reference electrode",
    beta: "Indicator electrode",
    charlie: "Working electrode",
    delta: "Counter electrode",
    correct_answer: "Reference electrode",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 483,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "Which electroanalytical technique involves the measurement of the current resulting from the application of a constant potential?",
    alpha: "Cyclic voltammetry",
    beta: "Chronopotentiometry",
    charlie: "Amperometry",
    delta: "Polarography",
    correct_answer: "Amperometry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 484,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of polarography in electroanalysis?",
    alpha: "Measurement of voltage",
    beta: "Measurement of current",
    charlie: "Measurement of resistance",
    delta: "Measurement of capacitance",
    correct_answer: "Measurement of current",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 485,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "In chronoamperometry, what is being monitored over time?",
    alpha: "Voltage",
    beta: "Current",
    charlie: "Resistance",
    delta: "Capacitance",
    correct_answer: "Current",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 486,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "Which electroanalytical technique involves applying a linear voltage sweep and measuring the resulting current?",
    alpha: "Cyclic voltammetry",
    beta: "Chronopotentiometry",
    charlie: "Amperometry",
    delta: "Polarography",
    correct_answer: "Cyclic voltammetry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 487,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "In impedance spectroscopy, what is being analyzed?",
    alpha: "Voltage",
    beta: "Current",
    charlie: "Resistance",
    delta: "Frequency-dependent response",
    correct_answer: "Frequency-dependent response",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 488,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "What is the primary advantage of using cyclic voltammetry in electroanalysis?",
    alpha: "High sensitivity",
    beta: "High selectivity",
    charlie: "Simultaneous measurement of current and voltage",
    delta: "Rapid analysis",
    correct_answer: "Simultaneous measurement of current and voltage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 489,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "Which electroanalytical technique is particularly useful for studying electrode kinetics and reaction mechanisms?",
    alpha: "Chronopotentiometry",
    beta: "Cyclic voltammetry",
    charlie: "Amperometry",
    delta: "Polarography",
    correct_answer: "Cyclic voltammetry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 490,
    quiz_id: 49,
    question: "In a three-electrode electrochemical cell, what is the purpose of the working electrode?",
    alpha: "Generate current",
    beta: "Measure potential",
    charlie: "Provide a reference potential",
    delta: "Facilitate the reaction of interest",
    correct_answer: "Facilitate the reaction of interest",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 491,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "What is the fundamental principle behind mass spectrometry?",
    alpha: "Measurement of voltage",
    beta: "Measurement of current",
    charlie: "Measurement of mass-to-charge ratio",
    delta: "Measurement of resistance",
    correct_answer: "Measurement of mass-to-charge ratio",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 492,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "In mass spectrometry, what ionization technique involves the use of a laser to desorb and ionize samples from a solid surface?",
    alpha: "Electron impact ionization",
    beta: "Chemical ionization",
    charlie: "Matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization (MALDI)",
    delta: "Atmospheric pressure chemical ionization (APCI)",
    correct_answer: "Matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization (MALDI)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 493,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "What is the purpose of the mass analyzer in a mass spectrometer?",
    alpha: "Ionize the sample",
    beta: "Separate ions based on their mass-to-charge ratio",
    charlie: "Detect ions",
    delta: "Accelerate ions",
    correct_answer: "Separate ions based on their mass-to-charge ratio",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 494,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "Which type of mass spectrometry is commonly used for determining the elemental composition of a sample?",
    alpha: "Gas Chromatography-Mass Spectrometry (GC-MS)",
    beta: "Liquid Chromatography-Mass Spectrometry (LC-MS)",
    charlie: "Inductively Coupled Plasma Mass Spectrometry (ICP-MS)",
    delta: "Time-of-Flight Mass Spectrometry (TOF-MS)",
    correct_answer: "Inductively Coupled Plasma Mass Spectrometry (ICP-MS)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 495,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "In electron impact ionization, what is used to generate electrons that collide with the sample molecules?",
    alpha: "Laser",
    beta: "Photons",
    charlie: "Electrons",
    delta: "High-energy electrons",
    correct_answer: "High-energy electrons",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 496,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "What information can be obtained from a mass spectrum?",
    alpha: "Concentration of the sample",
    beta: "Molecular weight of the sample",
    charlie: "Temperature of the sample",
    delta: "Volume of the sample",
    correct_answer: "Molecular weight of the sample",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 497,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "In tandem mass spectrometry (MS/MS), what is the purpose of the second mass analyzer?",
    alpha: "Ionize the sample",
    beta: "Detect ions",
    charlie: "Fragment ions from the first mass analyzer",
    delta: "Separate ions based on their charge",
    correct_answer: "Fragment ions from the first mass analyzer",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 498,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "Which type of mass spectrometer is based on the principle that ions traveling through a magnetic field experience a force proportional to their mass-to-charge ratio?",
    alpha: "Time-of-Flight Mass Spectrometry (TOF-MS)",
    beta: "Quadrupole Mass Spectrometry",
    charlie: "Ion Trap Mass Spectrometry",
    delta: "Magnetic Sector Mass Spectrometry",
    correct_answer: "Magnetic Sector Mass Spectrometry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 499,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "What is the role of the detector in a mass spectrometer?",
    alpha: "Ionize the sample",
    beta: "Separate ions based on their mass-to-charge ratio",
    charlie: "Detect ions",
    delta: "Accelerate ions",
    correct_answer: "Detect ions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 500,
    quiz_id: 50,
    question: "Which factor affects the trajectory of ions in a mass spectrometer?",
    alpha: "Concentration of the sample",
    beta: "Mass-to-charge ratio",
    charlie: "Temperature of the sample",
    delta: "Volume of the sample",
    correct_answer: "Mass-to-charge ratio",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 501,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Simplify the expression: 3x + 5y - 2x - 7y",
    alpha: "x - 2y",
    beta: "x + 2y",
    charlie: "x - 12y",
    delta: "x + 12y",
    correct_answer: "x - 2y",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 502,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Combine like terms: 4a + 2b - 3a - 7b",
    alpha: "a - 5b",
    beta: "a + 5b",
    charlie: "a - 10b",
    delta: "a + 10b",
    correct_answer: "a - 5b",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 503,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Solve for x: 2(x - 4) = 3x + 6",
    alpha: "-2",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "-4",
    correct_answer: "-2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 504,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Factorize: x^2 - 9",
    alpha: "(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    beta: "(x - 9)(x + 9)",
    charlie: "(x - 6)(x + 6)",
    delta: "(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    correct_answer: "(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 505,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Multiply: (2x + 3)(4x - 5)",
    alpha: "8x^2 - 7x - 15",
    beta: "8x^2 + 7x - 15",
    charlie: "8x^2 - 7x + 15",
    delta: "8x^2 + 7x + 15",
    correct_answer: "8x^2 - 7x - 15",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 506,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Divide: (6x^2 - 9x) ÷ 3x",
    alpha: "2x - 3",
    beta: "2x + 3",
    charlie: "2x - 1",
    delta: "2x + 1",
    correct_answer: "2x - 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 507,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Solve the equation: 5(x - 2) = 3(2x + 1)",
    alpha: "x = 3",
    beta: "x = -3",
    charlie: "x = 2",
    delta: "x = -2",
    correct_answer: "x = 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 508,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Expand and simplify: (a - 2)(a^2 + 2a + 4)",
    alpha: "a^3 + 4a^2 - 8",
    beta: "a^3 - 4a^2 + 8",
    charlie: "a^3 - 2a^2 - 8",
    delta: "a^3 + 2a^2 + 8",
    correct_answer: "a^3 - 2a^2 - 8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 509,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Factorize: 9x^2 - 16y^2",
    alpha: "(3x + 4y)(3x - 4y)",
    beta: "(3x - 4y)(3x + 4y)",
    charlie: "(9x + 16y)(9x - 16y)",
    delta: "(9x - 16y)(9x + 16y)",
    correct_answer: "(3x + 4y)(3x - 4y)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 510,
    quiz_id: 51,
    question: "Solve for x: 2(x + 1) = x - 3",
    alpha: "x = -5",
    beta: "x = 2",
    charlie: "x = -2",
    delta: "x = 4",
    correct_answer: "x = -5",
    selected_option: null,
  }, {
    question_id: 511,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve for x: 2x + 5 = 11",
    alpha: "x = 3",
    beta: "x = 2",
    charlie: "x = 6",
    delta: "x = 8",
    correct_answer: "x = 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 512,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Simplify: 3(x - 4) + 2 = 5x - 6",
    alpha: "x = 4",
    beta: "x = 2",
    charlie: "x = 6",
    delta: "x = 8",
    correct_answer: "x = 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 513,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve the inequality: 2x + 7 < 15",
    alpha: "x < 4",
    beta: "x > 4",
    charlie: "x < 2",
    delta: "x > 2",
    correct_answer: "x < 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 514,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Simplify: -2(3x - 5) + 4x = 12",
    alpha: "x = 3",
    beta: "x = 2",
    charlie: "x = 4",
    delta: "x = 5",
    correct_answer: "x = 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 515,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve for y: 5(y - 2) + 3 = 2(y + 4)",
    alpha: "y = 1",
    beta: "y = 2",
    charlie: "y = -1",
    delta: "y = -2",
    correct_answer: "y = -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 516,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve the inequality: 3 - 2x ≥ 7",
    alpha: "x ≤ -2",
    beta: "x ≥ -2",
    charlie: "x ≤ 2",
    delta: "x ≥ 2",
    correct_answer: "x ≤ -2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 517,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Simplify: 4(2y + 3) - 2(3y - 1)",
    alpha: "6y + 14",
    beta: "2y + 8",
    charlie: "8y + 14",
    delta: "6y - 14",
    correct_answer: "6y + 14",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 518,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve for x: 2(3x + 1) = 5 - x",
    alpha: "x = -1",
    beta: "x = 1",
    charlie: "x = -2",
    delta: "x = 2",
    correct_answer: "x = -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 519,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Solve the inequality: -3x + 6 < 9",
    alpha: "x > -1",
    beta: "x < -1",
    charlie: "x > 3",
    delta: "x < 3",
    correct_answer: "x > -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 520,
    quiz_id: 52,
    question: "Simplify: 2(a - 3) - 5a = 7",
    alpha: "a = -2",
    beta: "a = -1",
    charlie: "a = 0",
    delta: "a = 1",
    correct_answer: "a = -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 521,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Factorize: x^2 - 4",
    alpha: "(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    beta: "(x - 4)(x + 4)",
    charlie: "(x - 3)(x + 3)",
    delta: "(x - 1)(x + 1)",
    correct_answer: "(x - 2)(x + 2)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 522,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Simplify: (2a + 3b)^2",
    alpha: "4a^2 + 9b^2",
    beta: "4a^2 + 12ab + 9b^2",
    charlie: "4a^2 - 12ab + 9b^2",
    delta: "4a^2 - 9b^2",
    correct_answer: "4a^2 + 12ab + 9b^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 523,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Factorize: 9x^2 - 16",
    alpha: "(3x - 4)(3x + 4)",
    beta: "(3x - 9)(3x + 9)",
    charlie: "(9x - 16)(9x + 16)",
    delta: "(9x - 4)(9x + 4)",
    correct_answer: "(3x - 4)(3x + 4)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 524,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Multiply: (x - 2)(x + 3)",
    alpha: "x^2 + x - 6",
    beta: "x^2 + x + 6",
    charlie: "x^2 - x - 6",
    delta: "x^2 - x + 6",
    correct_answer: "x^2 + x - 6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 525,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Factorize completely: x^2 - 5x + 6",
    alpha: "(x - 2)(x - 3)",
    beta: "(x + 2)(x - 3)",
    charlie: "(x - 2)(x + 3)",
    delta: "(x + 2)(x + 3)",
    correct_answer: "(x - 2)(x - 3)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 526,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Simplify: (a^2 + 4a + 4)/(a + 2)",
    alpha: "a + 2",
    beta: "a + 4",
    charlie: "a + 1",
    delta: "a + 3",
    correct_answer: "a + 2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 527,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Factorize: 4y^2 - 1",
    alpha: "(2y - 1)(2y + 1)",
    beta: "(4y - 1)(4y + 1)",
    charlie: "(2y - 1)(2y + 2)",
    delta: "(4y - 2)(4y + 2)",
    correct_answer: "(2y - 1)(2y + 1)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 528,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Multiply: (x + 5)(x - 2)",
    alpha: "x^2 + 5x + 10",
    beta: "x^2 + 3x - 10",
    charlie: "x^2 - 3x + 10",
    delta: "x^2 + 3x + 10",
    correct_answer: "x^2 + 3x - 10",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 529,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Factorize completely: x^3 - 8",
    alpha: "(x - 2)(x^2 + 2x + 4)",
    beta: "(x + 2)(x^2 - 2x + 4)",
    charlie: "(x - 2)(x^2 - 2x + 4)",
    delta: "(x + 2)(x^2 + 2x + 4)",
    correct_answer: "(x - 2)(x^2 + 2x + 4)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 530,
    quiz_id: 53,
    question: "Divide: (3x^2 + 5x - 2) ÷ (x - 2)",
    alpha: "3x + 7",
    beta: "3x - 7",
    charlie: "3x + 2",
    delta: "3x - 2",
    correct_answer: "3x + 7",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 531,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "Which of the following is a function?",
    alpha: "y^2 = x",
    beta: "x^2 + y^2 = 1",
    charlie: "y = 2x + 3",
    delta: "x^2 - y^2 = 4",
    correct_answer: "y = 2x + 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 532,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "What is the domain of the function f(x) = 2x - 5?",
    alpha: "All real numbers",
    beta: "x ≥ 5",
    charlie: "x ≤ 5",
    delta: "x ≠ 5",
    correct_answer: "All real numbers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 533,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "Which of the following graphs represents a quadratic function?",
    alpha: "Line",
    beta: "Parabola",
    charlie: "Circle",
    delta: "Hyperbola",
    correct_answer: "Parabola",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 534,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "If f(x) = x^2, what is the value of f(-3)?",
    alpha: "9",
    beta: "6",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "0",
    correct_answer: "9",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 535,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "Which of the following is the inverse of the function f(x) = 2x + 4?",
    alpha: "y = (x - 4)/2",
    beta: "y = (x + 4)/2",
    charlie: "y = 2x - 4",
    delta: "y = 2x + 4",
    correct_answer: "y = (x - 4)/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 536,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "What is the range of the function g(x) = sin(x)?",
    alpha: "All real numbers",
    beta: "-1 ≤ y ≤ 1",
    charlie: "y > 1",
    delta: "y < -1",
    correct_answer: "-1 ≤ y ≤ 1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 537,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "Which of the following is the vertical asymptote of the function h(x) = 1/(x - 2)?",
    alpha: "x = 2",
    beta: "y = 0",
    charlie: "x = 0",
    delta: "y = 2",
    correct_answer: "x = 2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 538,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "If k(x) = |x - 3|, what is the value of k(7)?",
    alpha: "4",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "0",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 539,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "Which of the following statements is true for an even function?",
    alpha: "f(x) = f(-x) for all x",
    beta: "f(x) = -f(-x) for all x",
    charlie: "f(x) = -f(x) for all x",
    delta: "f(x) = f(x + 1) for all x",
    correct_answer: "f(x) = f(-x) for all x",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 540,
    quiz_id: 54,
    question: "The function p(x) = 3x^2 - 5x + 2 is a?",
    alpha: "Linear function",
    beta: "Quadratic function",
    charlie: "Cubic function",
    delta: "Exponential function",
    correct_answer: "Quadratic function",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 541,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Simplify: 2^3 * 2^5",
    alpha: "2^15",
    beta: "2^8",
    charlie: "2^12",
    delta: "2^40",
    correct_answer: "2^8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 542,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "What is the value of 5^0?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "5",
    delta: "25",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 543,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Solve for x: 3^x = 81",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 544,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Evaluate: log2(8)",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 545,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Simplify: log3(81)",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 546,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "What is the value of 10^(-2)?",
    alpha: "1/10",
    beta: "1/100",
    charlie: "1/20",
    delta: "1/200",
    correct_answer: "1/100",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 547,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Solve for x: log5(x) = 2",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "25",
    delta: "100",
    correct_answer: "25",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 548,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Evaluate: ln(e)",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "e",
    delta: "π",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 549,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "Simplify: 4^(1/2)",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "4",
    charlie: "8",
    delta: "16",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 550,
    quiz_id: 55,
    question: "If 2^x = 16, what is the value of x?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 551,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Evaluate the limit as x approaches 3: (x^2 - 9)/(x - 3)",
    alpha: "6",
    beta: "9",
    charlie: "12",
    delta: "Undefined",
    correct_answer: "6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 552,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Find the limit as x approaches 0: (sin(x))/x",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "Undefined",
    delta: "π",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 553,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Determine the limit as x approaches 2 from the left: 1/(x - 2)",
    alpha: "-∞",
    beta: "∞",
    charlie: "-1",
    delta: "Undefined",
    correct_answer: "-∞",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 554,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Evaluate the limit as x approaches 1: (x^3 - 1)/(x^2 - 1)",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "2",
    delta: "Undefined",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 555,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Find the limit as x approaches ∞: (2x^2 - 3x)/(4x^2 + 5)",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1/2",
    charlie: "1",
    delta: "Undefined",
    correct_answer: "1/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 556,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Determine the limit as x approaches 4: (x^2 - 16)/(x - 4)",
    alpha: "8",
    beta: "12",
    charlie: "Undefined",
    delta: "16",
    correct_answer: "8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 557,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Find the limit as x approaches -1: (|x + 1|)/(x + 1)",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "Undefined",
    delta: "-1",
    correct_answer: "Undefined",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 558,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Evaluate the limit as x approaches 0: (e^x - 1)/x",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "e",
    charlie: "Undefined",
    delta: "0",
    correct_answer: "e",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 559,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Determine the limit as x approaches ∞: (3x^2 - 5)/(2x^2 + 1)",
    alpha: "3/2",
    beta: "5/2",
    charlie: "3/4",
    delta: "Undefined",
    correct_answer: "3/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 560,
    quiz_id: 56,
    question: "Find the limit as x approaches -2: (x^2 + 3x + 2)/(x^2 - 4)",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "Undefined",
    delta: "0",
    correct_answer: "Undefined",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 561,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Find the derivative of f(x) = 3x^2 + 2x - 1",
    alpha: "6x + 2",
    beta: "3x^2 + 2",
    charlie: "6x - 2",
    delta: "6x",
    correct_answer: "6x + 2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 562,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Compute the derivative of g(x) = sin(x)",
    alpha: "cos(x)",
    beta: "-sin(x)",
    charlie: "tan(x)",
    delta: "cot(x)",
    correct_answer: "cos(x)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 563,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Find the derivative of h(x) = e^x",
    alpha: "e^x",
    beta: "e^(x+1)",
    charlie: "e^(x-1)",
    delta: "2e^x",
    correct_answer: "e^x",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 564,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Compute the derivative of f(x) = ln(x)",
    alpha: "1/x",
    beta: "-1/x",
    charlie: "x",
    delta: "e^x",
    correct_answer: "1/x",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 565,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Find the derivative of g(x) = 2x^3 - 5x^2 + 3x + 1",
    alpha: "6x^2 - 10x + 3",
    beta: "6x^2 - 10x - 3",
    charlie: "6x^2 - 5x + 3",
    delta: "6x^2 - 5x - 3",
    correct_answer: "6x^2 - 10x + 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 566,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Compute the derivative of h(x) = cos(2x)",
    alpha: "-2sin(2x)",
    beta: "2cos(2x)",
    charlie: "-sin(2x)",
    delta: "-cos(2x)",
    correct_answer: "-2sin(2x)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 567,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Find the derivative of f(x) = sqrt(x)",
    alpha: "1/(2sqrt(x))",
    beta: "1/(2x)",
    charlie: "sqrt(x)",
    delta: "2sqrt(x)",
    correct_answer: "1/(2sqrt(x))",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 568,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Compute the derivative of g(x) = tan(x)",
    alpha: "sec^2(x)",
    beta: "cos(x)",
    charlie: "csc^2(x)",
    delta: "-csc^2(x)",
    correct_answer: "sec^2(x)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 569,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Find the derivative of h(x) = 1/x",
    alpha: "-1/x^2",
    beta: "1/x^2",
    charlie: "-2/x^2",
    delta: "2/x^2",
    correct_answer: "-1/x^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 570,
    quiz_id: 57,
    question: "Compute the derivative of f(x) = e^(2x)",
    alpha: "2e^(2x)",
    beta: "e^(2x)",
    charlie: "4e^(2x)",
    delta: "2e^(2x + 1)",
    correct_answer: "2e^(2x)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 571,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Evaluate the integral: ∫ (2x + 3) dx",
    alpha: "x^2 + 3x",
    beta: "x^2 + 3x + C",
    charlie: "x^2 + 3",
    delta: "x^2 + C",
    correct_answer: "x^2 + 3x + C",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 572,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Compute the definite integral: ∫[1 to 4] (3x^2 - 2x) dx",
    alpha: "29",
    beta: "45",
    charlie: "57",
    delta: "62",
    correct_answer: "29",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 573,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Find the integral: ∫ e^x dx",
    alpha: "e^x",
    beta: "e^(x+1)",
    charlie: "e^(x-1)",
    delta: "2e^x",
    correct_answer: "e^x + C",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 574,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Evaluate the definite integral: ∫[0 to π] sin(x) dx",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "π",
    delta: "2",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 575,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Compute the integral: ∫ 2x^3 dx",
    alpha: "x^4",
    beta: "(1/2)x^4",
    charlie: "(1/4)x^4",
    delta: "(1/8)x^4",
    correct_answer: "(1/2)x^4 + C",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 576,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Find the definite integral: ∫[1 to 3] (x^2 - 1) dx",
    alpha: "9",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "11",
    delta: "12",
    correct_answer: "12",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 577,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Evaluate the integral: ∫ cos(2x) dx",
    alpha: "(1/2)sin(2x)",
    beta: "sin(2x)",
    charlie: "(1/4)sin(2x)",
    delta: "(1/2)cos(2x)",
    correct_answer: "(1/2)sin(2x) + C",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 578,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Compute the definite integral: ∫[0 to 2] e^x dx",
    alpha: "e^2 - 1",
    beta: "e^2",
    charlie: "e - 1",
    delta: "e",
    correct_answer: "e^2 - 1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 579,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Find the integral: ∫ 1/x dx",
    alpha: "ln|x|",
    beta: "ln(x)",
    charlie: "ln(1/x)",
    delta: "xln(x)",
    correct_answer: "ln|x| + C",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 580,
    quiz_id: 58,
    question: "Evaluate the definite integral: ∫[1 to 4] x^2 dx",
    alpha: "20",
    beta: "45",
    charlie: "60",
    delta: "75",
    correct_answer: "60",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 581,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A particle moves along a straight line. Its position at time t is given by s(t) = 3t^2 - 2t + 1. Find its velocity at time t.",
    alpha: "6t - 2",
    beta: "6t - 4",
    charlie: "6t + 2",
    delta: "6t + 4",
    correct_answer: "6t - 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 582,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A ladder is leaning against a wall. The bottom of the ladder is sliding away from the wall at a rate of 2 ft/s. If the top of the ladder is 10 ft above the ground, how fast is the top of the ladder sliding down the wall when the bottom is 6 ft away from the wall?",
    alpha: "2 ft/s",
    beta: "3 ft/s",
    charlie: "4 ft/s",
    delta: "5 ft/s",
    correct_answer: "3 ft/s",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 583,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A rectangular box with a square base is to be constructed with a given volume V. If the length of one side of the square base is x and the height of the box is h, express the surface area A of the box as a function of x.",
    alpha: "A(x) = x^2 + 4V/x",
    beta: "A(x) = x^2 + 4V/x^2",
    charlie: "A(x) = x^2 + 2V/x",
    delta: "A(x) = x^2 + 2V/x^2",
    correct_answer: "A(x) = x^2 + 4V/x",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 584,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A balloon is rising straight up from the ground. If the balloon is 100 feet above the ground and rising at a rate of 10 feet per second, how fast is the angle of elevation changing when the balloon is 60 feet above the ground?",
    alpha: "1/6 radians per second",
    beta: "1/5 radians per second",
    charlie: "1/4 radians per second",
    delta: "1/3 radians per second",
    correct_answer: "1/5 radians per second",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 585,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A rectangle has one side along the x-axis and one vertex on the curve y = 4 - x^2. Find the dimensions of the rectangle of maximum area.",
    alpha: "Length = 2, Width = 4",
    beta: "Length = 4, Width = 2",
    charlie: "Length = 3, Width = 3",
    delta: "Length = 1, Width = 4",
    correct_answer: "Length = 2, Width = 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 586,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A cylindrical can is to be made to hold 1 liter of oil. Find the dimensions (radius and height) that will minimize the cost of the metal to manufacture the can.",
    alpha: "r = 0.5, h = 2",
    beta: "r = 1, h = 1",
    charlie: "r = 0.25, h = 4",
    delta: "r = 2, h = 0.5",
    correct_answer: "r = 0.5, h = 2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 587,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A ladder 15 feet long is leaning against a building. If the bottom of the ladder is sliding away from the building at a rate of 4 feet per second, how fast is the top of the ladder sliding down the wall when the bottom is 9 feet from the wall?",
    alpha: "2 ft/s",
    beta: "3 ft/s",
    charlie: "4 ft/s",
    delta: "5 ft/s",
    correct_answer: "4 ft/s",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 588,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A circular metal plate is heated in an oven and its radius increases at a rate of 0.1 cm/minute. At what rate is the plate's area increasing when the radius is 5 cm?",
    alpha: "0.5π cm^2/min",
    beta: "π cm^2/min",
    charlie: "1.5π cm^2/min",
    delta: "2π cm^2/min",
    correct_answer: "π cm^2/min",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 589,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A ladder 20 feet long is leaning against a vertical wall. If the bottom of the ladder is sliding away from the wall at a rate of 2 feet per second, how fast is the top of the ladder sliding down the wall when the bottom is 16 feet from the wall?",
    alpha: "1 ft/s",
    beta: "2 ft/s",
    charlie: "3 ft/s",
    delta: "4 ft/s",
    correct_answer: "3 ft/s",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 590,
    quiz_id: 59,
    question: "A cone-shaped cup is to be made with a fixed volume of 100π cubic centimeters. Find the dimensions that will minimize the cost of making the cup if the material costs $0.02 per square centimeter.",
    alpha: "r = 5 cm, h = 4 cm",
    beta: "r = 4 cm, h = 5 cm",
    charlie: "r = 6 cm, h = 3 cm",
    delta: "r = 3 cm, h = 6 cm",
    correct_answer: "r = 5 cm, h = 4 cm",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 591,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A tank is full of water. Find the work required to pump out half of the water through the top of the tank.",
    alpha: "Work = ρghV/2",
    beta: "Work = ρghV",
    charlie: "Work = ρghV/4",
    delta: "Work = ρghV/3",
    correct_answer: "Work = ρghV/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 592,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A particle moves along the x-axis with velocity v(t) = t^2 - 2t, where t is in seconds. Find the displacement of the particle from time t = 1 to t = 4.",
    alpha: "12 units",
    beta: "16 units",
    charlie: "18 units",
    delta: "20 units",
    correct_answer: "16 units",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 593,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A wire has density function δ(x) = e^(-x) for 0 ≤ x ≤ ∞. Find the total mass of the wire.",
    alpha: "Mass = 1",
    beta: "Mass = 2",
    charlie: "Mass = e",
    delta: "Mass = 1/e",
    correct_answer: "Mass = 1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 594,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A plate of metal occupies the region bounded by the curves y = x^2 and y = 4. Find the area of the region.",
    alpha: "Area = 7",
    beta: "Area = 8",
    charlie: "Area = 9",
    delta: "Area = 10",
    correct_answer: "Area = 7",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 595,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A curve is defined by the equation y = 2x^3. Find the length of the curve from x = 0 to x = 2.",
    alpha: "Length = 10",
    beta: "Length = 12",
    charlie: "Length = 14",
    delta: "Length = 16",
    correct_answer: "Length = 14",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 596,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A solid has base region bounded by the curve y = sqrt(x) and the x-axis from x = 0 to x = 1. Cross-sections perpendicular to the x-axis are semicircles. Find the volume of the solid.",
    alpha: "Volume = π/4",
    beta: "Volume = π/2",
    charlie: "Volume = 3π/8",
    delta: "Volume = 2π/3",
    correct_answer: "Volume = π/4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 597,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A rope 10 meters long weighs 4 N/m. How much work is required to lift the entire rope to a height of 5 meters?",
    alpha: "Work = 125 J",
    beta: "Work = 100 J",
    charlie: "Work = 75 J",
    delta: "Work = 50 J",
    correct_answer: "Work = 100 J",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 598,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A tank is in the shape of a cone with height 10 m and base radius 5 m. If the tank is full of water, find the work required to pump all the water to the top of the tank.",
    alpha: "Work = 2500π J",
    beta: "Work = 1250π J",
    charlie: "Work = 1000π J",
    delta: "Work = 750π J",
    correct_answer: "Work = 1250π J",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 599,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A particle moves along the x-axis with position function x(t) = t^2 - 3t + 2. Find the total distance traveled by the particle from t = 0 to t = 3.",
    alpha: "Distance = 3 units",
    beta: "Distance = 4 units",
    charlie: "Distance = 5 units",
    delta: "Distance = 6 units",
    correct_answer: "Distance = 6 units",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 600,
    quiz_id: 60,
    question: "A wire of length 12 meters is bent into the shape of a semicircle. Find the radius of the semicircle if it maximizes the area.",
    alpha: "Radius = 2",
    beta: "Radius = 3",
    charlie: "Radius = 4",
    delta: "Radius = 5",
    correct_answer: "Radius = 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 601,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "In a right-angled triangle, if the lengths of the legs are 3 and 4, what is the length of the hypotenuse?",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "6",
    charlie: "7",
    delta: "8",
    correct_answer: "5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 602,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "What is the measure of each interior angle in a regular hexagon?",
    alpha: "120 degrees",
    beta: "130 degrees",
    charlie: "140 degrees",
    delta: "150 degrees",
    correct_answer: "120 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 603,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "If two angles of a triangle are 45 degrees and 75 degrees, what is the measure of the third angle?",
    alpha: "50 degrees",
    beta: "60 degrees",
    charlie: "70 degrees",
    delta: "80 degrees",
    correct_answer: "60 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 604,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "In a parallelogram, opposite angles are equal. If one angle is 80 degrees, what is the measure of its adjacent angle?",
    alpha: "80 degrees",
    beta: "100 degrees",
    charlie: "120 degrees",
    delta: "140 degrees",
    correct_answer: "100 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 605,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "The sum of the interior angles of a convex octagon is:",
    alpha: "720 degrees",
    beta: "800 degrees",
    charlie: "900 degrees",
    delta: "1000 degrees",
    correct_answer: "1080 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 606,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "What is the measure of each exterior angle of a regular pentagon?",
    alpha: "60 degrees",
    beta: "72 degrees",
    charlie: "90 degrees",
    delta: "108 degrees",
    correct_answer: "72 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 607,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "If a triangle is equilateral, what can be said about its angles?",
    alpha: "All angles are acute",
    beta: "All angles are obtuse",
    charlie: "All angles are right angles",
    delta: "All angles are equal",
    correct_answer: "All angles are equal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 608,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "What is the sum of the interior angles of a regular heptagon?",
    alpha: "540 degrees",
    beta: "630 degrees",
    charlie: "720 degrees",
    delta: "810 degrees",
    correct_answer: "900 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 609,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "If two angles are complementary, what is the sum of their measures?",
    alpha: "90 degrees",
    beta: "120 degrees",
    charlie: "180 degrees",
    delta: "360 degrees",
    correct_answer: "90 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 610,
    quiz_id: 61,
    question: "What is the area of a triangle with base 6 units and height 8 units?",
    alpha: "24 square units",
    beta: "30 square units",
    charlie: "36 square units",
    delta: "48 square units",
    correct_answer: "24 square units",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 611,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "If a figure is reflected across the x-axis, what happens to the y-coordinates of its vertices?",
    alpha: "They remain the same",
    beta: "They are multiplied by -1",
    charlie: "They are squared",
    delta: "They are divided by 2",
    correct_answer: "They are multiplied by -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 612,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "What type of symmetry does a rectangle have?",
    alpha: "No symmetry",
    beta: "Rotational symmetry",
    charlie: "Reflectional symmetry",
    delta: "Both rotational and reflectional symmetry",
    correct_answer: "Reflectional symmetry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 613,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "In a 90-degree rotation of a figure about the origin, what happens to the coordinates of its vertices?",
    alpha: "They are unchanged",
    beta: "They are multiplied by -1",
    charlie: "They are rotated 90 degrees",
    delta: "They are reflected across the y-axis",
    correct_answer: "They are rotated 90 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 614,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "If a figure is dilated with a scale factor of 2, what happens to its dimensions?",
    alpha: "They double",
    beta: "They halve",
    charlie: "They remain the same",
    delta: "They become square",
    correct_answer: "They double",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 615,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "Which transformation preserves both size and shape?",
    alpha: "Translation",
    beta: "Reflection",
    charlie: "Rotation",
    delta: "Dilation",
    correct_answer: "Translation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 616,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "A figure has rotational symmetry of order 3. What does this mean?",
    alpha: "It has 3 lines of symmetry",
    beta: "It can be rotated 3 times to coincide with itself",
    charlie: "It has 3 vertices",
    delta: "It has 3 sides",
    correct_answer: "It can be rotated 3 times to coincide with itself",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 617,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "What is the image of point P(2, 3) after a reflection across the y-axis?",
    alpha: "(-2, 3)",
    beta: "(2, -3)",
    charlie: "(-2, -3)",
    delta: "(3, 2)",
    correct_answer: "(-2, 3)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 618,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "A rectangle is translated 5 units to the right and 3 units down. What are the new coordinates of its vertices?",
    alpha: "(x + 5, y - 3)",
    beta: "(x - 5, y + 3)",
    charlie: "(x + 5, y + 3)",
    delta: "(x - 5, y - 3)",
    correct_answer: "(x + 5, y - 3)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 619,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "If a figure is rotated 180 degrees about the origin, what happens to its coordinates?",
    alpha: "They remain the same",
    beta: "They are multiplied by -1",
    charlie: "They are rotated 180 degrees",
    delta: "They are reflected across the x-axis",
    correct_answer: "They are multiplied by -1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 620,
    quiz_id: 62,
    question: "Which of the following transformations changes the shape of a figure?",
    alpha: "Translation",
    beta: "Rotation",
    charlie: "Dilation",
    delta: "Reflection",
    correct_answer: "Dilation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 621,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "In a right-angled triangle, if the length of one leg is 3 and the length of the other leg is 4, what is the value of the sine of the angle opposite the leg of length 3?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "2/3",
    charlie: "3/5",
    delta: "4/5",
    correct_answer: "3/5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 622,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "If sin θ = 3/4, what is the value of cos θ?",
    alpha: "1/4",
    beta: "1/3",
    charlie: "4/5",
    delta: "√7/4",
    correct_answer: "√7/4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 623,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "What is the cosecant of an angle if the sine of the angle is 2/3?",
    alpha: "3/2",
    beta: "3/√5",
    charlie: "√5/2",
    delta: "2/√5",
    correct_answer: "3/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 624,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "If tan θ = 4/3, what is the value of sec θ?",
    alpha: "3/4",
    beta: "4/3",
    charlie: "3/5",
    delta: "5/4",
    correct_answer: "5/4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 625,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "What is the value of sin(π/6)?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "√2/2",
    charlie: "√3/2",
    delta: "1/√2",
    correct_answer: "1/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 626,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "If cos α = -1/2, in which quadrant does the angle α lie?",
    alpha: "Quadrant I",
    beta: "Quadrant II",
    charlie: "Quadrant III",
    delta: "Quadrant IV",
    correct_answer: "Quadrant II",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 627,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "What is the value of cot(π/4)?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "√2",
    charlie: "1/√2",
    delta: "√3",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 628,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "If sin β = 3/5, what is the value of tan β?",
    alpha: "3/4",
    beta: "4/3",
    charlie: "√2/3",
    delta: "3/√2",
    correct_answer: "3/4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 629,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "If cos γ = 1/√2, what is the value of sin γ?",
    alpha: "√2/2",
    beta: "1/√3",
    charlie: "1/2",
    delta: "√3/2",
    correct_answer: "√2/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 630,
    quiz_id: 63,
    question: "What is the value of sec(π/3)?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "1/2",
    charlie: "√3",
    delta: "2/√3",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 631,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the opposite sides of a parallelogram are equal in length.",
    alpha: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: AB = CD.",
    beta: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: AD = BC.",
    charlie: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: AB + BC = CD + DA.",
    delta: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: AB * CD = BC * AD.",
    correct_answer: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: AB = CD.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 632,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the diagonals of a rectangle are equal in length.",
    alpha: "Given: ABCD is a rectangle. Prove: AC = BD.",
    beta: "Given: ABCD is a rectangle. Prove: AB = CD.",
    charlie: "Given: ABCD is a rectangle. Prove: AD = BC.",
    delta: "Given: ABCD is a rectangle. Prove: AB + BC = CD + DA.",
    correct_answer: "Given: ABCD is a rectangle. Prove: AC = BD.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 633,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the sum of the interior angles of a triangle is 180 degrees.",
    alpha: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: ∠A + ∠B + ∠C = 180°.",
    beta: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: ∠A + ∠B = ∠C.",
    charlie: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: ∠A * ∠B * ∠C = 180°.",
    delta: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: ∠A = ∠B = ∠C.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: ∠A + ∠B + ∠C = 180°.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 634,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the angles opposite congruent sides of a triangle are congruent.",
    alpha: "Given: Triangle ABC with AB ≅ AC. Prove: ∠B ≅ ∠C.",
    beta: "Given: Triangle ABC with AB ≅ AC. Prove: ∠A ≅ ∠B.",
    charlie: "Given: Triangle ABC with AB ≅ AC. Prove: ∠A = ∠B = ∠C.",
    delta: "Given: Triangle ABC with AB ≅ AC. Prove: ∠A * ∠B * ∠C = 180°.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Triangle ABC with AB ≅ AC. Prove: ∠B ≅ ∠C.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 635,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the angles in a cyclic quadrilateral add up to 360 degrees.",
    alpha: "Given: Quadrilateral ABCD is cyclic. Prove: ∠A + ∠B + ∠C + ∠D = 360°.",
    beta: "Given: Quadrilateral ABCD is cyclic. Prove: ∠A = ∠B = ∠C = ∠D.",
    charlie: "Given: Quadrilateral ABCD is cyclic. Prove: ∠A + ∠B = ∠C + ∠D.",
    delta: "Given: Quadrilateral ABCD is cyclic. Prove: ∠A + ∠C = ∠B + ∠D.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Quadrilateral ABCD is cyclic. Prove: ∠A + ∠B + ∠C + ∠D = 360°.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 636,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove the Pythagorean Theorem: In a right-angled triangle, the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the sum of the squares of the other two sides.",
    alpha: "Given: Right-angled triangle ABC with right angle at C. Prove: AC² = AB² + BC².",
    beta: "Given: Right-angled triangle ABC with right angle at C. Prove: AB² + BC² = AC² + BC².",
    charlie: "Given: Right-angled triangle ABC with right angle at C. Prove: AC * BC = AB.",
    delta: "Given: Right-angled triangle ABC with right angle at C. Prove: AC + BC = AB.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Right-angled triangle ABC with right angle at C. Prove: AC² = AB² + BC².",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 637,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the opposite angles of a parallelogram are equal.",
    alpha: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: ∠A = ∠C.",
    beta: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: ∠A + ∠B = ∠C + ∠D.",
    charlie: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: ∠A + ∠C = ∠B + ∠D.",
    delta: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: ∠A = ∠B.",
    correct_answer: "Given: ABCD is a parallelogram. Prove: ∠A = ∠C.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 638,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the medians of a triangle intersect at a point called the centroid.",
    alpha: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: The medians AD, BE, and CF intersect at a point G.",
    beta: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: The medians AD, BE, and CF are parallel.",
    charlie: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: The centroid is equidistant from all three vertices.",
    delta: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: The centroid is located at the midpoint of any median.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Triangle ABC. Prove: The medians AD, BE, and CF intersect at a point G.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 639,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the area of a triangle is equal to half the product of its base and height.",
    alpha: "Given: Triangle ABC with base BC. Prove: Area = 1/2 * BC * h.",
    beta: "Given: Triangle ABC with base BC. Prove: Area = BC * h.",
    charlie: "Given: Triangle ABC with base BC. Prove: Area = 2 * BC * h.",
    delta: "Given: Triangle ABC with base BC. Prove: Area = 1/3 * BC * h.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Triangle ABC with base BC. Prove: Area = 1/2 * BC * h.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 640,
    quiz_id: 64,
    question: "Prove that the sum of the angles of a convex polygon with n sides is (n-2) * 180 degrees.",
    alpha: "Given: Convex polygon with n sides. Prove: Sum of angles = (n-2) * 180°.",
    beta: "Given: Convex polygon with n sides. Prove: Sum of angles = n * 180°.",
    charlie: "Given: Convex polygon with n sides. Prove: Sum of angles = (n+2) * 180°.",
    delta: "Given: Convex polygon with n sides. Prove: Sum of angles = (n/2) * 180°.",
    correct_answer: "Given: Convex polygon with n sides. Prove: Sum of angles = (n-2) * 180°.",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 641,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Find the distance between the points A(1, 2, 3) and B(4, 5, 6).",
    alpha: "√2",
    beta: "√3",
    charlie: "√6",
    delta: "√9",
    correct_answer: "√14",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 642,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Given points P(2, -1, 3), Q(1, 4, -2), and R(-3, 2, 5), find the area of triangle PQR.",
    alpha: "√30",
    beta: "√35",
    charlie: "√40",
    delta: "√45",
    correct_answer: "√30",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 643,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Determine the equation of a plane passing through the points (1, -1, 2), (2, 1, -1), and (3, 3, 0).",
    alpha: "x - y + z = 0",
    beta: "2x + y - z = 5",
    charlie: "3x + y + 2z = 7",
    delta: "4x - y + 2z = 3",
    correct_answer: "2x + y - z = 5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 644,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Find the coordinates of the midpoint of the line segment joining points A(-1, 3, 2) and B(5, -2, 7).",
    alpha: "(2, 0.5, 4.5)",
    beta: "(2, 1, 5)",
    charlie: "(3, 0.5, 4.5)",
    delta: "(3, 1, 5)",
    correct_answer: "(2, 0.5, 4.5)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 645,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "If a line has direction ratios 2, -1, and 3, what is the direction cosine of the line?",
    alpha: "2/√14, -1/√14, 3/√14",
    beta: "2/√6, -1/√6, 3/√6",
    charlie: "2/√10, -1/√10, 3/√10",
    delta: "2/√7, -1/√7, 3/√7",
    correct_answer: "2/√14, -1/√14, 3/√14",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 646,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Find the volume of a parallelepiped with adjacent edges given by vectors i + 2j - k, 3i - j + 2k, and 2i + 3j + 4k.",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "15",
    delta: "20",
    correct_answer: "20",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 647,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Determine the shortest distance between the line x + 2 = y - 1 = z + 3 and the plane 2x - y + z = 4.",
    alpha: "√3",
    beta: "2√2",
    charlie: "√6",
    delta: "3√3",
    correct_answer: "√6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 648,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Given the points A(1, 2, -3), B(-2, 0, 1), and C(3, 1, 4), find the coordinates of the centroid of triangle ABC.",
    alpha: "(0, 1, 0)",
    beta: "(-1, 1, 2)",
    charlie: "(1, 1, 1)",
    delta: "(2, 1, 2)",
    correct_answer: "(0, 1, 0)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 649,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "If two vectors A and B are orthogonal (perpendicular) and |A| = 4, |B| = 5, find the magnitude of their cross product A × B.",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "20",
    delta: "10",
    correct_answer: "20",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 650,
    quiz_id: 65,
    question: "Determine the angle between the vectors i + j and 2i - j.",
    alpha: "30 degrees",
    beta: "45 degrees",
    charlie: "60 degrees",
    delta: "90 degrees",
    correct_answer: "45 degrees",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 651,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "What is the mean (average) of the following set of numbers: 10, 15, 20, 25, 30?",
    alpha: "18",
    beta: "20",
    charlie: "22",
    delta: "25",
    correct_answer: "20",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 652,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "Calculate the median of the dataset: 12, 18, 14, 20, 16, 22, 24.",
    alpha: "16",
    beta: "18",
    charlie: "20",
    delta: "22",
    correct_answer: "18",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 653,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "If the range of a dataset is 15 and the minimum value is 10, what is the maximum value?",
    alpha: "15",
    beta: "20",
    charlie: "25",
    delta: "30",
    correct_answer: "25",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 654,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "Find the mode of the following set: 7, 8, 5, 7, 5, 9, 7.",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "7",
    charlie: "8",
    delta: "9",
    correct_answer: "7",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 655,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "If the standard deviation of a dataset is 5, what is the variance?",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "15",
    delta: "25",
    correct_answer: "25",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 656,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "Calculate the interquartile range (IQR) for the dataset: 10, 12, 15, 18, 22, 25, 28.",
    alpha: "8",
    beta: "12",
    charlie: "15",
    delta: "18",
    correct_answer: "15",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 657,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "If the data points are 12, 14, 18, 20, 22, what is the sum of the squared deviations from the mean?",
    alpha: "8",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "12",
    delta: "14",
    correct_answer: "40",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 658,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "Find the coefficient of variation (CV) for a dataset with a mean of 25 and a standard deviation of 5.",
    alpha: "10%",
    beta: "15%",
    charlie: "20%",
    delta: "25%",
    correct_answer: "20%",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 659,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "Calculate the mean absolute deviation (MAD) for the dataset: 5, 8, 10, 12, 15.",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "3",
    charlie: "4",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 660,
    quiz_id: 66,
    question: "If the first quartile (Q1) is 15 and the third quartile (Q3) is 25, what is the semi-interquartile range (SIQR)?",
    alpha: "5",
    beta: "10",
    charlie: "15",
    delta: "20",
    correct_answer: "5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 661,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "In a standard six-sided die, what is the probability of rolling an even number?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "1/3",
    charlie: "1/4",
    delta: "1/6",
    correct_answer: "1/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 662,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "A bag contains 5 red balls, 3 blue balls, and 2 green balls. What is the probability of drawing a blue ball?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "3/10",
    charlie: "1/3",
    delta: "2/5",
    correct_answer: "3/10",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 663,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "If P(A) = 0.4 and P(B) = 0.3, what is the probability of both events A and B occurring?",
    alpha: "0.7",
    beta: "0.12",
    charlie: "0.15",
    delta: "0.2",
    correct_answer: "0.12",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 664,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "A card is drawn from a standard deck. What is the probability of drawing a heart or a spade?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "1/3",
    charlie: "1/4",
    delta: "1/5",
    correct_answer: "1/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 665,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "If P(A) = 0.6 and P(B) = 0.5, what is the probability of either event A or event B occurring?",
    alpha: "0.8",
    beta: "0.7",
    charlie: "0.6",
    delta: "0.5",
    correct_answer: "0.8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 666,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "The probability distribution of a discrete random variable X is given by P(X = 1) = 0.2, P(X = 2) = 0.5, P(X = 3) = 0.3. What is the expected value of X?",
    alpha: "1.5",
    beta: "2.0",
    charlie: "2.5",
    delta: "3.0",
    correct_answer: "2.0",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 667,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "If the mean of a probability distribution is 4 and the standard deviation is 2, what is the variance?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "4",
    charlie: "6",
    delta: "8",
    correct_answer: "4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 668,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "The probability density function (PDF) of a continuous random variable X is given by f(x) = kx for 0 ≤ x ≤ 2 and f(x) = 0 otherwise. What is the value of the constant k?",
    alpha: "1/2",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "2/3",
    delta: "3/2",
    correct_answer: "1/2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 669,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "A fair six-sided die is rolled twice. What is the probability of getting a sum of 7 on the two rolls?",
    alpha: "1/6",
    beta: "1/12",
    charlie: "1/8",
    delta: "1/36",
    correct_answer: "1/6",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 670,
    quiz_id: 67,
    question: "The binomial probability distribution is characterized by two parameters. What are these parameters?",
    alpha: "Mean and Variance",
    beta: "Mean and Standard Deviation",
    charlie: "Success Probability and Number of Trials",
    delta: "Success Probability and Standard Deviation",
    correct_answer: "Success Probability and Number of Trials",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 671,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is the purpose of statistical inference in data analysis?",
    alpha: "To summarize and describe data",
    beta: "To make predictions about future data",
    charlie: "To draw conclusions about a population based on a sample",
    delta: "To calculate probabilities of random events",
    correct_answer: "To draw conclusions about a population based on a sample",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 672,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "In hypothesis testing, what is the null hypothesis?",
    alpha: "The hypothesis we want to prove",
    beta: "The opposite of the research hypothesis",
    charlie: "A statement that there is no effect or difference",
    delta: "A statement that supports the research hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "A statement that there is no effect or difference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 673,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is the p-value in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "The probability of rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "The probability of accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "The probability of obtaining the observed data or more extreme if the null hypothesis is true",
    delta: "The probability of obtaining the null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "The probability of obtaining the observed data or more extreme if the null hypothesis is true",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 674,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "In a confidence interval, what does a 95% confidence level mean?",
    alpha: "There is a 95% probability that the parameter is in the interval",
    beta: "There is a 95% probability that the sample mean is in the interval",
    charlie: "If we were to take many samples, 95% of the intervals would contain the true parameter",
    delta: "The interval contains 95% of the data",
    correct_answer: "If we were to take many samples, 95% of the intervals would contain the true parameter",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 675,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is Type I error in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "Rejecting a false null hypothesis",
    delta: "Accepting a true null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 676,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is Type II error in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "Rejecting a false null hypothesis",
    delta: "Accepting a true null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 677,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "In regression analysis, what does the coefficient of determination (R-squared) measure?",
    alpha: "The strength of the relationship between the variables",
    beta: "The slope of the regression line",
    charlie: "The proportion of the variance in the dependent variable explained by the independent variable",
    delta: "The standard error of the regression",
    correct_answer: "The proportion of the variance in the dependent variable explained by the independent variable",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 678,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is the purpose of a t-test in statistical inference?",
    alpha: "To test the equality of variances",
    beta: "To compare means of two groups",
    charlie: "To assess the normality of the data",
    delta: "To analyze the relationship between two variables",
    correct_answer: "To compare means of two groups",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 679,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "In Bayesian inference, what is a prior probability?",
    alpha: "The probability of the observed data given the parameter",
    beta: "The probability assigned to a parameter before observing the data",
    charlie: "The probability of obtaining a specific test statistic",
    delta: "The probability of a Type I error",
    correct_answer: "The probability assigned to a parameter before observing the data",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 680,
    quiz_id: 68,
    question: "What is the Central Limit Theorem in statistical inference?",
    alpha: "A theorem about the normal distribution",
    beta: "A theorem about the sampling distribution of the sample mean",
    charlie: "A theorem about the correlation between two variables",
    delta: "A theorem about the variability in a dataset",
    correct_answer: "A theorem about the sampling distribution of the sample mean",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 681,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "In simple linear regression, what is the purpose of the regression line?",
    alpha: "To predict the dependent variable based on the independent variable",
    beta: "To connect data points in a scatter plot",
    charlie: "To calculate the mean of the dependent variable",
    delta: "To test the normality of the data",
    correct_answer: "To predict the dependent variable based on the independent variable",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 682,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is the coefficient of determination (R-squared) in multiple linear regression?",
    alpha: "The slope of the regression line",
    beta: "The proportion of the variance in the dependent variable explained by the independent variables",
    charlie: "The standard deviation of the residuals",
    delta: "The p-value for the regression model",
    correct_answer: "The proportion of the variance in the dependent variable explained by the independent variables",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 683,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "In logistic regression, what type of variable is the dependent variable?",
    alpha: "Continuous",
    beta: "Categorical",
    charlie: "Ordinal",
    delta: "Nominal",
    correct_answer: "Categorical",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 684,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is the purpose of the residual plot in regression analysis?",
    alpha: "To check for multicollinearity",
    beta: "To assess the normality of the residuals",
    charlie: "To identify influential data points",
    delta: "To test the equality of variances",
    correct_answer: "To assess the normality of the residuals",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 685,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "In regression analysis, what does multicollinearity refer to?",
    alpha: "The presence of outliers in the data",
    beta: "High correlation among independent variables",
    charlie: "Non-linearity in the relationship between variables",
    delta: "The absence of a significant relationship between variables",
    correct_answer: "High correlation among independent variables",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 686,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is heteroscedasticity in regression analysis?",
    alpha: "The presence of outliers in the data",
    beta: "The violation of the normality assumption",
    charlie: "Unequal variance of residuals across levels of the independent variable",
    delta: "The absence of a significant relationship between variables",
    correct_answer: "Unequal variance of residuals across levels of the independent variable",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 687,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is the difference between simple linear regression and multiple linear regression?",
    alpha: "The number of data points",
    beta: "The number of independent variables",
    charlie: "The number of dependent variables",
    delta: "The type of variables involved",
    correct_answer: "The number of independent variables",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 688,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "In regression analysis, what is the purpose of stepwise regression?",
    alpha: "To assess the normality of the residuals",
    beta: "To select the most important variables for the model",
    charlie: "To calculate the coefficient of determination",
    delta: "To test the equality of variances",
    correct_answer: "To select the most important variables for the model",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 689,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is the difference between correlation and regression analysis?",
    alpha: "Correlation measures the strength of a linear relationship; regression predicts one variable from another",
    beta: "Regression measures the strength of a linear relationship; correlation predicts one variable from another",
    charlie: "Both correlation and regression measure the strength of a linear relationship",
    delta: "Neither correlation nor regression measures the strength of a linear relationship",
    correct_answer: "Correlation measures the strength of a linear relationship; regression predicts one variable from another",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 690,
    quiz_id: 69,
    question: "What is the purpose of residual analysis in regression?",
    alpha: "To assess the normality of the residuals",
    beta: "To test the equality of variances",
    charlie: "To identify influential data points",
    delta: "To check for multicollinearity",
    correct_answer: "To assess the normality of the residuals",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 691,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is the purpose of hypothesis testing in statistics?",
    alpha: "To describe and summarize data",
    beta: "To make predictions about future data",
    charlie: "To draw conclusions about a population based on a sample",
    delta: "To identify patterns in the data",
    correct_answer: "To draw conclusions about a population based on a sample",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 692,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is the null hypothesis in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "The hypothesis we want to prove",
    beta: "The opposite of the research hypothesis",
    charlie: "A statement that there is no effect or difference",
    delta: "A statement that supports the research hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "A statement that there is no effect or difference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 693,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "In a hypothesis test, what is the p-value?",
    alpha: "The probability of rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "The probability of accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "The probability of obtaining the observed data or more extreme if the null hypothesis is true",
    delta: "The probability of obtaining the null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "The probability of obtaining the observed data or more extreme if the null hypothesis is true",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 694,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is Type I error in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "Rejecting a false null hypothesis",
    delta: "Accepting a true null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 695,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is Type II error in hypothesis testing?",
    alpha: "Rejecting a true null hypothesis",
    beta: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    charlie: "Rejecting a false null hypothesis",
    delta: "Accepting a true null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "Accepting a false null hypothesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 696,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "In hypothesis testing, what is the significance level (α)?",
    alpha: "The probability of Type II error",
    beta: "The probability of Type I error",
    charlie: "The level of confidence in the test results",
    delta: "The probability of obtaining a significant result",
    correct_answer: "The probability of Type I error",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 697,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is the critical region in a hypothesis test?",
    alpha: "The region where the null hypothesis is true",
    beta: "The region where the alternative hypothesis is true",
    charlie: "The region of extreme sample values that leads to the rejection of the null hypothesis",
    delta: "The region of non-extreme sample values that supports the null hypothesis",
    correct_answer: "The region of extreme sample values that leads to the rejection of the null hypothesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 698,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is a one-tailed (one-sided) hypothesis test?",
    alpha: "A test where the critical region is on one side of the distribution",
    beta: "A test with a significance level of 1%",
    charlie: "A test with a Type I error rate of 1%",
    delta: "A test with a Type II error rate of 1%",
    correct_answer: "A test where the critical region is on one side of the distribution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 699,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is a two-tailed (two-sided) hypothesis test?",
    alpha: "A test where the critical region is on both sides of the distribution",
    beta: "A test with a significance level of 2%",
    charlie: "A test with a Type I error rate of 2%",
    delta: "A test with a Type II error rate of 2%",
    correct_answer: "A test where the critical region is on both sides of the distribution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 700,
    quiz_id: 70,
    question: "What is the power of a statistical test?",
    alpha: "The probability of Type I error",
    beta: "The probability of Type II error",
    charlie: "The probability of obtaining a significant result when the alternative hypothesis is true",
    delta: "The probability of obtaining a non-significant result when the null hypothesis is true",
    correct_answer: "The probability of obtaining a significant result when the alternative hypothesis is true",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 701,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is a prime number?",
    alpha: "A number divisible by 2",
    beta: "A natural number greater than 1 with no positive divisors other than 1 and itself",
    charlie: "A number divisible by 1",
    delta: "A number divisible by 10",
    correct_answer: "A natural number greater than 1 with no positive divisors other than 1 and itself",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 702,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the smallest prime number?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "2",
    delta: "3",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 703,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "Is 1 a prime number?",
    alpha: "Yes",
    beta: "No",
    charlie: "Sometimes",
    delta: "Not sure",
    correct_answer: "No",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 704,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the prime factorization of 24?",
    alpha: "2^2 * 3",
    beta: "2 * 3^2",
    charlie: "2^3 * 3",
    delta: "2^2 * 3^2",
    correct_answer: "2^3 * 3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 705,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "How many prime numbers are there between 1 and 20?",
    alpha: "7",
    beta: "8",
    charlie: "9",
    delta: "10",
    correct_answer: "8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 706,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the sum of the first 5 prime numbers?",
    alpha: "15",
    beta: "20",
    charlie: "22",
    delta: "28",
    correct_answer: "28",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 707,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the largest known prime number?",
    alpha: "2^82589933 - 1",
    beta: "2^74207281 - 1",
    charlie: "2^57885161 - 1",
    delta: "2^43112609 - 1",
    correct_answer: "2^82589933 - 1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 708,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "Is 27 a prime number?",
    alpha: "Yes",
    beta: "No",
    charlie: "Sometimes",
    delta: "Not sure",
    correct_answer: "No",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 709,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the next prime number after 79?",
    alpha: "81",
    beta: "83",
    charlie: "85",
    delta: "87",
    correct_answer: "83",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 710,
    quiz_id: 71,
    question: "What is the product of the first 3 prime numbers?",
    alpha: "2 * 3 * 5",
    beta: "3 * 5 * 7",
    charlie: "2 * 3 * 7",
    delta: "5 * 7 * 11",
    correct_answer: "2 * 3 * 5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 711,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What does it mean for one integer to be divisible by another?",
    alpha: "Their sum is a multiple of the divisor",
    beta: "The remainder of their division is zero",
    charlie: "Their product is a multiple of the divisor",
    delta: "Their difference is a multiple of the divisor",
    correct_answer: "The remainder of their division is zero",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 712,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "If a number is divisible by both 3 and 5, what is it also divisible by?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "7",
    charlie: "15",
    delta: "8",
    correct_answer: "15",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 713,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the divisibility rule for 4?",
    alpha: "The sum of the digits is divisible by 4",
    beta: "The last two digits form a multiple of 4",
    charlie: "The product of the digits is divisible by 4",
    delta: "The number itself is divisible by 4",
    correct_answer: "The last two digits form a multiple of 4",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 714,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the smallest positive integer that is a multiple of both 6 and 8?",
    alpha: "12",
    beta: "16",
    charlie: "18",
    delta: "24",
    correct_answer: "24",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 715,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the remainder when 37 is divided by 5?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 716,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "If a number leaves a remainder of 3 when divided by 7, what is its remainder when divided by 14?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "2",
    delta: "3",
    correct_answer: "3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 717,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the modular arithmetic notation for '15 is congruent to 3 (mod 4)'?",
    alpha: "15 ≡ 3 (mod 4)",
    beta: "15 ≡ 1 (mod 4)",
    charlie: "15 ≡ 0 (mod 4)",
    delta: "15 ≡ 2 (mod 4)",
    correct_answer: "15 ≡ 3 (mod 4)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 718,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the value of 2^5 (mod 7)?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 719,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "If a ≡ b (mod m), what can be said about a^2 and b^2 (mod m)?",
    alpha: "a^2 ≡ b^2 (mod m)",
    beta: "a^2 + b^2 ≡ 0 (mod m)",
    charlie: "a^2 + b^2 ≡ 1 (mod m)",
    delta: "No conclusion can be drawn",
    correct_answer: "a^2 ≡ b^2 (mod m)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 720,
    quiz_id: 72,
    question: "What is the Chinese Remainder Theorem used for in modular arithmetic?",
    alpha: "Finding prime numbers",
    beta: "Solving systems of linear congruences",
    charlie: "Calculating modular inverses",
    delta: "Determining perfect squares",
    correct_answer: "Solving systems of linear congruences",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 721,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is a Diophantine equation?",
    alpha: "An equation involving only integers",
    beta: "An equation involving only real numbers",
    charlie: "An equation involving only irrational numbers",
    delta: "An equation involving only complex numbers",
    correct_answer: "An equation involving only integers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 722,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a Diophantine equation?",
    alpha: "y = 2x + 1",
    beta: "3x + 5y = 7",
    charlie: "sin(x) + cos(x) = 1",
    delta: "log(x) = 2",
    correct_answer: "3x + 5y = 7",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 723,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the solution to the Diophantine equation 5x + 3y = 1?",
    alpha: "(2, -3)",
    beta: "(-1, 2)",
    charlie: "(1, 0)",
    delta: "(0, 1)",
    correct_answer: "(-1, 2)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 724,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the solution to the Diophantine equation 4x - 6y = 2?",
    alpha: "(1, 1)",
    beta: "(2, 0)",
    charlie: "(3, -1)",
    delta: "(-1, -1)",
    correct_answer: "(3, -1)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 725,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "Which Diophantine equation represents a Pythagorean triple?",
    alpha: "x^2 + y^2 = z^2",
    beta: "2x + 3y = 5z",
    charlie: "3x - 4y = 7",
    delta: "sin(x) + cos(y) = 1",
    correct_answer: "x^2 + y^2 = z^2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 726,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the solution to the Diophantine equation 7x + 5y = 1?",
    alpha: "(2, -3)",
    beta: "(1, -2)",
    charlie: "(3, -2)",
    delta: "(2, -1)",
    correct_answer: "(3, -2)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 727,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the general form of a linear Diophantine equation in two variables (ax + by = c) if it has a solution?",
    alpha: "gcd(a, b) divides c",
    beta: "gcd(a, b) is divisible by c",
    charlie: "gcd(a, b) is prime",
    delta: "c is a prime number",
    correct_answer: "gcd(a, b) divides c",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 728,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "Which method is commonly used to find solutions to linear Diophantine equations?",
    alpha: "Graphing",
    beta: "Integration",
    charlie: "Modular arithmetic",
    delta: "Differentiation",
    correct_answer: "Modular arithmetic",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 729,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the solution to the Diophantine equation 6x + 9y = 15?",
    alpha: "(1, 1)",
    beta: "(2, 1)",
    charlie: "(3, 1)",
    delta: "(4, 0)",
    correct_answer: "(3, 1)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 730,
    quiz_id: 73,
    question: "What is the solution to the Diophantine equation 8x - 12y = 4?",
    alpha: "(1, 1)",
    beta: "(2, 0)",
    charlie: "(3, -1)",
    delta: "(-1, -1)",
    correct_answer: "(2, 1)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 731,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is a congruence in modular arithmetic?",
    alpha: "An equality between two integers",
    beta: "An inequality between two integers",
    charlie: "A relation between two integers that have the same remainder when divided by a given modulus",
    delta: "A relation between two integers that have different remainders when divided by a given modulus",
    correct_answer: "A relation between two integers that have the same remainder when divided by a given modulus",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 732,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What does 'a ≡ b (mod m)' mean?",
    alpha: "a is equal to b",
    beta: "a is congruent to b modulo m",
    charlie: "a is divisible by m",
    delta: "a is the remainder when b is divided by m",
    correct_answer: "a is congruent to b modulo m",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 733,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the smallest positive residue of -27 modulo 5?",
    alpha: "0",
    beta: "1",
    charlie: "2",
    delta: "3",
    correct_answer: "3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 734,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "If a ≡ b (mod m), what can be said about a + c and b + c (mod m)?",
    alpha: "a + c ≡ b + c (mod m)",
    beta: "a + c ≡ b (mod m)",
    charlie: "a + c ≡ c (mod m)",
    delta: "No conclusion can be drawn",
    correct_answer: "a + c ≡ b + c (mod m)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 735,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the inverse of 3 modulo 7?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "5",
    correct_answer: "5",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 736,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "If a ≡ b (mod m), what can be said about ac and bc (mod m)?",
    alpha: "ac ≡ bc (mod m)",
    beta: "ac ≡ b (mod m)",
    charlie: "ac ≡ c (mod m)",
    delta: "No conclusion can be drawn",
    correct_answer: "ac ≡ bc (mod m)",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 737,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the solution to the congruence 2x ≡ 1 (mod 5)?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "3",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 738,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the solution to the congruence 4x ≡ 3 (mod 7)?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 739,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the product of the residues of the numbers 1 to 6 modulo 7?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 740,
    quiz_id: 74,
    question: "What is the solution to the congruence 5x ≡ 2 (mod 9)?",
    alpha: "1",
    beta: "2",
    charlie: "3",
    delta: "4",
    correct_answer: "8",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 741,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is the main goal of cryptography?",
    alpha: "To ensure data integrity",
    beta: "To secure communication and data from unauthorized access",
    charlie: "To compress data for efficient storage",
    delta: "To improve data transfer speed",
    correct_answer: "To secure communication and data from unauthorized access",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 742,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is a key in cryptography?",
    alpha: "A secret code used for encryption",
    beta: "A public code used for decryption",
    charlie: "A piece of hardware used for encryption",
    delta: "A mathematical function used for decryption",
    correct_answer: "A secret code used for encryption",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 743,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is symmetric key cryptography?",
    alpha: "A system using the same key for both encryption and decryption",
    beta: "A system using different keys for encryption and decryption",
    charlie: "A system using a combination of keys for encryption",
    delta: "A system without the use of keys",
    correct_answer: "A system using the same key for both encryption and decryption",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 744,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "Which encryption algorithm is widely used for secure data transmission over the internet?",
    alpha: "MD5",
    beta: "SHA-256",
    charlie: "RSA",
    delta: "AES",
    correct_answer: "AES",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 745,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is public key cryptography?",
    alpha: "A system using the same key for both encryption and decryption",
    beta: "A system using different keys for encryption and decryption",
    charlie: "A system using a combination of keys for encryption",
    delta: "A system without the use of keys",
    correct_answer: "A system using different keys for encryption and decryption",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 746,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is the Diffie-Hellman key exchange used for?",
    alpha: "Digital signatures",
    beta: "Symmetric key exchange",
    charlie: "Public key exchange",
    delta: "Secure communication over an insecure channel",
    correct_answer: "Public key exchange",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 747,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is a digital signature in cryptography?",
    alpha: "A secret code used for encryption",
    beta: "A technique to verify the authenticity of a message or document",
    charlie: "A method of compressing data",
    delta: "A symmetric key used for decryption",
    correct_answer: "A technique to verify the authenticity of a message or document",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 748,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is the purpose of a hash function in cryptography?",
    alpha: "To encrypt data",
    beta: "To generate a digital signature",
    charlie: "To verify the integrity of data",
    delta: "To exchange symmetric keys",
    correct_answer: "To verify the integrity of data",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 749,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "What is the concept of a 'man-in-the-middle' attack in cryptography?",
    alpha: "An attack on a physical location where cryptographic keys are stored",
    beta: "An attack involving the interception and alteration of communication between two parties",
    charlie: "An attack on a cryptographic algorithm",
    delta: "An attack using brute force to break encryption",
    correct_answer: "An attack involving the interception and alteration of communication between two parties",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 750,
    quiz_id: 75,
    question: "Which cryptographic algorithm is commonly used for digital signatures and public key encryption?",
    alpha: "AES",
    beta: "RSA",
    charlie: "DES",
    delta: "Blowfish",
    correct_answer: "RSA",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 751,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "What is the basic structural and functional unit of life?",
    alpha: "Atom",
    beta: "Cell",
    charlie: "Molecule",
    delta: "Organism",
    correct_answer: "Cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 752,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "Which organelle is responsible for producing energy in a cell?",
    alpha: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    beta: "Mitochondrion",
    charlie: "Golgi apparatus",
    delta: "Nucleus",
    correct_answer: "Mitochondrion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 753,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "What is the function of the Golgi apparatus?",
    alpha: "Protein synthesis",
    beta: "Energy production",
    charlie: "Cellular respiration",
    delta: "Modifying and packaging proteins",
    correct_answer: "Modifying and packaging proteins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 754,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "Which structure contains the genetic material (DNA) in a eukaryotic cell?",
    alpha: "Nucleus",
    beta: "Ribosome",
    charlie: "Cell membrane",
    delta: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    correct_answer: "Nucleus",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 755,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "What is the main function of the cell membrane?",
    alpha: "Energy production",
    beta: "Regulating the passage of substances into and out of the cell",
    charlie: "Protein synthesis",
    delta: "Storage of genetic material",
    correct_answer: "Regulating the passage of substances into and out of the cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 756,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "Which organelle is responsible for detoxifying harmful substances in the cell?",
    alpha: "Lysosome",
    beta: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    charlie: "Peroxisome",
    delta: "Vacuole",
    correct_answer: "Peroxisome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 757,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "What is the function of the endoplasmic reticulum?",
    alpha: "Protein synthesis",
    beta: "Lipid synthesis",
    charlie: "Carbohydrate synthesis",
    delta: "Energy production",
    correct_answer: "Lipid synthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 758,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "Which cellular structure is responsible for breaking down and recycling cellular waste?",
    alpha: "Lysosome",
    beta: "Nucleus",
    charlie: "Centriole",
    delta: "Ribosome",
    correct_answer: "Lysosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 759,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "What is the primary function of chloroplasts in plant cells?",
    alpha: "Cellular respiration",
    beta: "Photosynthesis",
    charlie: "Protein synthesis",
    delta: "Lipid synthesis",
    correct_answer: "Photosynthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 760,
    quiz_id: 76,
    question: "Which structure is responsible for providing structural support and shape to the cell?",
    alpha: "Nucleus",
    beta: "Cell membrane",
    charlie: "Cytoskeleton",
    delta: "Golgi apparatus",
    correct_answer: "Cytoskeleton",
    selected_option: null,
  }, {
    question_id: 761,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the process by which cells obtain energy from nutrients?",
    alpha: "Photosynthesis",
    beta: "Cellular respiration",
    charlie: "Glycolysis",
    delta: "Mitosis",
    correct_answer: "Cellular respiration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 762,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "During which phase of the cell cycle does DNA replication occur?",
    alpha: "G1 phase",
    beta: "S phase",
    charlie: "G2 phase",
    delta: "M phase",
    correct_answer: "S phase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 763,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the main function of the process of mitosis?",
    alpha: "Cell division and growth",
    beta: "Production of gametes",
    charlie: "Genetic recombination",
    delta: "Energy production",
    correct_answer: "Cell division and growth",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 764,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the purpose of meiosis in sexual reproduction?",
    alpha: "Cell division and growth",
    beta: "Production of genetically identical cells",
    charlie: "Production of gametes with genetic variation",
    delta: "Energy production",
    correct_answer: "Production of gametes with genetic variation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 765,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "During which stage of cellular respiration does the majority of ATP production occur?",
    alpha: "Glycolysis",
    beta: "Citric acid cycle",
    charlie: "Electron transport chain",
    delta: "Pyruvate oxidation",
    correct_answer: "Electron transport chain",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 766,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the primary function of the cell cycle checkpoint in G1 phase?",
    alpha: "Monitoring DNA replication",
    beta: "Checking for DNA damage",
    charlie: "Ensuring sufficient energy for cell division",
    delta: "Initiating apoptosis",
    correct_answer: "Checking for DNA damage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 767,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the role of tRNA in protein synthesis?",
    alpha: "Transcribing DNA into RNA",
    beta: "Carrying amino acids to the ribosome",
    charlie: "Reading the genetic code",
    delta: "Initiating translation",
    correct_answer: "Carrying amino acids to the ribosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 768,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "In which organelle does protein synthesis occur?",
    alpha: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    beta: "Mitochondrion",
    charlie: "Nucleus",
    delta: "Ribosome",
    correct_answer: "Ribosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 769,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the process of breaking down glucose to produce ATP without the use of oxygen?",
    alpha: "Photosynthesis",
    beta: "Glycolysis",
    charlie: "Cellular respiration",
    delta: "Fermentation",
    correct_answer: "Fermentation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 770,
    quiz_id: 77,
    question: "What is the primary role of the enzyme DNA polymerase during DNA replication?",
    alpha: "Unzipping the DNA double helix",
    beta: "Joining Okazaki fragments",
    charlie: "Reading the genetic code",
    delta: "Synthesizing a new strand of DNA",
    correct_answer: "Synthesizing a new strand of DNA",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 771,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is the process by which a single cell divides into two daughter cells?",
    alpha: "Meiosis",
    beta: "Mitosis",
    charlie: "Glycolysis",
    delta: "Photosynthesis",
    correct_answer: "Mitosis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 772,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "During which phase of the cell cycle does mitosis occur?",
    alpha: "G1 phase",
    beta: "S phase",
    charlie: "G2 phase",
    delta: "M phase",
    correct_answer: "M phase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 773,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is the purpose of the cell cycle?",
    alpha: "Cellular respiration",
    beta: "Growth and repair of tissues",
    charlie: "Protein synthesis",
    delta: "DNA replication",
    correct_answer: "Growth and repair of tissues",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 774,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "Which phase of the cell cycle involves the synthesis of DNA?",
    alpha: "G1 phase",
    beta: "S phase",
    charlie: "G2 phase",
    delta: "M phase",
    correct_answer: "S phase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 775,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is the purpose of the G2 phase in the cell cycle?",
    alpha: "DNA replication",
    beta: "Preparation for cell division",
    charlie: "Growth and metabolic activities",
    delta: "Cellular respiration",
    correct_answer: "Preparation for cell division",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 776,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "During which stage of mitosis do chromosomes align at the cell's equator?",
    alpha: "Prophase",
    beta: "Metaphase",
    charlie: "Anaphase",
    delta: "Telophase",
    correct_answer: "Metaphase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 777,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is the result of mitosis?",
    alpha: "Two identical daughter cells",
    beta: "Four non-identical daughter cells",
    charlie: "One identical daughter cell",
    delta: "No daughter cells",
    correct_answer: "Two identical daughter cells",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 778,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is cytokinesis?",
    alpha: "Division of the cell's cytoplasm",
    beta: "Division of the cell's nucleus",
    charlie: "Synthesis of DNA",
    delta: "Formation of spindle fibers",
    correct_answer: "Division of the cell's cytoplasm",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 779,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "In which type of cells does meiosis occur?",
    alpha: "Somatic cells",
    beta: "Gamete cells",
    charlie: "Liver cells",
    delta: "Skin cells",
    correct_answer: "Gamete cells",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 780,
    quiz_id: 78,
    question: "What is the purpose of meiosis?",
    alpha: "Growth and repair",
    beta: "Production of genetically identical cells",
    charlie: "Production of gametes with genetic variation",
    delta: "DNA replication",
    correct_answer: "Production of gametes with genetic variation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 781,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is cell signaling?",
    alpha: "The process of cell division",
    beta: "Communication between cells",
    charlie: "Energy production in cells",
    delta: "Cellular respiration",
    correct_answer: "Communication between cells",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 782,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "Which molecules are commonly involved in cell signaling?",
    alpha: "Lipids",
    beta: "Nucleic acids",
    charlie: "Proteins",
    delta: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "All of the above",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 783,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is a ligand in the context of cell signaling?",
    alpha: "A type of cell membrane",
    beta: "A signaling molecule that binds to a receptor",
    charlie: "A type of cell organelle",
    delta: "A cellular enzyme",
    correct_answer: "A signaling molecule that binds to a receptor",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 784,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is the purpose of a receptor in cell signaling?",
    alpha: "Energy production",
    beta: "To transduce the signal",
    charlie: "Cell division",
    delta: "DNA replication",
    correct_answer: "To transduce the signal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 785,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "Which type of cell signaling involves direct physical contact between cells?",
    alpha: "Endocrine signaling",
    beta: "Paracrine signaling",
    charlie: "Autocrine signaling",
    delta: "Contact-dependent signaling",
    correct_answer: "Contact-dependent signaling",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 786,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is the primary function of second messengers in cell signaling?",
    alpha: "Transducing the signal inside the cell",
    beta: "Binding to the ligand",
    charlie: "Acting as the ligand",
    delta: "Initiating cell division",
    correct_answer: "Transducing the signal inside the cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 787,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of intracellular receptors?",
    alpha: "G protein-coupled receptors",
    beta: "Tyrosine kinase receptors",
    charlie: "Steroid receptors",
    delta: "Ion channel receptors",
    correct_answer: "Steroid receptors",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 788,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is the role of G proteins in signal transduction?",
    alpha: "Initiating apoptosis",
    beta: "Transducing the signal to the cell interior",
    charlie: "Acting as second messengers",
    delta: "Binding to ligands",
    correct_answer: "Transducing the signal to the cell interior",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 789,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "What is apoptosis?",
    alpha: "Cell division",
    beta: "Cellular respiration",
    charlie: "Programmed cell death",
    delta: "DNA replication",
    correct_answer: "Programmed cell death",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 790,
    quiz_id: 79,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a signal transduction pathway?",
    alpha: "Cellular respiration",
    beta: "Cell division",
    charlie: "Mitosis",
    delta: "MAP kinase pathway",
    correct_answer: "MAP kinase pathway",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 791,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of cellular respiration?",
    alpha: "Energy production",
    beta: "DNA replication",
    charlie: "Protein synthesis",
    delta: "Cell division",
    correct_answer: "Energy production",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 792,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "During which phase of cellular respiration does glucose get broken down into pyruvate?",
    alpha: "Glycolysis",
    beta: "Citric acid cycle",
    charlie: "Electron transport chain",
    delta: "Oxidative phosphorylation",
    correct_answer: "Glycolysis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 793,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "Where does the citric acid cycle (Krebs cycle) take place in the cell?",
    alpha: "Mitochondrial matrix",
    beta: "Cytoplasm",
    charlie: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    delta: "Nucleus",
    correct_answer: "Mitochondrial matrix",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 794,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "What is the final electron acceptor in the electron transport chain of cellular respiration?",
    alpha: "Oxygen",
    beta: "Carbon dioxide",
    charlie: "Water",
    delta: "Glucose",
    correct_answer: "Oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 795,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "How many ATP molecules are produced per glucose molecule in cellular respiration?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "4",
    charlie: "36",
    delta: "38",
    correct_answer: "38",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 796,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "What is the main product of glycolysis?",
    alpha: "ATP",
    beta: "Pyruvate",
    charlie: "Carbon dioxide",
    delta: "NADH",
    correct_answer: "Pyruvate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 797,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "In which cellular organelle does oxidative phosphorylation occur?",
    alpha: "Mitochondrion",
    beta: "Nucleus",
    charlie: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    delta: "Golgi apparatus",
    correct_answer: "Mitochondrion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 798,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "What is the net gain of ATP molecules in glycolysis?",
    alpha: "2",
    beta: "4",
    charlie: "6",
    delta: "8",
    correct_answer: "2",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 799,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "Which molecule is produced in the highest quantity during the citric acid cycle?",
    alpha: "ATP",
    beta: "NADH",
    charlie: "FADH2",
    delta: "Carbon dioxide",
    correct_answer: "Carbon dioxide",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 800,
    quiz_id: 80,
    question: "What is the function of NADH in cellular respiration?",
    alpha: "To produce ATP",
    beta: "To donate electrons in the electron transport chain",
    charlie: "To store energy",
    delta: "To transport oxygen",
    correct_answer: "To donate electrons in the electron transport chain",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 801,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "Who is considered the father of modern genetics?",
    alpha: "Charles Darwin",
    beta: "Gregor Mendel",
    charlie: "Watson and Crick",
    delta: "Alfred Wallace",
    correct_answer: "Gregor Mendel",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 802,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "What are Mendel's factors that determine traits now known as?",
    alpha: "Genes",
    beta: "Alleles",
    charlie: "Chromosomes",
    delta: "DNA",
    correct_answer: "Genes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 803,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "In Mendel's experiments, what is the term for the trait that masked the presence of the other trait?",
    alpha: "Dominant",
    beta: "Recessive",
    charlie: "Homozygous",
    delta: "Heterozygous",
    correct_answer: "Dominant",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 804,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "If an individual has two different alleles for a particular gene, they are said to be:",
    alpha: "Homozygous dominant",
    beta: "Homozygous recessive",
    charlie: "Heterozygous",
    delta: "Monohybrid",
    correct_answer: "Heterozygous",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 805,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "What is the Punnett square used for in genetics?",
    alpha: "To calculate the probability of offspring genotypes",
    beta: "To determine phenotypes",
    charlie: "To identify dominant traits",
    delta: "To study recessive alleles",
    correct_answer: "To calculate the probability of offspring genotypes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 806,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "If an organism has two identical alleles for a particular gene, they are said to be:",
    alpha: "Homozygous dominant",
    beta: "Homozygous recessive",
    charlie: "Heterozygous",
    delta: "Monohybrid",
    correct_answer: "Homozygous dominant",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 807,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "What is the phenotype of an organism?",
    alpha: "Its genetic makeup",
    beta: "Its observable traits",
    charlie: "Its dominant alleles",
    delta: "Its recessive alleles",
    correct_answer: "Its observable traits",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 808,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "What is the ratio of phenotypes in the F2 generation of a dihybrid cross between individuals heterozygous for both traits?",
    alpha: "1:1",
    beta: "1:2:1",
    charlie: "9:3:3:1",
    delta: "3:1",
    correct_answer: "9:3:3:1",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 809,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "In Mendel's experiments with pea plants, what trait is an example of incomplete dominance?",
    alpha: "Flower color",
    beta: "Seed shape",
    charlie: "Pod color",
    delta: "Height",
    correct_answer: "Flower color",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 810,
    quiz_id: 81,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where one gene affects multiple traits?",
    alpha: "Incomplete dominance",
    beta: "Polygenic inheritance",
    charlie: "Codominance",
    delta: "Epistasis",
    correct_answer: "Polygenic inheritance",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 811,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is the term for a chromosomal aberration where a part of a chromosome is repeated?",
    alpha: "Deletion",
    beta: "Duplication",
    charlie: "Inversion",
    delta: "Translocation",
    correct_answer: "Duplication",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 812,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "Which chromosomal aberration involves the reversal of the order of genes on a chromosome?",
    alpha: "Deletion",
    beta: "Duplication",
    charlie: "Inversion",
    delta: "Translocation",
    correct_answer: "Inversion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 813,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is aneuploidy?",
    alpha: "An abnormality in chromosome number",
    beta: "An abnormality in chromosome structure",
    charlie: "A balanced chromosomal rearrangement",
    delta: "A chromosomal inversion",
    correct_answer: "An abnormality in chromosome number",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 814,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "Which chromosomal aberration results from the presence of an extra chromosome?",
    alpha: "Monosomy",
    beta: "Trisomy",
    charlie: "Tetrasomy",
    delta: "Aneuploidy",
    correct_answer: "Trisomy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 815,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is the most common trisomy seen in humans?",
    alpha: "Trisomy 13",
    beta: "Trisomy 18",
    charlie: "Trisomy 21",
    delta: "Trisomy 22",
    correct_answer: "Trisomy 21",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 816,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is a karyotype?",
    alpha: "A chart of chromosome numbers",
    beta: "A diagram of chromosome structure",
    charlie: "A visualization of gene mutations",
    delta: "A summary of genetic disorders",
    correct_answer: "A chart of chromosome numbers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 817,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is Down syndrome caused by?",
    alpha: "Monosomy X",
    beta: "Trisomy 18",
    charlie: "Trisomy 21",
    delta: "Turner syndrome",
    correct_answer: "Trisomy 21",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 818,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "Which chromosomal aberration involves the loss of a portion of a chromosome?",
    alpha: "Deletion",
    beta: "Duplication",
    charlie: "Inversion",
    delta: "Translocation",
    correct_answer: "Deletion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 819,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "In which type of chromosomal aberration do parts of chromosomes switch places?",
    alpha: "Deletion",
    beta: "Duplication",
    charlie: "Inversion",
    delta: "Translocation",
    correct_answer: "Translocation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 820,
    quiz_id: 82,
    question: "What is the term for a chromosomal aberration where a part of a chromosome is repeated?",
    alpha: "Deletion",
    beta: "Duplication",
    charlie: "Inversion",
    delta: "Translocation",
    correct_answer: "Duplication",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 821,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What is the process by which DNA makes an exact copy of itself?",
    alpha: "Transcription",
    beta: "Translation",
    charlie: "Replication",
    delta: "Mutation",
    correct_answer: "Replication",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 822,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "Which enzyme is responsible for unwinding the DNA double helix during replication?",
    alpha: "DNA ligase",
    beta: "RNA polymerase",
    charlie: "Helicase",
    delta: "Primase",
    correct_answer: "Helicase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 823,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What is the function of DNA polymerase in DNA replication?",
    alpha: "Unwinds the DNA double helix",
    beta: "Joins Okazaki fragments",
    charlie: "Adds nucleotides to the growing strand",
    delta: "Repairs damaged DNA",
    correct_answer: "Adds nucleotides to the growing strand",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 824,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "Which of the following accurately describes the leading strand in DNA replication?",
    alpha: "It is synthesized in the 3' to 5' direction",
    beta: "It is synthesized continuously",
    charlie: "It requires multiple primers",
    delta: "It is synthesized in the 5' to 3' direction",
    correct_answer: "It is synthesized continuously",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 825,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What are Okazaki fragments in DNA replication?",
    alpha: "Short RNA primers",
    beta: "Segments of the lagging strand",
    charlie: "DNA helicases",
    delta: "Enzymes that repair DNA",
    correct_answer: "Segments of the lagging strand",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 826,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "Which enzyme is responsible for joining Okazaki fragments in DNA replication?",
    alpha: "DNA ligase",
    beta: "RNA polymerase",
    charlie: "Helicase",
    delta: "Primase",
    correct_answer: "DNA ligase",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 827,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What is the purpose of DNA proofreading during replication?",
    alpha: "To repair damaged DNA",
    beta: "To remove RNA primers",
    charlie: "To check for errors and correct them",
    delta: "To unwind the DNA double helix",
    correct_answer: "To check for errors and correct them",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 828,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What is the term for a change in the sequence of nucleotides in DNA?",
    alpha: "Mutation",
    beta: "Transcription",
    charlie: "Translation",
    delta: "Replication",
    correct_answer: "Mutation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 829,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "Which type of DNA repair mechanism is responsible for fixing thymine dimers caused by UV light?",
    alpha: "Mismatch repair",
    beta: "Nucleotide excision repair",
    charlie: "Base excision repair",
    delta: "Direct repair",
    correct_answer: "Nucleotide excision repair",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 830,
    quiz_id: 83,
    question: "What is the purpose of telomeres at the ends of eukaryotic chromosomes?",
    alpha: "To code for proteins",
    beta: "To provide a template for replication",
    charlie: "To protect against mutations",
    delta: "To prevent the loss of genetic information during replication",
    correct_answer: "To prevent the loss of genetic information during replication",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 831,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is gene expression?",
    alpha: "The process of DNA replication",
    beta: "The process of making RNA from DNA",
    charlie: "The process of making proteins from RNA",
    delta: "The process of copying genetic information",
    correct_answer: "The process of making proteins from RNA",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 832,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of RNA involved in protein synthesis?",
    alpha: "mRNA (messenger RNA)",
    beta: "tRNA (transfer RNA)",
    charlie: "rRNA (ribosomal RNA)",
    delta: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "All of the above",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 833,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is the role of mRNA in gene expression?",
    alpha: "Carries amino acids to the ribosome",
    beta: "Provides a template for protein synthesis",
    charlie: "Forms the structure of ribosomes",
    delta: "Catalyzes chemical reactions",
    correct_answer: "Provides a template for protein synthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 834,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is the function of tRNA in gene expression?",
    alpha: "Transcribes DNA into RNA",
    beta: "Carries amino acids to the ribosome",
    charlie: "Forms the structure of ribosomes",
    delta: "Catalyzes chemical reactions",
    correct_answer: "Carries amino acids to the ribosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 835,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "Where does translation (protein synthesis) occur in the cell?",
    alpha: "Nucleus",
    beta: "Mitochondria",
    charlie: "Endoplasmic reticulum",
    delta: "Ribosome",
    correct_answer: "Ribosome",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 836,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is a promoter in gene expression?",
    alpha: "A region of DNA that initiates transcription",
    beta: "A type of RNA molecule",
    charlie: "A structure in the cell membrane",
    delta: "A component of the ribosome",
    correct_answer: "A region of DNA that initiates transcription",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 837,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is the role of transcription factors in gene expression?",
    alpha: "Carry amino acids to the ribosome",
    beta: "Initiate translation",
    charlie: "Activate or repress gene transcription",
    delta: "Form the structure of ribosomes",
    correct_answer: "Activate or repress gene transcription",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 838,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is a gene regulatory element?",
    alpha: "A segment of DNA that codes for a protein",
    beta: "A region of RNA that regulates translation",
    charlie: "A sequence of amino acids in a protein",
    delta: "A segment of DNA involved in controlling gene expression",
    correct_answer: "A segment of DNA involved in controlling gene expression",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 839,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is the purpose of the lac operon in prokaryotic gene regulation?",
    alpha: "Regulates gene expression in response to lactose",
    beta: "Controls translation of mRNA",
    charlie: "Synthesizes ribosomal RNA",
    delta: "Initiates DNA replication",
    correct_answer: "Regulates gene expression in response to lactose",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 840,
    quiz_id: 84,
    question: "What is RNA interference (RNAi) used for in gene regulation?",
    alpha: "Enhancing gene expression",
    beta: "Inhibiting gene expression",
    charlie: "Controlling translation",
    delta: "Initiating transcription",
    correct_answer: "Inhibiting gene expression",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 841,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is biotechnology?",
    alpha: "The study of living organisms",
    beta: "The use of living organisms in industry",
    charlie: "The manipulation of genes for practical purposes",
    delta: "The development of new pharmaceuticals",
    correct_answer: "The manipulation of genes for practical purposes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 842,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is the purpose of genetic engineering?",
    alpha: "To create new species",
    beta: "To manipulate genes for specific traits",
    charlie: "To study the natural environment",
    delta: "To clone organisms",
    correct_answer: "To manipulate genes for specific traits",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 843,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is a GMO?",
    alpha: "Genetic Mutant Organism",
    beta: "Genetically Modified Organism",
    charlie: "General Modified Organism",
    delta: "Genetic Mutation Operation",
    correct_answer: "Genetically Modified Organism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 844,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "Which enzyme is commonly used in genetic engineering to cut DNA at specific sequences?",
    alpha: "DNA polymerase",
    beta: "RNA polymerase",
    charlie: "Ligase",
    delta: "Restriction enzyme",
    correct_answer: "Restriction enzyme",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 845,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is the purpose of a plasmid in genetic engineering?",
    alpha: "To serve as a template for DNA replication",
    beta: "To carry foreign genes into a host cell",
    charlie: "To synthesize RNA",
    delta: "To repair damaged DNA",
    correct_answer: "To carry foreign genes into a host cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 846,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is recombinant DNA?",
    alpha: "DNA formed by the recombination of RNA strands",
    beta: "DNA with mutations",
    charlie: "DNA from multiple sources combined",
    delta: "DNA undergoing replication",
    correct_answer: "DNA from multiple sources combined",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 847,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is a vector in genetic engineering?",
    alpha: "A carrier for introducing foreign genes into a host cell",
    beta: "A type of mutation",
    charlie: "A cloning organism",
    delta: "A fragment of DNA",
    correct_answer: "A carrier for introducing foreign genes into a host cell",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 848,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is gene therapy?",
    alpha: "Using genes to treat medical conditions",
    beta: "Creating genetically modified organisms",
    charlie: "Editing genes for aesthetic purposes",
    delta: "Cloning genes for research",
    correct_answer: "Using genes to treat medical conditions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 849,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is CRISPR-Cas9 used for in genetic engineering?",
    alpha: "Repairing damaged DNA",
    beta: "Editing specific genes",
    charlie: "Generating mutations",
    delta: "Synthesizing RNA",
    correct_answer: "Editing specific genes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 850,
    quiz_id: 85,
    question: "What is the ethical concern associated with genetic engineering?",
    alpha: "Potential misuse of genetic information",
    beta: "Increased biodiversity",
    charlie: "Enhanced medical treatments",
    delta: "Rapid evolution of species",
    correct_answer: "Potential misuse of genetic information",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 851,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "A group of interacting organisms",
    beta: "A community of plants",
    charlie: "A habitat with a specific climate",
    delta: "A biological community and its physical environment",
    correct_answer: "A biological community and its physical environment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 852,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is the role of a producer in an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "Consumes other organisms for energy",
    beta: "Converts sunlight into energy through photosynthesis",
    charlie: "Decomposes organic matter",
    delta: "Predates on other organisms",
    correct_answer: "Converts sunlight into energy through photosynthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 853,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is the primary source of energy in most ecosystems?",
    alpha: "Wind energy",
    beta: "Solar energy",
    charlie: "Geothermal energy",
    delta: "Chemical energy",
    correct_answer: "Solar energy",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 854,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is a trophic level in an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "A specific type of habitat",
    beta: "A level of ecological organization",
    charlie: "A type of decomposer",
    delta: "A group of interacting species",
    correct_answer: "A level of ecological organization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 855,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "Which organism is a primary consumer in a food chain?",
    alpha: "Herbivore",
    beta: "Carnivore",
    charlie: "Omnivore",
    delta: "Decomposer",
    correct_answer: "Herbivore",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 856,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is a decomposer in an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "An organism that eats plants",
    beta: "An organism that eats other animals",
    charlie: "An organism that breaks down dead organic matter",
    delta: "An organism that photosynthesizes",
    correct_answer: "An organism that breaks down dead organic matter",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 857,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is a keystone species?",
    alpha: "A species that builds nests in trees",
    beta: "A species that is a top predator",
    charlie: "A species with a large population",
    delta: "A species that has a disproportionate impact on its ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "A species that has a disproportionate impact on its ecosystem",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 858,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is symbiosis?",
    alpha: "Competition between species",
    beta: "Mutualism between species",
    charlie: "Predation between species",
    delta: "Coexistence between species",
    correct_answer: "Mutualism between species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 859,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is the difference between predation and parasitism?",
    alpha: "Predation benefits both parties, while parasitism harms one party",
    beta: "Predation involves two species, while parasitism involves three",
    charlie: "Predation harms both parties, while parasitism benefits one party",
    delta: "Predation is a form of mutualism, while parasitism is a form of commensalism",
    correct_answer: "Predation harms both parties, while parasitism benefits one party",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 860,
    quiz_id: 86,
    question: "What is succession in an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "The process of photosynthesis",
    beta: "The replacement of one community by another over time",
    charlie: "The migration of species to new habitats",
    delta: "The seasonal variation in weather patterns",
    correct_answer: "The replacement of one community by another over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 861,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is a population in ecology?",
    alpha: "A group of different species",
    beta: "A group of individuals of the same species",
    charlie: "A community of organisms",
    delta: "An ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "A group of individuals of the same species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 862,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is population density?",
    alpha: "The number of different species in an area",
    beta: "The number of individuals of a species per unit area or volume",
    charlie: "The variety of ecosystems in a region",
    delta: "The total number of organisms in a habitat",
    correct_answer: "The number of individuals of a species per unit area or volume",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 863,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the difference between density-dependent and density-independent factors in population ecology?",
    alpha: "Density-dependent factors have a constant effect, while density-independent factors vary with population size",
    beta: "Density-dependent factors vary with population size, while density-independent factors have a constant effect",
    charlie: "Both types of factors have a constant effect on population size",
    delta: "Both types of factors vary with population size",
    correct_answer: "Density-dependent factors vary with population size, while density-independent factors have a constant effect",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 864,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is carrying capacity in population ecology?",
    alpha: "The maximum population size that an environment can support",
    beta: "The rate at which a population grows",
    charlie: "The density-independent factors affecting a population",
    delta: "The reproductive potential of a population",
    correct_answer: "The maximum population size that an environment can support",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 865,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the logistic growth model in population ecology?",
    alpha: "A model of unlimited population growth",
    beta: "A model of population growth with a carrying capacity",
    charlie: "A model of rapid exponential growth",
    delta: "A model of population decline",
    correct_answer: "A model of population growth with a carrying capacity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 866,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the demographic transition in population ecology?",
    alpha: "A sudden increase in population growth",
    beta: "A shift from high birth and death rates to low birth and death rates",
    charlie: "The movement of individuals between populations",
    delta: "The seasonal variation in population size",
    correct_answer: "A shift from high birth and death rates to low birth and death rates",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 867,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the age structure of a population?",
    alpha: "The number of different age groups in a population",
    beta: "The average age of individuals in a population",
    charlie: "The gender distribution in a population",
    delta: "The number of individuals at different age levels",
    correct_answer: "The number of individuals at different age levels",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 868,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the significance of a pyramid-shaped age structure diagram?",
    alpha: "Stable population with slow growth",
    beta: "Rapid population decline",
    charlie: "Rapid population growth",
    delta: "Stable population with high growth",
    correct_answer: "Rapid population growth",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 869,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the demographic transition theory?",
    alpha: "A theory explaining population decline",
    beta: "A theory explaining population growth",
    charlie: "A theory explaining changes in birth and death rates over time",
    delta: "A theory explaining migration patterns",
    correct_answer: "A theory explaining changes in birth and death rates over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 870,
    quiz_id: 87,
    question: "What is the difference between r-selected and K-selected species?",
    alpha: "r-selected species have a stable population size, while K-selected species have rapid population growth",
    beta: "r-selected species have rapid population growth, while K-selected species have a stable population size",
    charlie: "Both types of species have rapid population growth",
    delta: "Both types of species have a stable population size",
    correct_answer: "r-selected species have rapid population growth, while K-selected species have a stable population size",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 871,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is a biological community?",
    alpha: "A group of different species",
    beta: "A group of individuals of the same species",
    charlie: "A habitat with a specific climate",
    delta: "An ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "A group of different species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 872,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is the difference between a niche and a habitat in community ecology?",
    alpha: "A niche is a physical location, while a habitat is an ecological role",
    beta: "A habitat is a physical location, while a niche is an ecological role",
    charlie: "Both terms refer to the same concept",
    delta: "Neither term is used in community ecology",
    correct_answer: "A habitat is a physical location, while a niche is an ecological role",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 873,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is competitive exclusion in community ecology?",
    alpha: "A situation where two species coexist peacefully",
    beta: "A situation where two species share the same habitat",
    charlie: "A situation where two species compete for the same resources, leading to the elimination of one species",
    delta: "A situation where two species collaborate for mutual benefit",
    correct_answer: "A situation where two species compete for the same resources, leading to the elimination of one species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 874,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is symbiosis in community ecology?",
    alpha: "A situation where two species compete for resources",
    beta: "A situation where two species collaborate for mutual benefit",
    charlie: "A situation where two species share the same habitat",
    delta: "A situation where two species avoid each other",
    correct_answer: "A situation where two species collaborate for mutual benefit",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 875,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is the difference between mutualism and commensalism?",
    alpha: "Mutualism benefits both species, while commensalism benefits only one species",
    beta: "Mutualism benefits only one species, while commensalism benefits both species",
    charlie: "Both terms refer to the same type of interaction",
    delta: "Neither term is used in community ecology",
    correct_answer: "Mutualism benefits both species, while commensalism benefits only one species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 876,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is a keystone species in community ecology?",
    alpha: "A species with a large population size",
    beta: "A species that builds nests in trees",
    charlie: "A species that is a top predator and has a disproportionate impact on its community",
    delta: "A species that avoids competition with other species",
    correct_answer: "A species that is a top predator and has a disproportionate impact on its community",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 877,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is ecological succession in community ecology?",
    alpha: "A gradual increase in biodiversity",
    beta: "The replacement of one community by another over time",
    charlie: "A sudden decline in population size",
    delta: "The migration of species to new habitats",
    correct_answer: "The replacement of one community by another over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 878,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is the difference between primary and secondary succession?",
    alpha: "Primary succession occurs first, while secondary succession occurs later",
    beta: "Primary succession occurs after secondary succession",
    charlie: "Both types of succession involve the same stages",
    delta: "Neither term is used in community ecology",
    correct_answer: "Primary succession occurs first, while secondary succession occurs later",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 879,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is the role of pioneer species in ecological succession?",
    alpha: "Species that only appear in the final stages of succession",
    beta: "Species that colonize a new or disturbed area first",
    charlie: "Species that are top predators",
    delta: "Species that are resistant to environmental changes",
    correct_answer: "Species that colonize a new or disturbed area first",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 880,
    quiz_id: 88,
    question: "What is biodiversity in community ecology?",
    alpha: "The number of individuals in a population",
    beta: "The variety of species in a community",
    charlie: "The average age of individuals in a population",
    delta: "The density of individuals in a habitat",
    correct_answer: "The variety of species in a community",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 881,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is the definition of ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "The study of static ecosystems",
    beta: "The study of the interactions and changes within ecosystems over time",
    charlie: "The study of individual species within ecosystems",
    delta: "The study of abiotic factors in ecosystems",
    correct_answer: "The study of the interactions and changes within ecosystems over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 882,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is a disturbance in the context of ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "A stable condition within an ecosystem",
    beta: "An event that disrupts the normal functioning of an ecosystem",
    charlie: "A gradual change in temperature",
    delta: "The introduction of new species to an ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "An event that disrupts the normal functioning of an ecosystem",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 883,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "How can natural disturbances contribute to ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "By maintaining a constant ecosystem structure",
    beta: "By preventing any changes in the ecosystem",
    charlie: "By introducing new species to the ecosystem",
    delta: "By creating opportunities for regeneration and diversity",
    correct_answer: "By creating opportunities for regeneration and diversity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 884,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is ecological resilience?",
    alpha: "The ability of an ecosystem to resist all disturbances",
    beta: "The ability of an ecosystem to return to its original state after a disturbance",
    charlie: "The ability of an ecosystem to avoid all disturbances",
    delta: "The ability of an ecosystem to prevent changes over time",
    correct_answer: "The ability of an ecosystem to return to its original state after a disturbance",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 885,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is the role of pioneer species in ecosystem succession?",
    alpha: "To maintain stability within the ecosystem",
    beta: "To prevent disturbances",
    charlie: "To initiate the colonization of a new or disturbed area",
    delta: "To resist changes within the ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "To initiate the colonization of a new or disturbed area",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 886,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "How does nutrient cycling contribute to ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "By depleting nutrients in the ecosystem",
    beta: "By preventing any changes in nutrient levels",
    charlie: "By promoting the accumulation of nutrients",
    delta: "By recycling and redistributing nutrients within the ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "By recycling and redistributing nutrients within the ecosystem",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 887,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is primary productivity in ecosystems?",
    alpha: "The total number of individuals in a population",
    beta: "The rate at which solar energy is converted into organic compounds through photosynthesis",
    charlie: "The variety of species in a community",
    delta: "The density of individuals in a habitat",
    correct_answer: "The rate at which solar energy is converted into organic compounds through photosynthesis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 888,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "How do keystone species impact ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "By having no impact on other species",
    beta: "By maintaining a constant population size",
    charlie: "By having a disproportionate impact on the structure and function of the ecosystem",
    delta: "By preventing disturbances",
    correct_answer: "By having a disproportionate impact on the structure and function of the ecosystem",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 889,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "What is the role of decomposers in nutrient cycling?",
    alpha: "To consume primary producers",
    beta: "To release nutrients by breaking down organic matter",
    charlie: "To produce organic matter through photosynthesis",
    delta: "To regulate nutrient levels in the ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "To release nutrients by breaking down organic matter",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 890,
    quiz_id: 89,
    question: "How can human activities impact ecosystem dynamics?",
    alpha: "By promoting biodiversity",
    beta: "By reducing disturbances",
    charlie: "By introducing keystone species",
    delta: "By altering nutrient cycling and causing habitat destruction",
    correct_answer: "By altering nutrient cycling and causing habitat destruction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 891,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is conservation biology?",
    alpha: "The study of individual species within ecosystems",
    beta: "The study of ecosystems and their dynamics over time",
    charlie: "The study of the interactions between species",
    delta: "The study of the preservation of biodiversity and ecosystems",
    correct_answer: "The study of the preservation of biodiversity and ecosystems",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 892,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "Why is biodiversity important for ecosystems and human well-being?",
    alpha: "Biodiversity has no impact on ecosystems",
    beta: "Biodiversity ensures ecosystem stability and resilience",
    charlie: "Biodiversity only benefits individual species",
    delta: "Biodiversity hinders ecological processes",
    correct_answer: "Biodiversity ensures ecosystem stability and resilience",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 893,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is habitat fragmentation?",
    alpha: "The destruction of ecosystems",
    beta: "The separation of an ecosystem into smaller, isolated patches",
    charlie: "The introduction of new species to an ecosystem",
    delta: "The migration of species to new habitats",
    correct_answer: "The separation of an ecosystem into smaller, isolated patches",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 894,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "How does habitat loss contribute to the decline of species?",
    alpha: "Habitat loss has no impact on species",
    beta: "Habitat loss leads to the increase in species populations",
    charlie: "Habitat loss reduces available resources and suitable living spaces for species",
    delta: "Habitat loss enhances species diversity",
    correct_answer: "Habitat loss reduces available resources and suitable living spaces for species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 895,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is the role of corridors in conservation biology?",
    alpha: "To restrict the movement of species",
    beta: "To enhance habitat fragmentation",
    charlie: "To provide connections between habitat patches to facilitate species movement",
    delta: "To eliminate species diversity",
    correct_answer: "To provide connections between habitat patches to facilitate species movement",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 896,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is overexploitation in the context of conservation biology?",
    alpha: "The underutilization of natural resources",
    beta: "The sustainable use of natural resources",
    charlie: "The excessive use of natural resources, leading to depletion",
    delta: "The protection of natural resources",
    correct_answer: "The excessive use of natural resources, leading to depletion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 897,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "How can invasive species impact native biodiversity?",
    alpha: "Invasive species have no impact on native biodiversity",
    beta: "Invasive species enhance native biodiversity",
    charlie: "Invasive species compete with and displace native species",
    delta: "Invasive species promote ecosystem stability",
    correct_answer: "Invasive species compete with and displace native species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 898,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is the importance of captive breeding programs in conservation?",
    alpha: "To reduce biodiversity",
    beta: "To exploit species for economic gain",
    charlie: "To enhance habitat loss",
    delta: "To prevent the extinction of endangered species by breeding them in controlled environments",
    correct_answer: "To prevent the extinction of endangered species by breeding them in controlled environments",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 899,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "What is the role of protected areas in conservation?",
    alpha: "To promote habitat fragmentation",
    beta: "To facilitate overexploitation",
    charlie: "To enhance invasive species introduction",
    delta: "To safeguard natural habitats and prevent habitat loss",
    correct_answer: "To safeguard natural habitats and prevent habitat loss",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 900,
    quiz_id: 90,
    question: "How can individuals contribute to conservation efforts?",
    alpha: "By promoting habitat destruction",
    beta: "By engaging in overexploitation",
    charlie: "By supporting sustainable practices and raising awareness about conservation",
    delta: "By introducing invasive species to new environments",
    correct_answer: "By supporting sustainable practices and raising awareness about conservation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 901,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the primary function of the skeletal system in the human body?",
    alpha: "To generate heat",
    beta: "To facilitate digestion",
    charlie: "To provide structural support and protect organs",
    delta: "To pump blood",
    correct_answer: "To provide structural support and protect organs",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 902,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "How many bones are typically present in the adult human body?",
    alpha: "100",
    beta: "206",
    charlie: "300",
    delta: "400",
    correct_answer: "206",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 903,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the purpose of joints in the skeletal system?",
    alpha: "To store nutrients",
    beta: "To provide structural support",
    charlie: "To facilitate movement between bones",
    delta: "To produce blood cells",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate movement between bones",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 904,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "Which type of joint allows the widest range of motion?",
    alpha: "Ball and socket joint",
    beta: "Hinge joint",
    charlie: "Pivot joint",
    delta: "Gliding joint",
    correct_answer: "Ball and socket joint",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 905,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the function of the vertebral column in the human skeletal system?",
    alpha: "To protect the brain",
    beta: "To support the upper limbs",
    charlie: "To provide a framework for the face",
    delta: "To protect and support the spinal cord",
    correct_answer: "To protect and support the spinal cord",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 906,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the role of red bone marrow in the skeletal system?",
    alpha: "To store fat",
    beta: "To store minerals",
    charlie: "To produce blood cells",
    delta: "To provide structural support",
    correct_answer: "To produce blood cells",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 907,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the function of the skull in the skeletal system?",
    alpha: "To support the spine",
    beta: "To protect the brain",
    charlie: "To store nutrients",
    delta: "To facilitate movement",
    correct_answer: "To protect the brain",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 908,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "Which bones make up the forearm in the human body?",
    alpha: "Humerus and femur",
    beta: "Radius and ulna",
    charlie: "Tibia and fibula",
    delta: "Femur and tibia",
    correct_answer: "Radius and ulna",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 909,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the function of the ribcage in the skeletal system?",
    alpha: "To protect the heart and lungs",
    beta: "To support the lower limbs",
    charlie: "To facilitate breathing",
    delta: "To store nutrients",
    correct_answer: "To protect the heart and lungs",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 910,
    quiz_id: 91,
    question: "What is the primary component of bones that provides strength and hardness?",
    alpha: "Collagen",
    beta: "Calcium phosphate",
    charlie: "Elastin",
    delta: "Chondroitin sulfate",
    correct_answer: "Calcium phosphate",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 911,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the primary function of the muscular system in the human body?",
    alpha: "To provide structural support",
    beta: "To facilitate movement",
    charlie: "To protect internal organs",
    delta: "To store nutrients",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate movement",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 912,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "How many types of muscle tissue are found in the human body?",
    alpha: "One",
    beta: "Two",
    charlie: "Three",
    delta: "Four",
    correct_answer: "Three",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 913,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "Which type of muscle is under voluntary control?",
    alpha: "Cardiac muscle",
    beta: "Smooth muscle",
    charlie: "Skeletal muscle",
    delta: "Involuntary muscle",
    correct_answer: "Skeletal muscle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 914,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the role of tendons in the muscular system?",
    alpha: "To store energy",
    beta: "To facilitate joint movement",
    charlie: "To connect muscles to bones",
    delta: "To protect internal organs",
    correct_answer: "To connect muscles to bones",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 915,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the function of the biceps muscle?",
    alpha: "To extend the arm",
    beta: "To flex the leg",
    charlie: "To flex the arm",
    delta: "To extend the leg",
    correct_answer: "To flex the arm",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 916,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the main function of smooth muscle in the body?",
    alpha: "To pump blood",
    beta: "To facilitate voluntary movements",
    charlie: "To control body temperature",
    delta: "To propel substances through internal organs",
    correct_answer: "To propel substances through internal organs",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 917,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "Which muscle is responsible for the pumping action of the heart?",
    alpha: "Skeletal muscle",
    beta: "Smooth muscle",
    charlie: "Cardiac muscle",
    delta: "Involuntary muscle",
    correct_answer: "Cardiac muscle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 918,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the function of the diaphragm muscle?",
    alpha: "To control eye movement",
    beta: "To facilitate breathing",
    charlie: "To aid in digestion",
    delta: "To pump blood",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate breathing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 919,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "What is the purpose of the quadriceps muscle group?",
    alpha: "To flex the knee",
    beta: "To extend the knee",
    charlie: "To rotate the hip",
    delta: "To rotate the shoulder",
    correct_answer: "To extend the knee",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 920,
    quiz_id: 92,
    question: "How do muscles work in pairs during movement?",
    alpha: "Both muscles contract simultaneously",
    beta: "One muscle contracts while the other relaxes",
    charlie: "Both muscles relax simultaneously",
    delta: "One muscle extends while the other flexes",
    correct_answer: "One muscle contracts while the other relaxes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 921,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the primary function of the circulatory system in the human body?",
    alpha: "To facilitate breathing",
    beta: "To provide structural support",
    charlie: "To transport nutrients and oxygen to cells and remove waste products",
    delta: "To store nutrients",
    correct_answer: "To transport nutrients and oxygen to cells and remove waste products",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 922,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What are the three main components of the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "Heart, lungs, and liver",
    beta: "Heart, blood vessels, and blood",
    charlie: "Brain, stomach, and kidneys",
    delta: "Muscles, bones, and skin",
    correct_answer: "Heart, blood vessels, and blood",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 923,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the function of the heart in the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "To filter blood",
    beta: "To pump blood and circulate it throughout the body",
    charlie: "To store nutrients",
    delta: "To facilitate digestion",
    correct_answer: "To pump blood and circulate it throughout the body",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 924,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What are the two main types of blood vessels in the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "Arteries and veins",
    beta: "Capillaries and alveoli",
    charlie: "Bronchi and trachea",
    delta: "Lymph nodes and spleen",
    correct_answer: "Arteries and veins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 925,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "Which type of blood vessels carry oxygenated blood away from the heart?",
    alpha: "Veins",
    beta: "Capillaries",
    charlie: "Arteries",
    delta: "Alveoli",
    correct_answer: "Arteries",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 926,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the purpose of capillaries in the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "To store blood",
    beta: "To transport nutrients and oxygen to cells and remove waste products",
    charlie: "To pump blood",
    delta: "To filter blood",
    correct_answer: "To transport nutrients and oxygen to cells and remove waste products",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 927,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the function of veins in the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "To pump blood",
    beta: "To transport oxygen to cells",
    charlie: "To carry deoxygenated blood back to the heart",
    delta: "To facilitate digestion",
    correct_answer: "To carry deoxygenated blood back to the heart",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 928,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the purpose of red blood cells in the blood?",
    alpha: "To fight infections",
    beta: "To clot blood",
    charlie: "To transport oxygen",
    delta: "To produce antibodies",
    correct_answer: "To transport oxygen",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 929,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the function of white blood cells in the blood?",
    alpha: "To transport oxygen",
    beta: "To fight infections",
    charlie: "To transport nutrients",
    delta: "To clot blood",
    correct_answer: "To fight infections",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 930,
    quiz_id: 93,
    question: "What is the role of platelets in the circulatory system?",
    alpha: "To transport nutrients",
    beta: "To produce antibodies",
    charlie: "To clot blood",
    delta: "To pump blood",
    correct_answer: "To clot blood",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 931,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the primary function of the nervous system in the human body?",
    alpha: "To facilitate digestion",
    beta: "To pump blood",
    charlie: "To provide structural support",
    delta: "To receive and transmit signals to control body functions",
    correct_answer: "To receive and transmit signals to control body functions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 932,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What are the two main divisions of the nervous system?",
    alpha: "Central and peripheral",
    beta: "Autonomic and somatic",
    charlie: "Sympathetic and parasympathetic",
    delta: "Motor and sensory",
    correct_answer: "Central and peripheral",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 933,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the function of the central nervous system (CNS)?",
    alpha: "To transmit signals to muscles",
    beta: "To receive sensory input",
    charlie: "To coordinate and process information",
    delta: "To regulate involuntary functions",
    correct_answer: "To coordinate and process information",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 934,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "Which structures make up the central nervous system?",
    alpha: "Brain and spinal cord",
    beta: "Nerves and ganglia",
    charlie: "Sensory receptors",
    delta: "Motor neurons",
    correct_answer: "Brain and spinal cord",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 935,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the function of the peripheral nervous system (PNS)?",
    alpha: "To process information",
    beta: "To transmit signals to muscles and glands",
    charlie: "To coordinate involuntary functions",
    delta: "To regulate body temperature",
    correct_answer: "To transmit signals to muscles and glands",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 936,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "Which structures make up the peripheral nervous system?",
    alpha: "Brain and spinal cord",
    beta: "Nerves and ganglia",
    charlie: "Sensory receptors",
    delta: "Motor neurons",
    correct_answer: "Nerves and ganglia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 937,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the role of sensory neurons in the nervous system?",
    alpha: "To carry signals from muscles to the brain",
    beta: "To transmit signals to muscles and glands",
    charlie: "To carry signals from sensory receptors to the central nervous system",
    delta: "To regulate involuntary functions",
    correct_answer: "To carry signals from sensory receptors to the central nervous system",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 938,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the function of motor neurons in the nervous system?",
    alpha: "To carry signals from sensory receptors to the central nervous system",
    beta: "To process information",
    charlie: "To transmit signals to muscles and glands",
    delta: "To regulate body temperature",
    correct_answer: "To transmit signals to muscles and glands",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 939,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is a synapse in the nervous system?",
    alpha: "A type of neuron",
    beta: "A sensory receptor",
    charlie: "The space between neurons where signals are transmitted",
    delta: "A motor neuron",
    correct_answer: "The space between neurons where signals are transmitted",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 940,
    quiz_id: 94,
    question: "What is the role of neurotransmitters in signal transmission?",
    alpha: "To regulate body temperature",
    beta: "To transmit signals to muscles",
    charlie: "To carry signals from sensory receptors to the central nervous system",
    delta: "To facilitate communication between neurons at synapses",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate communication between neurons at synapses",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 941,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "What is the primary function of the respiratory system?",
    alpha: "To regulate body temperature",
    beta: "To transport nutrients",
    charlie: "To facilitate breathing and exchange of gases",
    delta: "To digest food",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate breathing and exchange of gases",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 942,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "Which organ is responsible for the exchange of oxygen and carbon dioxide in the respiratory system?",
    alpha: "Stomach",
    beta: "Lungs",
    charlie: "Liver",
    delta: "Pancreas",
    correct_answer: "Lungs",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 943,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "What is the function of the diaphragm in the respiratory system?",
    alpha: "To filter air",
    beta: "To regulate blood pressure",
    charlie: "To facilitate breathing",
    delta: "To produce digestive enzymes",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate breathing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 944,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "What is the primary function of the digestive system?",
    alpha: "To transport oxygen",
    beta: "To regulate body temperature",
    charlie: "To facilitate digestion and absorption of nutrients",
    delta: "To pump blood",
    correct_answer: "To facilitate digestion and absorption of nutrients",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 945,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "Which organ produces digestive enzymes to break down food?",
    alpha: "Liver",
    beta: "Stomach",
    charlie: "Pancreas",
    delta: "Lungs",
    correct_answer: "Pancreas",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 946,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "What is the role of bile in the digestive system?",
    alpha: "To store nutrients",
    beta: "To neutralize stomach acid",
    charlie: "To emulsify fats",
    delta: "To filter blood",
    correct_answer: "To emulsify fats",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 947,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "Where does the majority of nutrient absorption occur in the digestive system?",
    alpha: "Stomach",
    beta: "Small intestine",
    charlie: "Large intestine",
    delta: "Esophagus",
    correct_answer: "Small intestine",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 948,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "Which substance helps in the mechanical breakdown of food in the mouth?",
    alpha: "Pepsin",
    beta: "Saliva",
    charlie: "Bile",
    delta: "Pancreatic juice",
    correct_answer: "Saliva",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 949,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "What is the function of the stomach in the digestive system?",
    alpha: "To absorb nutrients",
    beta: "To store bile",
    charlie: "To produce insulin",
    delta: "To break down food with acid and enzymes",
    correct_answer: "To break down food with acid and enzymes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 950,
    quiz_id: 95,
    question: "Where is water primarily absorbed in the digestive system?",
    alpha: "Stomach",
    beta: "Small intestine",
    charlie: "Large intestine",
    delta: "Esophagus",
    correct_answer: "Large intestine",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 951,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "Who is considered the father of modern evolutionary theory?",
    alpha: "Gregor Mendel",
    beta: "Charles Darwin",
    charlie: "Alfred Russel Wallace",
    delta: "Jean-Baptiste Lamarck",
    correct_answer: "Charles Darwin",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 952,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is natural selection?",
    alpha: "A process of random genetic mutations",
    beta: "The intentional breeding of organisms",
    charlie: "The process by which traits that increase reproductive success become more common in a population",
    delta: "The process of genetic drift",
    correct_answer: "The process by which traits that increase reproductive success become more common in a population",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 953,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "In the theory of evolution, what is adaptation?",
    alpha: "A sudden change in the genetic code",
    beta: "The process of natural selection",
    charlie: "A trait that increases an organism's fitness in its environment",
    delta: "The process of artificial selection",
    correct_answer: "A trait that increases an organism's fitness in its environment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 954,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What evidence did Darwin use to support his theory of evolution?",
    alpha: "Fossil records",
    beta: "Comparative anatomy",
    charlie: "Biogeography",
    delta: "All of the above",
    correct_answer: "All of the above",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 955,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is speciation?",
    alpha: "The process of artificial selection",
    beta: "The process of natural selection",
    charlie: "The formation of new and distinct species in the course of evolution",
    delta: "The process of genetic drift",
    correct_answer: "The formation of new and distinct species in the course of evolution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 956,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is the role of genetic variation in evolution?",
    alpha: "It slows down the evolutionary process",
    beta: "It has no impact on evolution",
    charlie: "It provides the raw material for natural selection to work on",
    delta: "It causes extinction",
    correct_answer: "It provides the raw material for natural selection to work on",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 957,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is the founder effect?",
    alpha: "A type of genetic drift",
    beta: "A form of natural selection",
    charlie: "The intentional breeding of organisms",
    delta: "A process of random genetic mutations",
    correct_answer: "A type of genetic drift",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 958,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is convergent evolution?",
    alpha: "The process of artificial selection",
    beta: "The process of natural selection",
    charlie: "The independent evolution of similar traits in different species",
    delta: "The process of genetic drift",
    correct_answer: "The independent evolution of similar traits in different species",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 959,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is the role of mutation in evolution?",
    alpha: "It causes extinction",
    beta: "It slows down the evolutionary process",
    charlie: "It provides the raw material for genetic variation",
    delta: "It has no impact on evolution",
    correct_answer: "It provides the raw material for genetic variation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 960,
    quiz_id: 96,
    question: "What is a homologous structure?",
    alpha: "Structures with similar functions but different evolutionary origins",
    beta: "Structures with different functions but similar evolutionary origins",
    charlie: "Structures that have no evolutionary significance",
    delta: "Structures that are vestigial",
    correct_answer: "Structures with different functions but similar evolutionary origins",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 961,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "What is fossil evidence, and how does it support the theory of evolution?",
    alpha: "Fossil evidence is irrelevant to evolution",
    beta: "Fossil evidence provides a record of extinct species and transitional forms, showing changes over time",
    charlie: "Fossil evidence only supports creationism",
    delta: "Fossil evidence proves that evolution is false",
    correct_answer: "Fossil evidence provides a record of extinct species and transitional forms, showing changes over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 962,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "How does comparative anatomy provide evidence for evolution?",
    alpha: "Comparative anatomy is not related to evolution",
    beta: "Comparative anatomy shows that organisms have the same structures, suggesting a common ancestry",
    charlie: "Comparative anatomy proves that species were created independently",
    delta: "Comparative anatomy supports the idea that organisms never change",
    correct_answer: "Comparative anatomy shows that organisms have the same structures, suggesting a common ancestry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 963,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "What is the significance of homologous structures in evolutionary biology?",
    alpha: "Homologous structures are unrelated to evolution",
    beta: "Homologous structures are vestigial and have no function",
    charlie: "Homologous structures indicate a common ancestry, suggesting a shared evolutionary history",
    delta: "Homologous structures prove that species were created independently",
    correct_answer: "Homologous structures indicate a common ancestry, suggesting a shared evolutionary history",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 964,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "How does the study of embryology support the theory of evolution?",
    alpha: "Embryology has no relevance to evolution",
    beta: "Embryology shows that embryos of different species are identical, providing evidence for a common ancestry",
    charlie: "Embryology proves that species were created independently",
    delta: "Embryology supports the idea that organisms never change",
    correct_answer: "Embryology shows that embryos of different species are identical, providing evidence for a common ancestry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 965,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "What is molecular evidence, and how does it contribute to our understanding of evolution?",
    alpha: "Molecular evidence has no bearing on evolution",
    beta: "Molecular evidence, such as DNA and protein sequences, reveals genetic similarities and differences, supporting the idea of a common ancestry",
    charlie: "Molecular evidence only supports creationism",
    delta: "Molecular evidence proves that evolution is false",
    correct_answer: "Molecular evidence, such as DNA and protein sequences, reveals genetic similarities and differences, supporting the idea of a common ancestry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 966,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "What is biogeography, and how does it provide evidence for evolution?",
    alpha: "Biogeography is unrelated to evolution",
    beta: "Biogeography studies the distribution of species and shows patterns that align with evolutionary predictions",
    charlie: "Biogeography supports the idea that species never change",
    delta: "Biogeography only supports creationism",
    correct_answer: "Biogeography studies the distribution of species and shows patterns that align with evolutionary predictions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 967,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "How does the concept of vestigial structures support the theory of evolution?",
    alpha: "Vestigial structures have no evolutionary significance",
    beta: "Vestigial structures are fully functional and refute the idea of evolution",
    charlie: "Vestigial structures indicate remnants of ancestral features with reduced or no function, suggesting a shared evolutionary history",
    delta: "Vestigial structures support the idea that species were created independently",
    correct_answer: "Vestigial structures indicate remnants of ancestral features with reduced or no function, suggesting a shared evolutionary history",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 968,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "What is the significance of the observed patterns of biodiversity in supporting evolution?",
    alpha: "Patterns of biodiversity do not provide evidence for evolution",
    beta: "Patterns of biodiversity align with evolutionary predictions, reflecting a branching pattern of common ancestry",
    charlie: "Patterns of biodiversity only support creationism",
    delta: "Patterns of biodiversity prove that species were created independently",
    correct_answer: "Patterns of biodiversity align with evolutionary predictions, reflecting a branching pattern of common ancestry",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 969,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "How do transitional fossils provide evidence for evolutionary transitions between species?",
    alpha: "Transitional fossils have no impact on the theory of evolution",
    beta: "Transitional fossils show intermediate forms between different species, supporting the idea of gradual change over time",
    charlie: "Transitional fossils only support creationism",
    delta: "Transitional fossils prove that species were created independently",
    correct_answer: "Transitional fossils show intermediate forms between different species, supporting the idea of gradual change over time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 970,
    quiz_id: 97,
    question: "How does the observed antibiotic resistance in bacteria provide evidence for natural selection?",
    alpha: "Antibiotic resistance is unrelated to natural selection",
    beta: "Antibiotic resistance in bacteria is a result of random mutations and does not support the idea of natural selection",
    charlie: "Antibiotic resistance demonstrates the impact of artificial selection",
    delta: "Antibiotic resistance in bacteria is a clear example of natural selection favoring advantageous traits",
    correct_answer: "Antibiotic resistance in bacteria is a clear example of natural selection favoring advantageous traits",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 971,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "What is natural selection, and how does it contribute to evolution?",
    alpha: "Natural selection is a random process with no impact on evolution",
    beta: "Natural selection is the intentional breeding of organisms",
    charlie: "Natural selection is the process by which traits that enhance survival and reproduction become more common in a population",
    delta: "Natural selection accelerates the process of extinction",
    correct_answer: "Natural selection is the process by which traits that enhance survival and reproduction become more common in a population",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 972,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "How does genetic drift influence the evolution of small populations?",
    alpha: "Genetic drift has no impact on evolution",
    beta: "Genetic drift leads to increased genetic diversity in small populations",
    charlie: "Genetic drift is more prominent in large populations",
    delta: "Genetic drift can lead to the loss of alleles and reduced genetic diversity in small populations",
    correct_answer: "Genetic drift can lead to the loss of alleles and reduced genetic diversity in small populations",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 973,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "What is gene flow, and how does it affect the genetic composition of populations?",
    alpha: "Gene flow has no impact on genetic composition",
    beta: "Gene flow increases genetic diversity by introducing new alleles to a population",
    charlie: "Gene flow occurs only in asexual reproduction",
    delta: "Gene flow leads to the isolation of populations",
    correct_answer: "Gene flow increases genetic diversity by introducing new alleles to a population",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 974,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "How does mutation contribute to genetic variation and evolution?",
    alpha: "Mutations are always harmful and reduce genetic diversity",
    beta: "Mutations have no impact on genetic diversity",
    charlie: "Mutations provide a source of genetic variation, and some may be advantageous in specific environments",
    delta: "Mutations only occur in large populations",
    correct_answer: "Mutations provide a source of genetic variation, and some may be advantageous in specific environments",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 975,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "What is artificial selection, and how does it differ from natural selection?",
    alpha: "Artificial selection is a random process similar to natural selection",
    beta: "Artificial selection is the intentional breeding of organisms by humans, while natural selection is driven by environmental factors",
    charlie: "Artificial selection is a process that occurs only in plants",
    delta: "Artificial selection and natural selection are interchangeable terms",
    correct_answer: "Artificial selection is the intentional breeding of organisms by humans, while natural selection is driven by environmental factors",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 976,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "How does sexual selection contribute to the evolution of specific traits?",
    alpha: "Sexual selection has no impact on the evolution of traits",
    beta: "Sexual selection favors traits that enhance an individual's ability to obtain mates and reproduce",
    charlie: "Sexual selection is only relevant in asexual reproduction",
    delta: "Sexual selection accelerates the process of extinction",
    correct_answer: "Sexual selection favors traits that enhance an individual's ability to obtain mates and reproduce",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 977,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "What role does non-random mating play in evolutionary processes?",
    alpha: "Non-random mating increases genetic diversity",
    beta: "Non-random mating has no impact on genetic composition",
    charlie: "Non-random mating leads to genetic drift",
    delta: "Non-random mating can affect allele frequencies and contribute to evolution",
    correct_answer: "Non-random mating can affect allele frequencies and contribute to evolution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 978,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "How does the bottleneck effect influence genetic diversity in a population?",
    alpha: "The bottleneck effect increases genetic diversity",
    beta: "The bottleneck effect has no impact on genetic diversity",
    charlie: "The bottleneck effect leads to the loss of genetic diversity in a population",
    delta: "The bottleneck effect is only relevant in large populations",
    correct_answer: "The bottleneck effect leads to the loss of genetic diversity in a population",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 979,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "What is the role of selective pressures in the evolution of adaptations?",
    alpha: "Selective pressures have no impact on evolution",
    beta: "Selective pressures lead to the loss of adaptations",
    charlie: "Selective pressures favor traits that enhance survival and reproduction, leading to the evolution of adaptations",
    delta: "Selective pressures are only relevant in large populations",
    correct_answer: "Selective pressures favor traits that enhance survival and reproduction, leading to the evolution of adaptations",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 980,
    quiz_id: 98,
    question: "How does the concept of adaptive radiation contribute to biodiversity?",
    alpha: "Adaptive radiation leads to a reduction in biodiversity",
    beta: "Adaptive radiation has no impact on biodiversity",
    charlie: "Adaptive radiation results in the diversification of species into different ecological niches, increasing biodiversity",
    delta: "Adaptive radiation only occurs in isolated populations",
    correct_answer: "Adaptive radiation results in the diversification of species into different ecological niches, increasing biodiversity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 981,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "What is the term for the process of biological evolution by which new species arise?",
    alpha: "Natural selection",
    beta: "Adaptation",
    charlie: "Speciation",
    delta: "Mutation",
    correct_answer: "Speciation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 982,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "Which hominid species is considered the closest extinct relative to modern humans?",
    alpha: "Australopithecus afarensis",
    beta: "Homo habilis",
    charlie: "Neanderthal",
    delta: "Homo erectus",
    correct_answer: "Neanderthal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 983,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "What is the name of the theory proposing that early humans originated in Africa and then migrated to other parts of the world?",
    alpha: "Out of Africa theory",
    beta: "Multiregional theory",
    charlie: "Punctuated equilibrium",
    delta: "Convergent evolution",
    correct_answer: "Out of Africa theory",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 984,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "Which species is known for the use of tools and is considered an early representative of the Homo genus?",
    alpha: "Australopithecus afarensis",
    beta: "Homo habilis",
    charlie: "Neanderthal",
    delta: "Homo erectus",
    correct_answer: "Homo habilis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 985,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "What is the name of the ancient human ancestor known for the famous fossil 'Lucy'?",
    alpha: "Australopithecus afarensis",
    beta: "Homo habilis",
    charlie: "Neanderthal",
    delta: "Homo erectus",
    correct_answer: "Australopithecus afarensis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 986,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "In what period did Homo sapiens, the modern human species, first appear?",
    alpha: "Pleistocene",
    beta: "Holocene",
    charlie: "Miocene",
    delta: "Pliocene",
    correct_answer: "Pleistocene",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 987,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "Which early human species is associated with the use of fire and cave paintings?",
    alpha: "Homo habilis",
    beta: "Homo erectus",
    charlie: "Neanderthal",
    delta: "Cro-Magnon",
    correct_answer: "Homo erectus",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 988,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "What is the scientific name of the anatomically modern humans who first appeared in Africa?",
    alpha: "Homo habilis",
    beta: "Homo erectus",
    charlie: "Homo sapiens",
    delta: "Homo neanderthalensis",
    correct_answer: "Homo sapiens",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 989,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "Which group of early humans is known for their distinctive cranial features, including large brow ridges?",
    alpha: "Australopithecus afarensis",
    beta: "Homo habilis",
    charlie: "Neanderthal",
    delta: "Homo erectus",
    correct_answer: "Neanderthal",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 990,
    quiz_id: 99,
    question: "What is the concept that describes the change in the frequency of certain traits in a population over time?",
    alpha: "Genetic drift",
    beta: "Gene flow",
    charlie: "Mutation",
    delta: "Natural selection",
    correct_answer: "Natural selection",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 991,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is the primary focus of evolutionary ecology?",
    alpha: "Study of ecosystems",
    beta: "Understanding animal behavior",
    charlie: "Examining genetic mutations",
    delta: "Investigating cultural evolution",
    correct_answer: "Understanding animal behavior",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 992,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "Which term refers to the maximum number of individuals that an environment can support?",
    alpha: "Carrying capacity",
    beta: "Biotic potential",
    charlie: "Population density",
    delta: "Ecological niche",
    correct_answer: "Carrying capacity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 993,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is the role of natural selection in evolutionary ecology?",
    alpha: "Maintaining ecosystem stability",
    beta: "Determining optimal population size",
    charlie: "Shaping traits that enhance survival and reproduction",
    delta: "Promoting interspecific competition",
    correct_answer: "Shaping traits that enhance survival and reproduction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 994,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "In the context of evolutionary ecology, what is an adaptation?",
    alpha: "A sudden environmental change",
    beta: "A specialized trait that enhances fitness",
    charlie: "A genetic mutation leading to extinction",
    delta: "An anthropogenic disturbance",
    correct_answer: "A specialized trait that enhances fitness",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 995,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is the term for the study of the interactions between different species in a community?",
    alpha: "Population ecology",
    beta: "Community ecology",
    charlie: "Ecosystem ecology",
    delta: "Behavioral ecology",
    correct_answer: "Community ecology",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 996,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "How does coevolution contribute to biodiversity in ecosystems?",
    alpha: "Reduces species diversity",
    beta: "Promotes extinction",
    charlie: "Leads to ecological imbalance",
    delta: "Fosters the development of specialized relationships",
    correct_answer: "Fosters the development of specialized relationships",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 997,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is an example of a mutualistic relationship in evolutionary ecology?",
    alpha: "Predator-prey interaction",
    beta: "Parasitism",
    charlie: "Competition for resources",
    delta: "Pollination by bees and flowers",
    correct_answer: "Pollination by bees and flowers",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 998,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "How does the niche concept relate to evolutionary ecology?",
    alpha: "It describes the role of an organism in its environment",
    beta: "It quantifies population density",
    charlie: "It measures genetic diversity",
    delta: "It evaluates ecosystem stability",
    correct_answer: "It describes the role of an organism in its environment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 999,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is the importance of genetic diversity in the context of evolutionary ecology?",
    alpha: "Reduces adaptability",
    beta: "Increases vulnerability to diseases",
    charlie: "Enhances ecosystem stability",
    delta: "Promotes interspecific competition",
    correct_answer: "Enhances ecosystem stability",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1000,
    quiz_id: 100,
    question: "What is a keystone species in an ecosystem?",
    alpha: "A dominant predator",
    beta: "A species with a large population size",
    charlie: "A species that plays a critical role in maintaining biodiversity",
    delta: "A species with no impact on the ecosystem",
    correct_answer: "A species that plays a critical role in maintaining biodiversity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1011,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "What is the term for a comparison between two unlike things using 'like' or 'as'?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Simile",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1012,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "Which literary device involves the use of words that imitate the sound they describe?",
    alpha: "Onomatopoeia",
    beta: "Euphemism",
    charlie: "Allusion",
    delta: "Anaphora",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1013,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "In literature, what is the term for a recurring word, phrase, or image that has symbolic significance?",
    alpha: "Symbolism",
    beta: "Motif",
    charlie: "Theme",
    delta: "Allegory",
    correct_answer: "Motif",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1014,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "What is the term for a play on words that exploits the different meanings of a word?",
    alpha: "Pun",
    beta: "Irony",
    charlie: "Paradox",
    delta: "Alliteration",
    correct_answer: "Pun",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1015,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "Which literary term refers to a brief and often witty statement expressing a truth or observation?",
    alpha: "Parable",
    beta: "Epiphany",
    charlie: "Aphorism",
    delta: "Soliloquy",
    correct_answer: "Aphorism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1016,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "What is the term for a character who contrasts with another character to highlight their qualities?",
    alpha: "Protagonist",
    beta: "Antagonist",
    charlie: "Foil",
    delta: "Dynamic character",
    correct_answer: "Foil",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1017,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "Which literary technique involves the repetition of a word or phrase at the beginning of successive clauses?",
    alpha: "Anaphora",
    beta: "Epiphora",
    charlie: "Epanalepsis",
    delta: "Chiasmus",
    correct_answer: "Anaphora",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1018,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "What is the term for the use of a word that imitates the sound it represents?",
    alpha: "Onomatopoeia",
    beta: "Euphony",
    charlie: "Cacophony",
    delta: "Metaphor",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1019,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "In literature, what is the term for a figure of speech that combines contradictory terms?",
    alpha: "Oxymoron",
    beta: "Paradox",
    charlie: "Hyperbole",
    delta: "Allusion",
    correct_answer: "Oxymoron",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1020,
    quiz_id: 102,
    question: "What literary device involves a narrative or description in which the literal events consistently point to a parallel sequence of symbolic meanings?",
    alpha: "Allegory",
    beta: "Allusion",
    charlie: "Metonymy",
    delta: "Irony",
    correct_answer: "Allegory",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1021,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "What is the central idea or message conveyed in a literary work called?",
    alpha: "Mood",
    beta: "Motif",
    charlie: "Theme",
    delta: "Tone",
    correct_answer: "Theme",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1022,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "In literature, what term refers to a recurring image, idea, or symbol that develops or explains a theme?",
    alpha: "Allegory",
    beta: "Metaphor",
    charlie: "Motif",
    delta: "Simile",
    correct_answer: "Motif",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1023,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "Which theme explores the conflict between individuals and societal expectations?",
    alpha: "Love and Friendship",
    beta: "Identity and Self-Discovery",
    charlie: "Conformity and Rebellion",
    delta: "Nature and the Environment",
    correct_answer: "Conformity and Rebellion",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1024,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "In literature, what is the theme that often explores the struggle between good and evil?",
    alpha: "Justice and Injustice",
    beta: "Power and Corruption",
    charlie: "Fate and Free Will",
    delta: "Morality and Ethics",
    correct_answer: "Justice and Injustice",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1025,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "Which theme focuses on the challenges and rewards of personal growth and understanding?",
    alpha: "Isolation and Alienation",
    beta: "Identity and Self-Discovery",
    charlie: "Love and Friendship",
    delta: "Tradition and Modernity",
    correct_answer: "Identity and Self-Discovery",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1026,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "What motif is often associated with the cycle of life, death, and rebirth?",
    alpha: "Quest",
    beta: "Journey",
    charlie: "Circle",
    delta: "Triangle",
    correct_answer: "Circle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1027,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "Which theme explores the impact of technology and progress on individuals and society?",
    alpha: "Freedom and Oppression",
    beta: "Power and Corruption",
    charlie: "Science and Technology",
    delta: "Nature and the Environment",
    correct_answer: "Science and Technology",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1028,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "In literature, what is the theme that often explores the consequences of abusing power?",
    alpha: "Justice and Injustice",
    beta: "Love and Friendship",
    charlie: "Power and Corruption",
    delta: "War and Peace",
    correct_answer: "Power and Corruption",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1029,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "What motif often represents a protagonist's journey to achieve a goal or overcome challenges?",
    alpha: "Quest",
    beta: "Circle",
    charlie: "Triangle",
    delta: "Journey",
    correct_answer: "Quest",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1030,
    quiz_id: 103,
    question: "Which theme explores the complex relationships between individuals and their environment?",
    alpha: "Nature and the Environment",
    beta: "Isolation and Alienation",
    charlie: "Tradition and Modernity",
    delta: "Conformity and Rebellion",
    correct_answer: "Nature and the Environment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1031,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "Which literary movement emphasized intuition, imagination, and emotion over reason and logic?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Naturalism",
    delta: "Enlightenment",
    correct_answer: "Romanticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1032,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "In which literary movement did authors focus on depicting everyday life and its social realities?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Naturalism",
    delta: "Gothic",
    correct_answer: "Realism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1033,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "Which literary movement explored the impact of genetics, environment, and social forces on human behavior?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Naturalism",
    delta: "Transcendentalism",
    correct_answer: "Naturalism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1034,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "During which period did literature reflect a focus on reason, science, and skepticism toward tradition?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Enlightenment",
    charlie: "Victorian",
    delta: "Gothic",
    correct_answer: "Enlightenment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1035,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "Which literary movement rejected Romanticism's emphasis on emotion and embraced precision and objectivity?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Enlightenment",
    delta: "Modernism",
    correct_answer: "Modernism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1036,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "In which literary movement did writers explore the supernatural, mysterious, and irrational aspects of human existence?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Gothic",
    delta: "Transcendentalism",
    correct_answer: "Gothic",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1037,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "Which literary movement stressed the inherent goodness of people and the importance of nature and self-reliance?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Realism",
    charlie: "Transcendentalism",
    delta: "Naturalism",
    correct_answer: "Transcendentalism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1038,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "During which period did literature often focus on the struggle between the individual and society?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Victorian",
    charlie: "Transcendentalism",
    delta: "Modernism",
    correct_answer: "Victorian",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1039,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "Which literary movement emerged in the post-World War I era, expressing disillusionment with traditional values?",
    alpha: "Romanticism",
    beta: "Victorian",
    charlie: "Modernism",
    delta: "Postmodernism",
    correct_answer: "Modernism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1040,
    quiz_id: 104,
    question: "In which literary movement did authors challenge and deconstruct traditional narrative structures and cultural norms?",
    alpha: "Realism",
    beta: "Modernism",
    charlie: "Postmodernism",
    delta: "Transcendentalism",
    correct_answer: "Postmodernism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1041,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "Which critical approach focuses on analyzing the social, political, and economic contexts of a literary work?",
    alpha: "Formalism",
    beta: "Marxist Criticism",
    charlie: "Feminist Criticism",
    delta: "Structuralism",
    correct_answer: "Marxist Criticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1042,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "In this critical approach, the analysis centers on the relationship between the text and the reader's response.",
    alpha: "Psychoanalytic Criticism",
    beta: "Reader-Response Criticism",
    charlie: "New Criticism",
    delta: "Postcolonial Criticism",
    correct_answer: "Reader-Response Criticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1043,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "Which critical approach explores how power dynamics, gender roles, and sexuality are portrayed in literature?",
    alpha: "Feminist Criticism",
    beta: "Marxist Criticism",
    charlie: "Psychoanalytic Criticism",
    delta: "Deconstruction",
    correct_answer: "Feminist Criticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1044,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "In this approach, the analysis focuses on the formal elements of a text, such as structure, language, and style.",
    alpha: "Formalism",
    beta: "Structuralism",
    charlie: "Reader-Response Criticism",
    delta: "Postmodernism",
    correct_answer: "Formalism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1045,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "Which critical approach examines the psychological motivations and unconscious desires of characters?",
    alpha: "Psychoanalytic Criticism",
    beta: "Feminist Criticism",
    charlie: "Marxist Criticism",
    delta: "Postcolonial Criticism",
    correct_answer: "Psychoanalytic Criticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1046,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "This critical approach focuses on the ways in which language shapes and constructs meaning.",
    alpha: "Deconstruction",
    beta: "Structuralism",
    charlie: "New Criticism",
    delta: "Postmodernism",
    correct_answer: "Deconstruction",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1047,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "Which critical approach emphasizes the role of colonialism, imperialism, and cultural identity in literature?",
    alpha: "Postcolonial Criticism",
    beta: "Feminist Criticism",
    charlie: "Marxist Criticism",
    delta: "Formalism",
    correct_answer: "Postcolonial Criticism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1048,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "In this approach, the focus is on the internal structures and systems within a literary work.",
    alpha: "Deconstruction",
    beta: "Structuralism",
    charlie: "Reader-Response Criticism",
    delta: "New Criticism",
    correct_answer: "Structuralism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1049,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "Which critical approach challenges traditional notions of truth and reality, often embracing ambiguity and uncertainty?",
    alpha: "Postmodernism",
    beta: "Formalism",
    charlie: "Deconstruction",
    delta: "Structuralism",
    correct_answer: "Postmodernism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1050,
    quiz_id: 105,
    question: "This critical approach aims to uncover hidden meanings and challenge binary oppositions in a text.",
    alpha: "Deconstruction",
    beta: "Psychoanalytic Criticism",
    charlie: "Reader-Response Criticism",
    delta: "Feminist Criticism",
    correct_answer: "Deconstruction",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 1051,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Identify the part of speech for the word 'happy' in the sentence: 'She felt happy after receiving the news.'",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Adjective",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1052,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "In the sentence 'They quickly ran to catch the bus,' what is the part of speech for the word 'quickly'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Adverb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1053,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Which part of speech is represented by the word 'honesty' in the sentence: 'Honesty is the best policy.'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Noun",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1054,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Identify the part of speech for the word 'sing' in the sentence: 'They love to sing together.'",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Verb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1055,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "In the phrase 'the big, red balloon,' what is the part of speech for the word 'red'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Adjective",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1056,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Which part of speech does the word 'quickly' represent in the sentence: 'She completed the task quickly.'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Adverb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1057,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Identify the part of speech for the word 'book' in the sentence: 'She read a fascinating book.'",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Noun",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1058,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "In the sentence 'The cat sat lazily on the windowsill,' what is the part of speech for the word 'lazily'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Adverb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1059,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Which part of speech is represented by the word 'laughter' in the sentence: 'Her laughter echoed through the room.'?",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Noun",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1060,
    quiz_id: 106,
    question: "Identify the part of speech for the word 'run' in the sentence: 'They love to run in the park.'",
    alpha: "Noun",
    beta: "Adjective",
    charlie: "Verb",
    delta: "Adverb",
    correct_answer: "Verb",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1061,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Identify the type of sentence: 'The sun is shining brightly.'",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Simple",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1062,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "In the sentence 'She enjoys reading and writing,' what is the sentence structure?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1063,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Which sentence structure combines independent and dependent clauses?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1064,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Identify the type of sentence: 'The cat slept on the windowsill, and the dog barked in the yard.'",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound-Complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1065,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "In the sentence 'Although it was raining, they decided to go for a walk,' what is the sentence structure?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1066,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Which sentence structure involves two or more independent clauses?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1067,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Identify the type of sentence: 'She opened the door and found a surprise waiting for her.'",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1068,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "In the sentence 'After finishing her homework, she went to bed,' what is the sentence structure?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1069,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Which sentence structure combines elements of both compound and complex sentences?",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound-Complex",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1070,
    quiz_id: 107,
    question: "Identify the type of sentence: 'She sings beautifully, and her voice captivates everyone.'",
    alpha: "Simple",
    beta: "Compound",
    charlie: "Complex",
    delta: "Compound-Complex",
    correct_answer: "Compound",
    selected_option: null,
  },

  {
    question_id: 1071,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Which punctuation mark is used to indicate the end of a declarative or imperative sentence?",
    alpha: "Comma",
    beta: "Semicolon",
    charlie: "Period",
    delta: "Exclamation Mark",
    correct_answer: "Period",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1072,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "In the sentence 'I enjoy reading, hiking, and cooking,' what punctuation mark is used to separate items in a list?",
    alpha: "Colon",
    beta: "Semicolon",
    charlie: "Comma",
    delta: "Hyphen",
    correct_answer: "Comma",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1073,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Which punctuation mark is used to indicate possession?",
    alpha: "Apostrophe",
    beta: "Quotation Mark",
    charlie: "Colon",
    delta: "Hyphen",
    correct_answer: "Apostrophe",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1074,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Identify the correct use of the semicolon in the sentence: 'She finished the project; then, she submitted it.'",
    alpha: "Between items in a list",
    beta: "To join independent clauses",
    charlie: "To separate introductory elements",
    delta: "To indicate a pause",
    correct_answer: "To join independent clauses",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1075,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "In the sentence 'The book is on the shelf; I'll get it later,' what punctuation mark is used to indicate a break between related independent clauses?",
    alpha: "Colon",
    beta: "Comma",
    charlie: "Apostrophe",
    delta: "Semicolon",
    correct_answer: "Semicolon",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1076,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Which punctuation mark is used to set off a quotation within a sentence?",
    alpha: "Comma",
    beta: "Apostrophe",
    charlie: "Quotation Mark",
    delta: "Hyphen",
    correct_answer: "Quotation Mark",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1077,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Identify the correct use of the apostrophe in the sentence: 'The cat's tail was fluffy.'",
    alpha: "To indicate possession",
    beta: "To indicate a contraction",
    charlie: "To form a plural",
    delta: "To set off a quotation",
    correct_answer: "To indicate possession",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1078,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Which punctuation mark is used to indicate a pause or a brief break within a sentence?",
    alpha: "Period",
    beta: "Comma",
    charlie: "Semicolon",
    delta: "Dash",
    correct_answer: "Dash",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1079,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "In the sentence 'The meeting is scheduled for Monday, March 15, 2022,' what punctuation marks are used to set off the date?",
    alpha: "Commas",
    beta: "Colons",
    charlie: "Apostrophes",
    delta: "Hyphens",
    correct_answer: "Commas",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1080,
    quiz_id: 108,
    question: "Which punctuation mark is used to indicate a sudden break or change in thought within a sentence?",
    alpha: "Colon",
    beta: "Semicolon",
    charlie: "Dash",
    delta: "Period",
    correct_answer: "Dash",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1081,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Choose the correct verb tense: 'She ___ to the store yesterday.'",
    alpha: "Goes",
    beta: "Going",
    charlie: "Go",
    delta: "Went",
    correct_answer: "Went",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1082,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "In the sentence 'The students ___ diligently for the exam,' which verb form is correct?",
    alpha: "Study",
    beta: "Studied",
    charlie: "Studying",
    delta: "Studies",
    correct_answer: "Studied",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1083,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Which sentence has the correct subject-verb agreement: 'The team of players ___ on the field.'",
    alpha: "Is",
    beta: "Are",
    charlie: "Am",
    delta: "Be",
    correct_answer: "Is",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1084,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Identify the correct verb form: 'He ___ a book every weekend.'",
    alpha: "Reads",
    beta: "Reading",
    charlie: "Read",
    delta: "To read",
    correct_answer: "Reads",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1085,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Choose the sentence with the correct verb tense: 'I ___ my keys at home this morning.'",
    alpha: "Forget",
    beta: "Forgets",
    charlie: "Forgot",
    delta: "Forgotten",
    correct_answer: "Forgot",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1086,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "In the sentence 'The cat and the dog ___ peacefully,' which verb form is correct?",
    alpha: "Sleep",
    beta: "Sleeps",
    charlie: "Sleeping",
    delta: "Slept",
    correct_answer: "Slept",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1087,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Which sentence has the correct subject-verb agreement: 'The group of friends ___ going to the party.'",
    alpha: "Is",
    beta: "Are",
    charlie: "Am",
    delta: "Be",
    correct_answer: "Is",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1088,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Identify the correct verb form: 'She ___ her lunch at noon every day.'",
    alpha: "Eats",
    beta: "Eat",
    charlie: "Eaten",
    delta: "Eating",
    correct_answer: "Eats",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1089,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "Choose the sentence with the correct verb tense: 'They ___ to the concert last night.'",
    alpha: "Goes",
    beta: "Go",
    charlie: "Going",
    delta: "Went",
    correct_answer: "Went",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1090,
    quiz_id: 109,
    question: "In the sentence 'The flowers ___ beautiful in the garden,' which verb form is correct?",
    alpha: "Is",
    beta: "Be",
    charlie: "Am",
    delta: "Are",
    correct_answer: "Are",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1091,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Select the correct sentence: 'He don't like coffee' or 'He doesn't like coffee'?",
    alpha: "He don't like coffee",
    beta: "He doesn't like coffee",
    charlie: "He not like coffee",
    delta: "He not likes coffee",
    correct_answer: "He doesn't like coffee",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1092,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Choose the correct use of the apostrophe: 'The cats tail' or 'The cat's tail'?",
    alpha: "The cats tail",
    beta: "The cat's tail",
    charlie: "The cats' tail",
    delta: "The cat tail",
    correct_answer: "The cat's tail",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1093,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Which sentence is grammatically correct: 'She don't have time' or 'She doesn't have time'?",
    alpha: "She don't have time",
    beta: "She doesn't have time",
    charlie: "She not have time",
    delta: "She no have time",
    correct_answer: "She doesn't have time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1094,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Identify the correct usage of 'your' and 'you're': 'Your going to love it' or 'You're going to love it'?",
    alpha: "Your going to love it",
    beta: "You're going to love it",
    charlie: "You're going too love it",
    delta: "You are going to love it",
    correct_answer: "You're going to love it",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1095,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence: 'Their going to the park' or 'They're going to the park'?",
    alpha: "Their going to the park",
    beta: "They're going to the park",
    charlie: "They going to the park",
    delta: "They are going to the park",
    correct_answer: "They're going to the park",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1096,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Select the grammatically correct sentence: 'Its a beautiful day' or 'It's a beautiful day'?",
    alpha: "Its a beautiful day",
    beta: "It's a beautiful day",
    charlie: "Its a beautiful day outside",
    delta: "It is a beautiful day",
    correct_answer: "It's a beautiful day",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1097,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence: 'Whose going to the party?' or 'Who's going to the party'?",
    alpha: "Whose going to the party?",
    beta: "Who's going to the party",
    charlie: "Whos going to the party",
    delta: "Whose going to the party",
    correct_answer: "Who's going to the party",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1098,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Identify the correct sentence: 'I seen that movie before' or 'I've seen that movie before'?",
    alpha: "I seen that movie before",
    beta: "I've seen that movie before",
    charlie: "I have seen that movie before",
    delta: "I saw that movie before",
    correct_answer: "I've seen that movie before",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1099,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Which sentence is grammatically correct: 'He talks louder than me' or 'He talks louder than I'?",
    alpha: "He talks louder than me",
    beta: "He talks louder than I",
    charlie: "He talks louder then me",
    delta: "He talks louder than myself",
    correct_answer: "He talks louder than I",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1100,
    quiz_id: 110,
    question: "Choose the correct usage of 'its' and 'it's': 'Its a great idea' or 'It's a great idea'?",
    alpha: "Its a great idea",
    beta: "It's a great idea",
    charlie: "Its a good idea",
    delta: "It is a great idea",
    correct_answer: "It's a great idea",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1101,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "Which writing technique involves the use of vivid and descriptive language to create a mental image for the reader?",
    alpha: "Exposition",
    beta: "Imagery",
    charlie: "Flashback",
    delta: "Foreshadowing",
    correct_answer: "Imagery",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1102,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "In which writing style does the author express personal thoughts, feelings, and experiences?",
    alpha: "Descriptive",
    beta: "Narrative",
    charlie: "Persuasive",
    delta: "Reflective",
    correct_answer: "Reflective",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1103,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "Which writing technique involves providing background information to enhance understanding of the main idea?",
    alpha: "Dialogue",
    beta: "Foreshadowing",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Flashback",
    correct_answer: "Exposition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1104,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "In which writing style does the author attempt to convince the reader to adopt a particular viewpoint or take a specific action?",
    alpha: "Descriptive",
    beta: "Narrative",
    charlie: "Persuasive",
    delta: "Reflective",
    correct_answer: "Persuasive",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1105,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "Which writing technique involves hinting at future events to build anticipation in the reader?",
    alpha: "Dialogue",
    beta: "Foreshadowing",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Flashback",
    correct_answer: "Foreshadowing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1106,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "In which writing style does the author present a sequence of events, often in chronological order?",
    alpha: "Descriptive",
    beta: "Narrative",
    charlie: "Persuasive",
    delta: "Reflective",
    correct_answer: "Narrative",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1107,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "Which writing technique involves a conversation between characters to convey information and develop the plot?",
    alpha: "Imagery",
    beta: "Dialogue",
    charlie: "Flashback",
    delta: "Foreshadowing",
    correct_answer: "Dialogue",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1108,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "In which writing style does the author use sensory details to create a vivid and detailed portrayal of a scene or subject?",
    alpha: "Descriptive",
    beta: "Narrative",
    charlie: "Persuasive",
    delta: "Reflective",
    correct_answer: "Descriptive",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1109,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "Which writing technique involves a scene or event from the past to provide context or background information?",
    alpha: "Dialogue",
    beta: "Foreshadowing",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Flashback",
    correct_answer: "Flashback",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1110,
    quiz_id: 111,
    question: "In which writing style does the author aim to create a strong emotional response from the reader?",
    alpha: "Descriptive",
    beta: "Narrative",
    charlie: "Persuasive",
    delta: "Reflective",
    correct_answer: "Persuasive",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1111,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "What term refers to the internal changes a character undergoes throughout a story?",
    alpha: "Plot",
    beta: "Conflict",
    charlie: "Setting",
    delta: "Character Arc",
    correct_answer: "Character Arc",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1112,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "Which literary element involves the revelation of a character's traits, personality, and motivations?",
    alpha: "Conflict",
    beta: "Setting",
    charlie: "Characterization",
    delta: "Theme",
    correct_answer: "Characterization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1113,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "In a story, what term describes the central character who undergoes significant changes?",
    alpha: "Antagonist",
    beta: "Protagonist",
    charlie: "Static Character",
    delta: "Dynamic Character",
    correct_answer: "Dynamic Character",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1114,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "Which type of character remains unchanged throughout the story and does not experience significant development?",
    alpha: "Antagonist",
    beta: "Protagonist",
    charlie: "Static Character",
    delta: "Dynamic Character",
    correct_answer: "Static Character",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1115,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "What term refers to the external events and situations that shape a character's development?",
    alpha: "Character Arc",
    beta: "Conflict",
    charlie: "Foreshadowing",
    delta: "Resolution",
    correct_answer: "Conflict",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1116,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "Which type of character is in opposition to the main character and often creates conflict?",
    alpha: "Protagonist",
    beta: "Antagonist",
    charlie: "Static Character",
    delta: "Dynamic Character",
    correct_answer: "Antagonist",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1117,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "What technique involves providing hints or clues about events that will happen later in the story?",
    alpha: "Characterization",
    beta: "Setting",
    charlie: "Foreshadowing",
    delta: "Flashback",
    correct_answer: "Foreshadowing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1118,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "In character development, what does the term 'backstory' refer to?",
    alpha: "The central conflict",
    beta: "The character's past",
    charlie: "The story's setting",
    delta: "The resolution",
    correct_answer: "The character's past",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1119,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "What term describes the final outcome or solution to the main conflict in a story?",
    alpha: "Climax",
    beta: "Resolution",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Rising Action",
    correct_answer: "Resolution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1120,
    quiz_id: 112,
    question: "Which term refers to the emotional or moral message conveyed by a story?",
    alpha: "Conflict",
    beta: "Character Arc",
    charlie: "Theme",
    delta: "Setting",
    correct_answer: "Theme",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1121,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "What is the sequence of events that make up the structure of a story called?",
    alpha: "Setting",
    beta: "Conflict",
    charlie: "Character Arc",
    delta: "Plot",
    correct_answer: "Plot",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1122,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "Which part of the plot introduces the characters, setting, and basic situation of a story?",
    alpha: "Climax",
    beta: "Exposition",
    charlie: "Rising Action",
    delta: "Resolution",
    correct_answer: "Exposition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1123,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "In a story, what is the term for the events leading up to the climax?",
    alpha: "Exposition",
    beta: "Climax",
    charlie: "Rising Action",
    delta: "Falling Action",
    correct_answer: "Rising Action",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1124,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "Which part of the plot is the turning point or the moment of greatest intensity in a story?",
    alpha: "Exposition",
    beta: "Climax",
    charlie: "Rising Action",
    delta: "Resolution",
    correct_answer: "Climax",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1125,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "What follows the climax in a story and leads to the resolution?",
    alpha: "Exposition",
    beta: "Climax",
    charlie: "Rising Action",
    delta: "Falling Action",
    correct_answer: "Falling Action",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1126,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "Which term refers to the final outcome or solution to the main conflict in a story?",
    alpha: "Climax",
    beta: "Resolution",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Rising Action",
    correct_answer: "Resolution",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1127,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "In literature, what is the struggle between opposing forces that drives the plot?",
    alpha: "Climax",
    beta: "Resolution",
    charlie: "Exposition",
    delta: "Conflict",
    correct_answer: "Conflict",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1128,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "Which type of conflict involves a character's struggle against an external force or another character?",
    alpha: "Internal Conflict",
    beta: "Man vs. Nature",
    charlie: "Man vs. Society",
    delta: "External Conflict",
    correct_answer: "External Conflict",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1129,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "In literature, what type of conflict is a character's struggle with their own thoughts, feelings, or choices?",
    alpha: "Internal Conflict",
    beta: "Man vs. Nature",
    charlie: "Man vs. Society",
    delta: "External Conflict",
    correct_answer: "Internal Conflict",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1130,
    quiz_id: 113,
    question: "Which type of conflict involves a character's struggle against the laws or beliefs of a group?",
    alpha: "Internal Conflict",
    beta: "Man vs. Nature",
    charlie: "Man vs. Society",
    delta: "External Conflict",
    correct_answer: "Man vs. Society",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1131,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "What term refers to the time and place in which a story takes place?",
    alpha: "Conflict",
    beta: "Plot",
    charlie: "Setting",
    delta: "Atmosphere",
    correct_answer: "Setting",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1132,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "Which element of setting involves the physical location, such as a city, country, or building?",
    alpha: "Time",
    beta: "Place",
    charlie: "Weather",
    delta: "Atmosphere",
    correct_answer: "Place",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1133,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "In literature, what term refers to the overall feeling or mood created by a story?",
    alpha: "Conflict",
    beta: "Plot",
    charlie: "Setting",
    delta: "Atmosphere",
    correct_answer: "Atmosphere",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1134,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "Which element of setting involves the specific era or time period in which a story takes place?",
    alpha: "Time",
    beta: "Place",
    charlie: "Weather",
    delta: "Atmosphere",
    correct_answer: "Time",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1135,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "In a story, how does the weather contribute to the atmosphere?",
    alpha: "It affects the characters' emotions",
    beta: "It determines the plot",
    charlie: "It establishes the setting",
    delta: "It creates suspense",
    correct_answer: "It affects the characters' emotions",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1136,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "Which element of setting involves the season, time of day, and climate in a story?",
    alpha: "Time",
    beta: "Place",
    charlie: "Weather",
    delta: "Atmosphere",
    correct_answer: "Weather",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1137,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "How does the choice of setting contribute to the overall atmosphere of a horror story?",
    alpha: "By creating a joyful mood",
    beta: "By providing comic relief",
    charlie: "By evoking fear and tension",
    delta: "By introducing romance",
    correct_answer: "By evoking fear and tension",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1138,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "In literature, what role does the setting play in enhancing the reader's understanding of the characters and events?",
    alpha: "It has no impact",
    beta: "It serves as a distraction",
    charlie: "It is irrelevant",
    delta: "It provides context and background",
    correct_answer: "It provides context and background",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1139,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "Which term refers to the emotional response and feelings evoked in the reader by a story's atmosphere?",
    alpha: "Conflict",
    beta: "Mood",
    charlie: "Setting",
    delta: "Tone",
    correct_answer: "Mood",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1140,
    quiz_id: 114,
    question: "How can a vivid and detailed setting contribute to the overall quality of a narrative?",
    alpha: "It confuses the reader",
    beta: "It slows down the plot",
    charlie: "It adds complexity to the characters",
    delta: "It immerses the reader in the story",
    correct_answer: "It immerses the reader in the story",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1141,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "What is the process of reviewing and making changes to improve the overall quality of a written work?",
    alpha: "Drafting",
    beta: "Editing",
    charlie: "Revising",
    delta: "Proofreading",
    correct_answer: "Revising",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1142,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "Which stage of the writing process involves checking for errors in grammar, punctuation, and spelling?",
    alpha: "Drafting",
    beta: "Editing",
    charlie: "Revising",
    delta: "Proofreading",
    correct_answer: "Proofreading",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1143,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "What does the process of editing primarily focus on?",
    alpha: "Improving clarity and coherence",
    beta: "Checking for typos",
    charlie: "Adding new content",
    delta: "Developing the plot",
    correct_answer: "Improving clarity and coherence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1144,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "In the revision process, what is the writer's goal when restructuring sentences or paragraphs?",
    alpha: "To increase word count",
    beta: "To remove all details",
    charlie: "To improve flow and organization",
    delta: "To add unnecessary information",
    correct_answer: "To improve flow and organization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1145,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "Which activity is part of the proofreading stage in writing?",
    alpha: "Rearranging paragraphs",
    beta: "Adding new ideas",
    charlie: "Checking for spelling errors",
    delta: "Developing characters",
    correct_answer: "Checking for spelling errors",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1146,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "During the revision process, what should writers focus on when evaluating the clarity of their writing?",
    alpha: "Adding complex vocabulary",
    beta: "Ensuring the use of jargon",
    charlie: "Removing unnecessary details",
    delta: "Enhancing sentence structure and coherence",
    correct_answer: "Enhancing sentence structure and coherence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1147,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "What is a common purpose of the revision process in writing?",
    alpha: "To create the first draft",
    beta: "To fix typographical errors",
    charlie: "To develop new ideas",
    delta: "To refine and clarify the message",
    correct_answer: "To refine and clarify the message",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1148,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "What should a writer consider when deciding whether to keep or delete a particular sentence during the revision process?",
    alpha: "The length of the sentence",
    beta: "Whether the sentence includes a question",
    charlie: "The overall theme of the writing",
    delta: "The writer's favorite sentence",
    correct_answer: "The overall theme of the writing",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1149,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of proofreading in the writing process?",
    alpha: "To generate new ideas",
    beta: "To fix grammatical errors",
    charlie: "To revise and reorganize",
    delta: "To create the first draft",
    correct_answer: "To fix grammatical errors",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1150,
    quiz_id: 115,
    question: "During the editing process, what does a writer focus on when assessing the overall structure and organization of a piece?",
    alpha: "Individual word choice",
    beta: "Grammar and punctuation",
    charlie: "Clarity and coherence",
    delta: "Flow and organization",
    correct_answer: "Flow and organization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1151,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "What is the term for a 14-line poem, typically written in iambic pentameter, with various rhyme schemes?",
    alpha: "Sonnet",
    beta: "Haiku",
    charlie: "Limerick",
    delta: "Free Verse",
    correct_answer: "Sonnet",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1152,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "In poetry, what is the term for a three-line stanza, often with a specific rhyme scheme?",
    alpha: "Quatrain",
    beta: "Couplet",
    charlie: "Tercet",
    delta: "Octave",
    correct_answer: "Tercet",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1153,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "Which poetic form consists of five lines with a specific syllable count per line (2-4-6-8-2) and a rhyme scheme?",
    alpha: "Villanelle",
    beta: "Haiku",
    charlie: "Cinquain",
    delta: "Limerick",
    correct_answer: "Cinquain",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1154,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "What is a poem with 10 lines, often written in iambic pentameter with a specific rhyme scheme?",
    alpha: "Sonnet",
    beta: "Quatrain",
    charlie: "Octave",
    delta: "Rondeau",
    correct_answer: "Sonnet",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1155,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "In poetry, what is a fixed verse form with 19 lines, divided into five tercets followed by a final quatrain?",
    alpha: "Sestina",
    beta: "Rondeau",
    charlie: "Villanelle",
    delta: "Pantoum",
    correct_answer: "Villanelle",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1156,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "Which poetic form consists of 17 syllables in a 5-7-5 pattern and often captures a moment in nature?",
    alpha: "Sonnet",
    beta: "Haiku",
    charlie: "Limerick",
    delta: "Free Verse",
    correct_answer: "Haiku",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1157,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "What is a humorous, often nonsensical, five-line poem with a specific rhyme scheme (AABBA)?",
    alpha: "Sonnet",
    beta: "Haiku",
    charlie: "Limerick",
    delta: "Free Verse",
    correct_answer: "Limerick",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1158,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "In poetry, what is a fixed form with 39 lines, organized into six stanzas of six lines each, and a final three-line stanza?",
    alpha: "Sestina",
    beta: "Rondeau",
    charlie: "Villanelle",
    delta: "Pantoum",
    correct_answer: "Sestina",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1159,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "What is the term for a form of poetry that does not have a regular meter, rhyme scheme, or form?",
    alpha: "Blank Verse",
    beta: "Free Verse",
    charlie: "Rhymed Verse",
    delta: "Prose Poem",
    correct_answer: "Free Verse",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1160,
    quiz_id: 116,
    question: "What is a fixed verse form with 13 lines, typically divided into three stanzas (8-3-2) with a specific rhyme scheme?",
    alpha: "Sonnet",
    beta: "Rondeau",
    charlie: "Villanelle",
    delta: "Terza Rima",
    correct_answer: "Rondeau",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1161,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "What is the figurative language technique that involves a direct comparison between two unlike things using 'like' or 'as'?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Simile",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1162,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "In figurative language, what term is used to describe the attribution of human qualities to non-human entities?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Personification",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1163,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "Which figurative language technique involves exaggeration for emphasis or effect?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Hyperbole",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1164,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "What is the term for the use of words that imitate the sounds associated with the objects or actions they refer to?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Onomatopoeia",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1165,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "Which figurative language technique involves giving inanimate objects or abstract concepts human characteristics?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Personification",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1166,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "In figurative language, what is the term for a comparison between two unlike things without using 'like' or 'as'?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Metaphor",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1167,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "Which figurative language technique involves the use of words that appeal to the senses and create a vivid mental image?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Imagery",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1168,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "What is the term for the repetition of consonant sounds at the beginning of words in close proximity?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Rhyme",
    correct_answer: "Alliteration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1169,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "Which figurative language technique involves the use of contradictory terms or ideas to create a paradoxical effect?",
    alpha: "Oxymoron",
    beta: "Paradox",
    charlie: "Irony",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Oxymoron",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1170,
    quiz_id: 117,
    question: "In figurative language, what term is used to describe the repetition of vowel sounds within nearby words?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Rhyme",
    correct_answer: "Assonance",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1171,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "What is the term for the repetition of consonant sounds at the beginning of words in close proximity?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Rhyme",
    correct_answer: "Alliteration",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1172,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "Which poetic device involves the repetition of a word or phrase at the beginning of successive lines or clauses?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Anaphora",
    charlie: "Simile",
    delta: "Metaphor",
    correct_answer: "Anaphora",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1173,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "What is the term for the deliberate use of a word or phrase to create a specific sound effect?",
    alpha: "Onomatopoeia",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Euphony",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1174,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "Which poetic device involves the use of words that imitate the sounds associated with the objects or actions they refer to?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Onomatopoeia",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1175,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "What is the term for the use of words that appeal to the senses and create a vivid mental image?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Imagery",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1176,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "In poetry, what is the term for a comparison between two unlike things without using 'like' or 'as'?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Simile",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Metaphor",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1177,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "Which poetic device involves the use of contradictory terms or ideas to create a paradoxical effect?",
    alpha: "Oxymoron",
    beta: "Paradox",
    charlie: "Irony",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Oxymoron",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1178,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "What is the term for the use of language that appeals to the emotions and creates an emotional impact?",
    alpha: "Pathos",
    beta: "Logos",
    charlie: "Ethos",
    delta: "Rhetoric",
    correct_answer: "Pathos",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1179,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "In poetry, what is the term for the deliberate arrangement of words to create a specific effect?",
    alpha: "Syntax",
    beta: "Semantics",
    charlie: "Grammar",
    delta: "Diction",
    correct_answer: "Syntax",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1180,
    quiz_id: 118,
    question: "Which poetic device involves the use of words with similar vowel sounds within close proximity?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Rhyme",
    correct_answer: "Assonance",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1181,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Which poet is known for his works such as 'The Raven' and 'The Tell-Tale Heart' and is a master of macabre and Gothic literature?",
    alpha: "Emily Dickinson",
    beta: "Walt Whitman",
    charlie: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    delta: "Langston Hughes",
    correct_answer: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1182,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Who is often referred to as the 'Bard of Avon' and is widely regarded as one of the greatest playwrights and poets in the English language?",
    alpha: "William Wordsworth",
    beta: "William Shakespeare",
    charlie: "John Keats",
    delta: "Robert Frost",
    correct_answer: "William Shakespeare",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1183,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Which American poet is associated with transcendentalism and is known for works like 'Song of Myself' and 'Leaves of Grass'?",
    alpha: "Emily Dickinson",
    beta: "Walt Whitman",
    charlie: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    delta: "Langston Hughes",
    correct_answer: "Walt Whitman",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1184,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Who is considered one of the leading figures of the Harlem Renaissance and wrote poems like 'The Negro Speaks of Rivers'?",
    alpha: "Emily Dickinson",
    beta: "Walt Whitman",
    charlie: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    delta: "Langston Hughes",
    correct_answer: "Langston Hughes",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1185,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Which Romantic poet is known for works such as 'Ode to a Nightingale' and 'Ode to a Grecian Urn'?",
    alpha: "William Wordsworth",
    beta: "William Blake",
    charlie: "John Keats",
    delta: "Robert Frost",
    correct_answer: "John Keats",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1186,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Who wrote the epic poem 'Paradise Lost' and is regarded as one of the greatest English poets?",
    alpha: "John Milton",
    beta: "Alexander Pope",
    charlie: "Geoffrey Chaucer",
    delta: "Samuel Taylor Coleridge",
    correct_answer: "John Milton",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1187,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Which poet is associated with the Romantic movement and wrote 'The Rime of the Ancient Mariner'?",
    alpha: "William Wordsworth",
    beta: "William Blake",
    charlie: "John Keats",
    delta: "Samuel Taylor Coleridge",
    correct_answer: "Samuel Taylor Coleridge",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1188,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Who is known for her unconventional style and reclusive lifestyle, and wrote poems such as 'Because I could not stop for Death'?",
    alpha: "Emily Dickinson",
    beta: "Walt Whitman",
    charlie: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    delta: "Langston Hughes",
    correct_answer: "Emily Dickinson",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1189,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Which poet is often associated with the Romantic movement and wrote 'The Tyger' and 'Songs of Innocence and Experience'?",
    alpha: "William Wordsworth",
    beta: "William Blake",
    charlie: "John Keats",
    delta: "Robert Frost",
    correct_answer: "William Blake",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1190,
    quiz_id: 119,
    question: "Who is known for his rural and pastoral themes, and wrote poems like 'The Road Not Taken' and 'Stopping by Woods on a Snowy Evening'?",
    alpha: "William Wordsworth",
    beta: "Walt Whitman",
    charlie: "Edgar Allan Poe",
    delta: "Robert Frost",
    correct_answer: "Robert Frost",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1191,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "What is the term for the overall emotional atmosphere or feeling created by a poem?",
    alpha: "Theme",
    beta: "Mood",
    charlie: "Tone",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Mood",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1192,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "Which term refers to the central idea or underlying message of a poem?",
    alpha: "Theme",
    beta: "Mood",
    charlie: "Tone",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Theme",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1193,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "What is the term for the poet's attitude toward the subject or audience, conveyed through language and style?",
    alpha: "Theme",
    beta: "Mood",
    charlie: "Tone",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Tone",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1194,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "Which term refers to the use of language to evoke sensory experiences and create vivid mental images?",
    alpha: "Theme",
    beta: "Mood",
    charlie: "Tone",
    delta: "Imagery",
    correct_answer: "Imagery",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1195,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "What is the term for the repetition of sounds at the end of words, typically in the final syllables?",
    alpha: "Alliteration",
    beta: "Assonance",
    charlie: "Consonance",
    delta: "Rhyme",
    correct_answer: "Rhyme",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1196,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "Which term refers to the pattern of stressed and unstressed syllables in a line of poetry?",
    alpha: "Rhyme",
    beta: "Meter",
    charlie: "Imagery",
    delta: "Enjambment",
    correct_answer: "Meter",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1197,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "What is the term for the continuation of a sentence without a pause beyond the end of a line, stanza, or verse?",
    alpha: "Rhyme",
    beta: "Meter",
    charlie: "Imagery",
    delta: "Enjambment",
    correct_answer: "Enjambment",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1198,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "Which term refers to the use of a word or phrase to represent something beyond its literal meaning?",
    alpha: "Symbolism",
    beta: "Metaphor",
    charlie: "Simile",
    delta: "Personification",
    correct_answer: "Symbolism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1199,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "What is the term for the use of words that imitate the sounds associated with the objects or actions they refer to?",
    alpha: "Metaphor",
    beta: "Onomatopoeia",
    charlie: "Personification",
    delta: "Hyperbole",
    correct_answer: "Onomatopoeia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1200,
    quiz_id: 120,
    question: "Which term refers to the deliberate arrangement of words to create a specific effect?",
    alpha: "Syntax",
    beta: "Semantics",
    charlie: "Grammar",
    delta: "Diction",
    correct_answer: "Syntax",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1201,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "What term refers to the coexistence of multiple languages within a particular community or country?",
    alpha: "Bilingualism",
    beta: "Monolingualism",
    charlie: "Multilingualism",
    delta: "Polylingualism",
    correct_answer: "Multilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1202,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "Which linguistic term describes the process by which a person or community adopts a second language for communication?",
    alpha: "Acculturation",
    beta: "Assimilation",
    charlie: "Code-switching",
    delta: "Language acquisition",
    correct_answer: "Language acquisition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1203,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "What is the term for a language that is spoken as a native language by a specific ethnic or cultural group?",
    alpha: "Official language",
    beta: "Second language",
    charlie: "Mother tongue",
    delta: "Lingua franca",
    correct_answer: "Mother tongue",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1204,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "Which linguistic term refers to the process of blending or mixing elements of two or more languages within communication?",
    alpha: "Bilingualism",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Creole",
    correct_answer: "Code-switching",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1205,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "What is the term for a simplified language that develops as a means of communication between two or more groups with no common language?",
    alpha: "Pidgin",
    beta: "Dialect",
    charlie: "Slang",
    delta: "Jargon",
    correct_answer: "Pidgin",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1206,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "Which linguistic term refers to the use of language varieties associated with particular social groups or situations?",
    alpha: "Dialect",
    beta: "Creole",
    charlie: "Slang",
    delta: "Jargon",
    correct_answer: "Slang",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1207,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "What is the term for a form of a language that is spoken in a specific geographic area or by a particular social group?",
    alpha: "Official language",
    beta: "Creole",
    charlie: "Dialect",
    delta: "Lingua franca",
    correct_answer: "Dialect",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1208,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "Which linguistic term describes the use of language varieties in different social contexts or situations?",
    alpha: "Diglossia",
    beta: "Bilingualism",
    charlie: "Monolingualism",
    delta: "Multilingualism",
    correct_answer: "Diglossia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1209,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "What is the term for a language that is adopted as a common language between speakers whose native languages are different?",
    alpha: "Official language",
    beta: "Second language",
    charlie: "Mother tongue",
    delta: "Lingua franca",
    correct_answer: "Lingua franca",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1210,
    quiz_id: 121,
    question: "Which linguistic term refers to the process of gradual cultural and linguistic exchange between different language communities?",
    alpha: "Acculturation",
    beta: "Assimilation",
    charlie: "Language shift",
    delta: "Language contact",
    correct_answer: "Language contact",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1211,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "What is the term for the study of the relationship between language and society, including how language varies and changes in different social groups?",
    alpha: "Phonetics",
    beta: "Syntax",
    charlie: "Semantics",
    delta: "Sociolinguistics",
    correct_answer: "Sociolinguistics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1212,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "Which concept in sociolinguistics refers to the use of language to convey a speaker's social identity and group membership?",
    alpha: "Code-switching",
    beta: "Diglossia",
    charlie: "Language shift",
    delta: "Indexicality",
    correct_answer: "Indexicality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1213,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where speakers alter their language based on the social characteristics of their audience or interlocutors?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Convergence",
    correct_answer: "Convergence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1214,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "Which sociolinguistic concept describes the process by which a speaker gradually adopts the language of a different social group?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Convergence",
    delta: "Divergence",
    correct_answer: "Language shift",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1215,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "What is the term for the use of more than one language or dialect in conversation?",
    alpha: "Bilingualism",
    beta: "Monolingualism",
    charlie: "Multilingualism",
    delta: "Code-switching",
    correct_answer: "Code-switching",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1216,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "Which sociolinguistic phenomenon occurs when speakers use a formal variety of language in certain situations and an informal variety in others?",
    alpha: "Diglossia",
    beta: "Convergence",
    charlie: "Divergence",
    delta: "Code-switching",
    correct_answer: "Diglossia",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1217,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "What is the term for the phenomenon where speakers alter their language to make it more similar to that of their interlocutors?",
    alpha: "Divergence",
    beta: "Convergence",
    charlie: "Language shift",
    delta: "Code-switching",
    correct_answer: "Convergence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1218,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "Which sociolinguistic concept refers to the social and cultural associations linked to a particular linguistic form or variation?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Indexicality",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Convergence",
    correct_answer: "Indexicality",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1219,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "What is the term for the situation where two or more languages or dialects are used by a single community or speaker?",
    alpha: "Bilingualism",
    beta: "Monolingualism",
    charlie: "Multilingualism",
    delta: "Code-switching",
    correct_answer: "Multilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1220,
    quiz_id: 122,
    question: "Which sociolinguistic concept involves the use of language to differentiate oneself from a particular social group or identity?",
    alpha: "Convergence",
    beta: "Divergence",
    charlie: "Language shift",
    delta: "Indexicality",
    correct_answer: "Divergence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1221,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "What is the term for the process by which humans acquire the capacity to perceive and produce language?",
    alpha: "Linguistic immersion",
    beta: "Bilingualism",
    charlie: "Language acquisition",
    delta: "Syntax development",
    correct_answer: "Language acquisition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1222,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "At what age does the critical period for language acquisition typically end?",
    alpha: "2 years",
    beta: "5 years",
    charlie: "10 years",
    delta: "15 years",
    correct_answer: "5 years",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1223,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "Which theory of language acquisition suggests that innate biological factors play a crucial role in language development?",
    alpha: "Behaviorist theory",
    beta: "Cognitive theory",
    charlie: "Social learning theory",
    delta: "Nativist theory",
    correct_answer: "Nativist theory",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1224,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "Who proposed the theory of Universal Grammar, suggesting that humans are born with an innate ability to acquire language?",
    alpha: "B.F. Skinner",
    beta: "Jean Piaget",
    charlie: "Noam Chomsky",
    delta: "Lev Vygotsky",
    correct_answer: "Noam Chomsky",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1225,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "What is the term for the stage in language development when a child starts to produce meaningful words and short phrases?",
    alpha: "Telegraphic stage",
    beta: "Babbling stage",
    charlie: "Holophrastic stage",
    delta: "Overgeneralization stage",
    correct_answer: "Holophrastic stage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1226,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "Which term describes the use of a single word to convey a complete thought or idea during early language development?",
    alpha: "Telegraphic speech",
    beta: "Holophrasis",
    charlie: "Babbling",
    delta: "Overgeneralization",
    correct_answer: "Holophrasis",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1227,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "According to behaviorist theories, what is the primary influence on language acquisition?",
    alpha: "Innate ability",
    beta: "Cognitive development",
    charlie: "Environmental stimuli",
    delta: "Critical period",
    correct_answer: "Environmental stimuli",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1228,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "What is the term for the stage in language development when a child begins to produce two-word combinations?",
    alpha: "Telegraphic stage",
    beta: "Babbling stage",
    charlie: "Holophrastic stage",
    delta: "Two-word stage",
    correct_answer: "Two-word stage",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1229,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "Which theory emphasizes the role of social interaction and cultural context in language development?",
    alpha: "Behaviorist theory",
    beta: "Cognitive theory",
    charlie: "Social learning theory",
    delta: "Sociocultural theory",
    correct_answer: "Sociocultural theory",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1230,
    quiz_id: 123,
    question: "What is the term for the overapplication of grammar rules, such as using 'goed' instead of 'went' during language development?",
    alpha: "Telegraphic speech",
    beta: "Holophrasis",
    charlie: "Babbling",
    delta: "Overgeneralization",
    correct_answer: "Overgeneralization",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1231,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "What is the term for the study of how cultural factors influence language, including vocabulary, grammar, and communication styles?",
    alpha: "Cultural linguistics",
    beta: "Sociolinguistics",
    charlie: "Linguistic anthropology",
    delta: "Cross-cultural semantics",
    correct_answer: "Cultural linguistics",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1232,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "Which term refers to words or expressions that are unique to a particular language or culture and may not have an equivalent in other languages?",
    alpha: "Idioms",
    beta: "Dialects",
    charlie: "Cognates",
    delta: "Cultural markers",
    correct_answer: "Idioms",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1233,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "What is the term for the process of adapting words from one language into another, often with adjustments to pronunciation or spelling?",
    alpha: "Translation",
    beta: "Transculturation",
    charlie: "Transliteration",
    delta: "Transcreation",
    correct_answer: "Transculturation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1234,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "Which cultural concept refers to the practice of using more than one language in the course of daily life?",
    alpha: "Biculturalism",
    beta: "Multiculturalism",
    charlie: "Bilingualism",
    delta: "Translingualism",
    correct_answer: "Bilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1235,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "What is the term for the ability to understand and adapt to different cultural communication styles and norms?",
    alpha: "Cultural empathy",
    beta: "Cultural assimilation",
    charlie: "Cultural fluency",
    delta: "Cultural relativism",
    correct_answer: "Cultural fluency",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1236,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "Which term refers to the practice of using elements from different cultures to create a new cultural product or expression?",
    alpha: "Cultural appropriation",
    beta: "Cultural assimilation",
    charlie: "Cultural hybridity",
    delta: "Cultural relativism",
    correct_answer: "Cultural hybridity",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1237,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "What is the term for the process by which individuals from one culture come to adopt the customs and behaviors of another culture?",
    alpha: "Cultural assimilation",
    beta: "Cultural relativism",
    charlie: "Cultural appropriation",
    delta: "Cultural integration",
    correct_answer: "Cultural assimilation",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1238,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "Which term refers to the influence of one language on another due to prolonged contact between the two?",
    alpha: "Linguistic interference",
    beta: "Linguistic assimilation",
    charlie: "Linguistic convergence",
    delta: "Linguistic divergence",
    correct_answer: "Linguistic interference",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1239,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "What is the term for the belief that one's own cultural values and practices are superior to those of other cultures?",
    alpha: "Cultural relativism",
    beta: "Cultural ethnocentrism",
    charlie: "Cultural diversity",
    delta: "Cultural pluralism",
    correct_answer: "Cultural ethnocentrism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1240,
    quiz_id: 124,
    question: "Which term refers to the use of language to reinforce and perpetuate cultural stereotypes and biases?",
    alpha: "Linguistic relativism",
    beta: "Linguistic discrimination",
    charlie: "Linguistic hegemony",
    delta: "Linguistic bias",
    correct_answer: "Linguistic discrimination",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1241,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "What is the term for the ability to speak and understand two languages proficiently?",
    alpha: "Monolingualism",
    beta: "Multilingualism",
    charlie: "Bilingualism",
    delta: "Trilingualism",
    correct_answer: "Bilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1242,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "Which term refers to the use of more than two languages in daily life or communication?",
    alpha: "Bilingualism",
    beta: "Trilingualism",
    charlie: "Multilingualism",
    delta: "Polylingualism",
    correct_answer: "Multilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1243,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "What is the term for a person who is proficient in three languages?",
    alpha: "Monolingual",
    beta: "Bilingual",
    charlie: "Trilingual",
    delta: "Multilingual",
    correct_answer: "Trilingual",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1244,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "Which concept refers to the ability to switch between two or more languages in a conversation or context?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Language immersion",
    correct_answer: "Code-switching",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1245,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "What is the term for a person who can speak more than three languages proficiently?",
    alpha: "Multilingual",
    beta: "Polyglot",
    charlie: "Trilingual",
    delta: "Bilingual",
    correct_answer: "Polyglot",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1246,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "Which term refers to the situation where a person loses proficiency in one language due to extended use of another language?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Language attrition",
    charlie: "Code-switching",
    delta: "Linguistic assimilation",
    correct_answer: "Language attrition",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1247,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "What is the term for the coexistence of two or more languages in a particular region or community?",
    alpha: "Monolingualism",
    beta: "Bilingualism",
    charlie: "Plurilingualism",
    delta: "Language contact",
    correct_answer: "Plurilingualism",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1248,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "Which term refers to the gradual blending or mixing of two or more languages within a community or group?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Language convergence",
    correct_answer: "Language convergence",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1249,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "What is the term for the situation where individuals or groups use a common language for communication despite having different native languages?",
    alpha: "Language attrition",
    beta: "Language shift",
    charlie: "Lingua franca",
    delta: "Diglossia",
    correct_answer: "Lingua franca",
    selected_option: null,
  },
  {
    question_id: 1250,
    quiz_id: 125,
    question: "Which term refers to the practice of using different languages for different purposes or in different contexts?",
    alpha: "Language shift",
    beta: "Code-switching",
    charlie: "Diglossia",
    delta: "Domain-specific language",
    correct_answer: "Diglossia",
    selected_option: null,
  },


];






